What! This must be a mistake...!<P><END>
It's no mistake this time.<P><END>
I can't believe that for all these years...<P><END>
Things are the way they are. You might as well accept it...<P><END>
.......<P><END>
What's wrong, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><END>
You heard us from the waiting room? Sorry...<P><END>
You see, today we found out something very important about Jeff.<P><END>
A long time ago I had the Doctor check my blood type, but now he tells me<WB>
it's wrong!<P><END>
I'm terribly sorry. It must have been some kind of clerical error.<P><END>
And I used to think that my blood type fit my personality so well...<P><END>
