Hello, <NAME_MEMO1>. I've got a favor I'd like to ask of you.<P><END>
This Foal was born at our farm, but for some reason he's not doing<WB>
very well.<WB>
We can't look after him all the time, so do you think you'd be able to<WB>
until he grows up?<P><END>
Won't you reconsider? We really have anywhere else to go...<P><END>
Are you absolutely sure?<P><END>
Accept<END>
Don't accept<END>
Well, I guess I was wrong to depend on you, anyway!<WB>
Bye now.<P><END>
That's great! Thanks so much!<P><C>
In that case, you can even name him!<P><END>
Of course, you don't need to worry about him all that much.<P><C>
Just take care of him, and look after his needs.<P><C>
Most importantly, don't forget to talk to him everyday.<P><C>
Brushing regularly is also a good idea.<P><END>
I'll bring him to the Stable for you.<P><END>
I'll come back again when he gets bigger.<P><C>
Until then please take good care of him, OK?<P><END>
