Mother<END>
Mother<END>
Mother<END>
Mother<END>
<C>What about it, son? Aren't you glad you came on the trip?<P><END>
Father<END>
Father<END>
Father<END>
Father<END>
<C>I'm glad for the vacation, too.  Hey, want to go fishing in the river?<P><END>
<C><MF>?<P><C>
Oh, dear! I can't find our son!<P><END>
<C>What...?<P><END>
Old Man<END>
Old Man<END>
Old Man<END>
Old Man<END>
Old Man<END>
Old Man<END>
Old Man<END>
Old Man<END>
<C>Hey, young man. Why are you crying? Did you get lost?<WB>
What's this? Is that your phone number on your bag?<WB>
Let's call your parents.<P><END>
<C>Thank you so much for helping us find our son!<P><END>
<C>We live in the city, but we wanted to show our son the country on this trip.<P><END>
<C>Is that so?<P><C>
In that case, why not come spend a few days on my farm?<P><END>
<C>You really mean it?<P><END>
<C>Sure! I live alone, so you wouldn't bother anybody. I'd love the company.<P><END>
<C>Isn't this great, son?<WB>
Now you'll have a whole farm to play on!<P><END>
???<END>
<C>y...<P><C>
ey...<P><C>
Hey.<P><END>
<C>!<P><END>
Girl<END>
Girl<END>
Girl<END>
Girl<END>
Girl<END>
<C>You were so quiet that I thought you were dead!<P><END>
<C>This is perfect. I was looking for someone to play together. <WB>
I guess you'll do.<P><END>
<C>It's no fun if you just sit there and say nothing!<P><C>
Why don't you tell me about yourself?<P><END>
<C>Did you have fun?<P><C>
I sure had fun with you. I don't have any grandkids of my own, you know...<P><C>
Well, you have to go now. Farewell!...<P><END>
<C>Is there any chance of you writing an old man a letter once in a while...?<P><END>
<C>Really? Here's my address, then.<P><END>
<C>You're leaving already?<P><END>
<C>If you go, I'll be bored and lonely again...<P><C>
You HAVE to come back, OK?<P><END>
<C>Looks like you've made a friend! Just one more reason to return, I guess.<P><END>
<C>I'll be waiting for your letter...<P><END>
