Do you have a problem with me?<P><END>
Yeah! Don't mess around with my sister!<P><END>
What! Just who do you think you are!?<P><END>
I'm Popuri's brother, and I don't like her seeing you, Kai!<P><END>
What makes you think you can run her life?<P><C>
She can do as she wants!<P><END>
I'm her brother, so sometimes I know what's best for her!<P><END>
I feel sorry for Popuri, that she has a brother like you!<P><END>
Take that back!!<P><C>
...............<P><END>
From now on, I forbid you to see my sister!<P><END>
Oh yeah, what if she comes and visits me anyway?<P><END>
Grrr...<P><END>
