Welcome.<P><END>
I don't think I've seen you before. You must be <NAME_MEMO1>, right?<P><END>
I knew it! I heard about you from the Mayor.<P><C>
Nice to meet you. My name is Ann, and this is my father.<P><END>
Hi. I'm Doug.<P><END>
Hey there, <NAME_MEMO1>! Did you come to eat?<P><END>
Just wait one moment.<P><END>
Since you're new here, I think this one should be our treat!<P><C>
What do you think, Dad?<P><END>
Sure. Just make sure to come back often!<P><END>
See? Why don't you stay and eat?<P><END>
Sounds great!<END>
I really couldn't.<END>
Great! Make him your special, Dad!<P><END>
Just leave it to me! This'll be the best thing you ever ate!<P><END>
Dad's a great cook, you know.<P><END>
Here you are. Eat it while it's hot!<P><END>
Here you are, <NAME_MEMO1>!<P><END>
How does it taste?<P><END>
Do you like it, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><END>
In that case, feel free to have seconds!<P><END>
You're the best, Dad!<P><END>
Of course! Did you doubt me for a second?<P><END>
Eat all you want.<P><END>
A working man has to eat a lot.<P><C>
I like watching you shovel it in like that!<P><C>
I've decided I like you, <NAME_MEMO1>!<P><END>
Don't worry about paying us. Just come back often!<P><C>
I'm always working here.<P><END>
Yeah, come any time and visit Ann. I can tell she'd like it.<P><END>
Dad! Stop teasing me...<P><END>
What? You don't have to be so modest, you know!<P><END>
Exactly!<P><END>
Come back soon!<P><END>
