Now now...Both of you calm down.<P><END>
You be quiet!<P><END>
You shut up too!<P><END>
You don't have to be so rude.<P><END>
Ohh...My stomach is starting to hurt...!<P><END>
Oh, hello, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
Just listen to this. My cousin is sick and staying in the Hospital.<WB>
We decided to send her some Seeds as a get-well present.<P><C>
I wanted to send her Moon Drop Seeds, but Mom wants to send her<WB>
Pink Cat Seeds!<P><END>
I can't believe we're fighting about something like this!<P><END>
Right! So, let's ask <NAME_MEMO1> to decide for us, OK?<P><END>
OK. If that will settle it once and for all.<P><END>
Alright, it's a deal!<P><END>
It's all up to you, <NAME_MEMO1>. Which do you vote for?<P><END>
Moon Drop Seeds<END>
Pink Cat Seeds<END>
I knew you had a good taste, <NAME_MEMO1>!<P><END>
Alright. I give up. Let's send the Seeds Karen wanted to.<P><END>
Ha! Thanks, <NAME_MEMO1>!<P><END>
Hmm...<P><END>
<NAME_MEMO1> thinks so too, so you might as well give up!<P><END>
Fine!...<P><END>
