Sniff...Sniff... I wish I could write as well as this...!<P><END>
Ah, hello, <NAME_MEMO1>!<P><END>
I hope you didn't see me crying just now...<P><END>
I just found this book when I was cleaning out the bookshelves.<P><END>
I wanted to read it in a place with a nice view. <WB>
It turned out to be a wonderful story!<P><END>
Thanks for worrying about me. Do you ever cry like that when you read books?<P><END>
Sometimes.<END>
Never.<END>
I like people who read a lot, and respond to books.<P><C>
I think it means you're smart. Here, try reading this one.<P><END>
That's OK...I've already finished it. I think you'll like this <WB>
book...It made me cry!<P><END>
If you really like books so much, then I'm sure you'll like it, too!<P><END>
Here you are.<P><END>
I'm going back now. I hope you like the book.<P><END>
...Really? That's probably because you haven't read the right books yet! <WB>
I hope you do soon.<P><END>
I have to get back now... Bye, <NAME_MEMO1>!<P><END>
