This isn't it... Neither is this... Now where did it go...?<P><END>
Oh, <NAME_MEMO1>! You scared me!<P><END>
Welcome. Did you come to read a book?<WB>
Hmm? What am I looking for?<P><END>
Well, there's a book I'm using as a reference for the novel I'm writing.<P><C>
I think it's on the first floor, but I can't find it!<P><END>
Terribly sorry to ask, but will you help me find it, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><END>
I'd be glad to.<END>
Sorry, I don't want to.<END>
Really!? That's great of you! It's this kind of book...<P><END>
OK, <NAME_MEMO1>, you look over there.<P><END>
It's not around here... Have you found it yet, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><END>
Will you mind looking a little more? Thanks!<P><END>
That's it! NOW I remember putting it there!<P><END>
Well, I can continue writing! I'm indebted to you, <NAME_MEMO1>!<P><END>
I'm sorry to ask such an unusual favor. Forget I asked.<P><END>
