Wait a second...!<P><END>
Wait, come back!<P><END>
Bad chicken! Don't run away again!<P><END>
Thanks for helping me out.<P><END>
I don't think I've seen you around before? <WB>
My name is Popuri. How do you do.<P><END>
Ah, you're the new guy over at that farm, right?<P><C>
<NAME_MEMO1> is your name? Nice to meet you!<P><END>
Uh-oh. I let the Chicken get away again!<P><END>
Thank you. Chickens are really hard to catch, you know.<P><END>
Do you like Chickens, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><END>
Yes, I do.<END>
No, I don't.<END>
I thought so! I love Chickens, too!<P><C>
I think people who like Chickens are just good people. Don't you agree?<P><END>
I've got to bring her back to the house now.<P><C>
If you ever need help with Chickens, just come to me!<P><END>
Let's go home now, baby!<P><END>
But why not?! They're so cute!<P><END>
Then what are you doing here?<P><C>
It's a Chicken farm, after all...Full of Chickens you hate, right?!<P><C>
Sorry to make you touch a Chicken!<P><END>
Let's go home now, Chickies!<P><END>
