You want to play house outside again?<P><END>
I like it! It's fun!<P><END>
No way...!<P><END>
Today Carter can be Father and Popuri can be Mother.<P><END>
Alright.<P><END>
I'm sorry, but I have a lot of work to do, so I can't play today.<P><END>
Oh no...! We can't play family without a father!...<P><END>
In that case, let's play something else!<P><END>
Now what'll I do...?<P><END>
<NAME_MEMO1>! Perfect timing!<P><END>
These kids want to play, but Carter has to leave. so we can't play their game.<P><END>
Would you be willing to play with the kids for me?<P><END>
It would mean a lot to me, too.<P><END>
Sure, I'll play.<END>
Sorry, I've got work.<END>
Thanks! I knew I could count on you, <NAME_MEMO1>!<P><END>
You're such a nice guy, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
Great!<P><END>
Are we really going to play house now?<P><END>
Welcome back, darling.<P><END>
Hi, Daddy!<P><END>
Welcome home.<P><END>
How was work today? Would you like dinner now?<P><END>
Daddy, listen to this!<P><END>
Today Stu wet his bed.<P><END>
How do you know that!?<P><END>
Stu, we're just playing. You don't have to get so angry...<P><END>
You mean you really wet your bed today...?<P><END>
Enough! I'm going home!<P><END>
Stu, wait...!!<P><END>
I guess that's it for today...<P><END>
I actually like playing house once in a while.<P><C>
It reminds me of when I was a child.<P><END>
Thinking about those days reminds me of this. <WB>
I made it the other day. Here. I'm giving it to you.<P><END>
I'm going home now, too.<P><END>
Oh...That's too bad.<P><END>
If you have to work... I don't blame you...<P><END>
That's too bad. Let's play superheroes instead.<P><END>
No...! I don't want to!!!<P><END>
Well, you don't have to throw a tantrum!<P><END>
In that case, why don't we go exploring?<P><END>
Really? That's great!<P><END>
Should we go right now?<P><END>
Yay!!<P><END>
Yippee!<P><END>
Well, I have to go back to work now. Sorry.<P><C>
I have to lock the Church up until tomorrow, so can you leave?<P><END>
