I can't believe how irresponsible Dad is!<P><C>
Leaving Mom like this and going off in search of some flower we're not<WB>
even sure it exists!!...<P><END>
Don't talk that way about dad!!<P><C>
The whole reason he went away is to cure Mom!<P><END>
Both of you stop it now! Please don't argue about your father!<P><END>
<NAME_MEMO1>, you're here at just the right time.<P><END>
Popuri and Rick are fighting about their dad, you see.<P><C>
They won't listen to me at all...<P><C>
Will you talk some sense into them for me?<P><END>
Our dad was brave enough to go out hunting for a rare flower to cure Mom.<WB>
Rick blames him for leaving us, but I think that's horrible!<P><C>
Dad only left because he loves Mom...<P><END>
Can you believe it?! Dad left without any real information about the <WB>
flower, or a plan about how to find it! <WB>
He'll never find it! That's why he's irresponsible!<P><END>
I agree with Popuri.<END>
I agree with Rick.<END>
Poor Lillia.<END>
See, even <NAME_MEMO1> thinks I'm right.<P><END>
<NAME_MEMO1>! Don't butt into other people's business!<P><END>
Don't get mad at <NAME_MEMO1> just because he doesn't agree<WB>
with you!<P><END>
......Popuri...<P><END>
Thanks for taking my side, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
I'm glad the argument's over! Thank you, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
.............<P><END>
But.... Why?! How could you say that!<P><END>
See, even <NAME_MEMO1> thinks Dad is wrong!<P><END>
Mmm... Looks like I was wrong about you, <NAME_MEMO1>!<P><END>
Popuri! Don't be mean to <NAME_MEMO1>!<P><END>
What!<P><END>
Now they're arguing over <NAME_MEMO1>...<P><C>
Will they ever stop...?<P><END>
........... I'm sorry, Mom...<P><END>
Sorry, Mom.<P><END>
Just...Please stop arguing about your father!!... Ohh...This is all my fault!<P><END>
Nothing's your fault, Mom!<P><END>
Popuri's right. It's not your fault at all, Mom...<P><C>
I'm sorry for talking that way about Dad...<P><END>
That's OK. I know you just talk that way because you're worried about me.<P><END>
