Good morning, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><C>
Today I came to look at your farm. Will you show me around?<P><END>
I'm too busy now!<END>
Sure.<END>
I thought you were nicer than that...<P><C>
I'm going home now...<P><END>
Really? Oh, thank you!<P><END>
So this is where you raise the Sheep and Cows?<P><END>
This is a very nice Chicken Coop you have!<P><C>
If you need to know anything about Chickens, just ask my mom!<P><END>
Thanks for showing me around. It was fun. See you later!<P><END>
