<NAME_MEMO1>? I love you! Could you marry with me?<P><C>
If you ever need a hand, just say the word!<P><END>
A birthday present? for me? What a surprise!<P><END>
You mean this is a present? For me! Awesome!<P><END>
...<NAME_MEMO2>... Thank you so much...! I'm so happy!<P><END>
For me? What a surprise! What a great birthday gift!<P><END>
...Thank you!<P><C>
This is the best birthday ever!...<P><END>
You really are a great guy, <NAME_MEMO2>. I love you!<P><END>
Yeah! Can I really take something so nice...?<P><END>
Thanks! I love getting presents from you!<P><END>
Is this really for me? Thanks so much!<P><END>
Thanks, <NAME_MEMO2>! I love presents!<P><END>
Thanks! This is great!<P><END>
Thanks!<P><END>
Thanks.<P><END>
I know I shouldn't refuse a present, but...<P><END>
You mean this is for me? Hmmm...Thanks.<P><END>
Don't bring that close to me!<P><END>
What are you doing?! Get that out of here!<P><END>
Aww...It's so cute!<P><END>
Eeeek! How can you be so mean?<P><END>
Stop playing scaring me like that! And I thought you were so nice...<P><END>
Wow, it's so pretty... You mean it's for me? Truly?...Thanks!<P><END>
You mean something so nice is really for me...?<P><C>
Thank you so much!... You're sure, now...?<P><END>
You really want to give me something so precious?<P><C>
Thanks! I mean it.<P><END>
This makes me so happy, <NAME_MEMO2>. Thanks!<P><END>
This is the nicest present ever! Thank you!<P><END>
This...This is for me? Thank you.<P><END>
Perfume? What a lovely scent! It smells like... Happiness!<P><END>
This is for me? Thanks.<P><END>
I really don't have any use for Perfume...<P><END>
But you really want to give it to me? In that case...Thanks!<P><END>
Cookies? For the Thanksgiving Festival? How thoughtful of you!<P><END>
These look great! I just love the Spring Thanksgiving Festival!<P><C>
They look even better than I can make!<P><END>
Wow, Cookies!<P><C>
Are these for the Spring Thanksgiving Festival?<P><C>
And I didn't give you anything last Winter! I feel horrible!<P><END>
Thanks...! I didn't expect you to actually give some back in<WB>
return...I'm so happy!<P><END>
You mean...?<P><C>
Umm...Why don't we just go to your house first...?<P><END>
Does that mean what I think it means? Congratulations!<P><C>
I'm sure she's waiting for you!<P><END>
Ha ha ha! What a funny joke!<P><C>
Now...Who do you really mean that for?<P><END>
Come over to my house tomorrow for the Starry Night Festival, OK?<P><END>
I can't wait!<END>
Sorry...<END>
Really? Great! We'll be waiting.<P><END>
Well, if you're already busy, I understand...I guess...<P><END>
We'll make you such a feast you won't regret it! Come around noon, OK?<P><END>
Now I'm getting embarrassed...<P><END>
When I told Elli I thought I was eating too much, she just laughed at me!<P><END>
Good morning! I feel much better today!<P><END>
I'm fine, I'm fine...<P><C>
<END>
Ugghh...<P><END>
Look how big my tummy's gotten!<P><END>
I'm not nervous, but it's fun to watch how my body changes over time...<P><END>
Today at the Clinic, they said the baby would be born tomorrow!<P><END>
So, the Doctor and Elli are both coming tomorrow. You stick around too, OK?<P><END>
Aaargghh!... I can't believe how busy I am!<P><END>
And I thought all babies did was sleep!<P><END>
His face is becoming more and more like yours!<P><END>
My dad thinks he looks like him when he was young, but I think he takes after you.<P><END>
I think <NAME_MEMO6> likes <NAME_MEMO4>!<P><END>
Don't worry, he still likes you the best!<P><END>
I can't wait until we can go on a family picnic!<P><END>
I want to take him to the mountain and show him all kinds of animals!<P><END>
Good morning.<P><C>
<NAME_MEMO6> can talk a little bit these days.<P><END>
Maybe it's because we live on a farm, but he keeps saying "moo-moo"!<P><END>
Hah... I feel so depressed.<P><END>
...Just leave me alone!<P><END>
I've got to get all the housework done before the baby wakes!<P><END>
What's wrong? Why don't you go work?<P><END>
I always get in a bad mood when I get hungry!<P><END>
You don't care what I make for dinner, do you? I barely have the time...<P><END>
Good morning! Looks like a great day!<P><END>
Alright, to work!<P><END>
Work up a good appetite, now!<P><END>
Just work a little longer!<P><END>
Good morning!ret>Feel like putting in a good day's work?<P><END>
Eat, sleep, work! Ah, the farm life is good!<P><END>
What do you want for supper? I still have to learn some more dishes from my dad!<P><END>
You can't keep healthy without three good meals a day!<P><END>
............<P><C>
<END>
Good morning, <NAME_MEMO2>!<P><END>
I've got no complaints...!<P><END>
Do you feel like making dinner today, dear?<P><END>
I can't decide what to make today...<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO2>. What's up?<P><END>
Whenever I start working, my dad gets mad at me and tells me to rest instead!<P><END>
Welcome, <NAME_MEMO2>.<P><END>
My dad wants us all to live at the Inn. I keep telling him it's impossible. Right?<P><END>
............<P><END>
Will you just get out of my way?!<P><END>
Need anything, <NAME_MEMO2>?<P><END>
That's dangerous there!<P><END>
I like working after all!<P><END>
Just a little bit more work!<P><END>
Did you come to eat, <NAME_MEMO2>?<P><END>
I'm learning how to cook from my father. Just wait 'til you try my latest<WB>
dish!<P><END>
I'm so happy with you, <NAME_MEMO2>.<P><END>
Hmm? Embarrassed? Of course not! After all, it's the truth!<P><END>
Welcome, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><C>
We close at 5, so I'll see you then.<P><END>
Today is my mother's... My dad always takes today off, you see.<P><END>
Welcome, <NAME_MEMO1>. Take your time.<P><END>
My father's been in a good mood lately. It's all because of Cliff.<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>. Welcome.<P><END>
Cliff is doing a good job working, I hear.<P><END>
How are you coming on the farm, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><END>
Cliff says he thinks of me as a younger sister. ...That makes me sad.<P><END>
Welcome, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
Listen to this! I got into a fight with Cliff!<P><C>
He told me to act more like a girl! Can you believe it?<P><END>
Cliff hates it when I talk to you like this.<P><C>
I think he's jealous!<P><END>
My dad and Cliff get along so well together I feel left out!<P><END>
Welcome, <NAME_MEMO1>. Hare are you?<P><END>
Hey, <NAME_MEMO1>, do you think Cliff is really happy right now?<P><C>
I think maybe he's doesn't like being tied down...<P><END>
It's hard to take care of things when my dad isn't here.<P><END>
This is the day my mother died.<P><C>
I don't remember her at all, but my dad gets so sad at times like this...<P><END>
Have you adjusted to married life, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><END>
Don't you look forward to going home, with you wife waiting there for you?<P><END>
Hi there, <NAME_MEMO1>. How's your wife?<P><END>
Tell her hi for me!<P><END>
Hello, <NAME_MEMO1>. You look like you're doing a good job on the farm.<P><END>
Having a wife makes working hard worth it, doesn't it?<P><END>
Just the idea of marriage makes me blush!...<P><END>
My father told me not to get embarrassed on the job! He's so strict with me!<P><END>
Welcome!<P><END>
If you want to order something, talk to my dad.<P><END>
Take your time.<P><END>
My dad is always complaining that I'm not "feminine" enough!<P><END>
I like myself just how I am! Besides, I don't need a boyfriend, anyway...<P><END>
Welcome! How goes things on the farm?<P><END>
I like eating food from farms. It tastes so good and fresh!<P><END>
Welcome, <NAME_MEMO1>! Take your time, now.<P><END>
Can I ask you a question? Do you think girls should dress "cute"?<P><END>
Welcome.<P><END>
These days, I think a lot. That's good...but I end up breaking lots of dishes!<P><END>
...Oh, sorry! What was it you wanted?<P><END>
Sometimes we don't have any guests staying here at all! Business can get real slow.<P><END>
When I was a kid, I used to like sleeping in empty guest rooms.<P><C>
Things were more fun, back then...<P><END>
Good morning! Off to work so early?<P><END>
I should take a lesson from you and get up earlier myself!...<P><END>
Welcome. We close at 5, remember.<P><END>
Today is my mom's... Anyway, my dad is taking the day off, today.<P><END>
I've got to clean Cliff's room before he gets back!<P><END>
Yes, Cliff is still staying here at the Inn.<P><END>
I can barely cope without my dad here! We close at 5 sharp!<P><END>
Today is the anniversary of my mother's death.<P><C>
I don't remember her at all but my dad gets so sad.<P><END>
I really don't mind cleaning, you know. I love getting dirty and then<WB>
taking a long, hot bath!<P><END>
We have more guests these days. That makes it much more fun around here!<P><END>
What's up? This is an unusual time to come around here!<P><END>
We've got a room... But you don't want to stay, do you?<P><END>
The Harvest Goddess Spring is really good for your health, you know.<P><C>
And the waterfall is a blast!<P><END>
Another day, another customer to take care of! I hope we get busy...<P><END>
Ahh...I sure like it around here!...<P><END>
I think Cliff's still in his room.<P><END>
So you're here too, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><END>
The air feels so good here in the morning!<P><END>
