Hello... Your name is <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><C>
Mine is Chef, budum. Welcome, budum.<P><END>
Our Tea Party is in the Spring, budum.<P><END>
Did you bring an invitation? Everyone! Get the Tea Set ready!...<P><END>
Sorry, but not everyone is here, budum, so we can't have the Tea Party now.<P><END>
It's not time to have a tea party now. We keep our schedule.<P><END>
We can't have a Tea Party here, budum!<P><END>
Today's my birthday, budum! Thank you!<P><END>
Yipee!! This is great, budum! Thank you!<P><END>
Thanks! This is great, budum!<P><C>
The Kappa loves cucumbers, budum.<P><C>
I think they taste  better cooked, though.<P><END>
Thanks, budum...<P><END>
This isn't so great, budum...<P><END>
Eeee!!! Get it out of here!....<P><END>
Awww...It's so cute, budum!<P><END>
It's so scarry...!<P><END>
Thanks much! Is this really for me, budum?<P><END>
I don't like this! It makes things taste bad, budum.<P><END>
I'll tell you how to make some delicious Sweet Potatos.<P><C>
Not even Doug at the Inn can make these, bubum!<P><C>
They're our favorite dish at our Tea Parties, too.<P><C>
The ingredients are Sweet Potatos, Eggs, Butter, and Sugar, bubum.<P><C>
Mix these all in a Pot and then bake in an Oven. That's all there is too<WB>
it, bubum!<P><C>
It really doesn't need anything else, either.<P><C>
Try it when you get home. I think you'll like it, bubum!<P><END>
What a gorgeous feather, bubum! Shame you can't cook with it...<P><END>
I heard a rumor that there are friends of ours in Forget-me-not Valley, budum?<P><END>
Spring is the season for Tea Parties, budum. We all love Tea Parties.<P><END>
Spring is the season for Tea Parties. We send invitations to our friends.<P><END>
Spring is the season for Tea Parties, budum. Do you like Tea Parties?<P><END>
Spring is the season for Tea Parties, budum. If you came, I would have<WB>
them everyday, budum!<P><END>
I like Spring because it means Tea Parties, budum!<P><END>
We only invite our true friends to Tea Parties, budum!<P><END>
I'm in charge of tea and treats for the Tea Party.<P><END>
If it were Spring all year... We could have Tea Parties all the time, budum!<P><END>
Welcome, budum.<P><END>
Welcome. Thanks for coming, budum.<P><END>
Oh, it's <NAME_MEMO1>, budum!<P><END>
I don't know why, but I had a feeling you'd come today, budum!<P><END>
I just love to cook, budum!<P><END>
Do you like to cook?<P><END>
What should I cook today....budum?<P><END>
I'll help you, if you want, budum.<P><END>
Did you need something?<P><END>
Can you help me?<END>
Let's play.<END>
Nothing in particular.<END>
I'll get started tomorrow, budum.<P><END>
I'll help you if we become better friends, budum.<P><END>
What should I do?<P><END>
Watering<END>
Harvest<END>
Animals<END>
Exit<END>
How long do you want me to water for, budum?<P><END>
1 day<END>
3 days<END>
1 week<END>
Got it. I'll water for 1 day, budum.<P><END>
Got it. I'll water for 3 days, budum.<P><END>
Got it. I'll water for 1 week, budum.<P><END>
How many days do you want me to harvest for, budum?<P><END>
Got it. I'll harvest for 1 day, budum.<P><END>
Got it. I'll harvest for 3 days, budum.<P><END>
Got it. I'll harvest for 1 week, budum.<P><END>
How long do you want me to look after the animals for, budum?<P><END>
Got it. I'll look after the animals for 1 day, budum.<P><END>
Got it. I'll look after the animals for 3 days, budum.<P><END>
Got it. I'll look after the animals for 1 week, budum.<P><END>
Really, budum? Is that so...?<P><END>
We already played today! Let's play tomorrow, budum.<P><END>
I'll play if we become better friends, budum.<P><END>
How should we play?<P><END>
Let's play the watering game, budum!<P><END>
I think I've gotten better than before, budum!<P><END>
I hope I don't make too many mistakes...<P><END>
Let's play the harvest game, budum!<P><END>
Let's play the animal husbandry game, budum!<P><END>
What? You don't want to play, budum? That's too bad...<P><END>
Just let me know if you need me later, budum.<P><END>
We're already done working for the day!<P><END>
I haven't gotten very good at it yet, budum...<P><END>
I think I'm getting the hang of it, budum...!<P><END>
Harvesting is fun, budum! Let's do more!<P><END>
Now I'm a master harvester! Just leave it to me, budum!<P><END>
Watering is fun, budum! Let's do more!<P><END>
Now I'm a master waterer! Just leave it to me, budum!<P><END>
Taking care of animals is fun, budum! Let's do more!<P><END>
Now I'm great at taking care of the animals! Just leave it to me, budum!<P><END>
Let's do more tomorrow!<END>
Your job is done for now.<END>
I'll do my best, budum.<P><END>
OK. Tomorrow I'll rest, budum.<P><END>
