Well I haven't seen you around these parts before!<P><C>
Oh, you're the new lad up at the farm, eh? My name's Doug, and I<WB>
run this here Inn.<P><END>
Wow, it's been years since anybody but Ann gave me a birthday present!<P><END>
Thanks a lot. I mean it!<P><END>
You're a good, guy, you know that?<P><END>
Thanks.<P><END>
What a surprise!... Thanks, now.<P><END>
Just what do you expect me to do with this!?...<P><END>
Ha ha ha...It's so cute!<P><END>
There are some animals I just can't stand.. This is one of them!<P><END>
This is for me?<P><C>
If you want to give it to Ann, give it to her yourself!<P><C>
I'll take it, though...<P><END>
I think I gave something like this to Ann's mother ages ago...<P><C>
I'll give this to Ann.<P><END>
Perfume, huh? Didn't I give the same one to Ann years ago...?<P><C>
Well, I'll give this to her. Thanks.<P><END>
As a thanks, I'll tell you the recipe to my famous Cheese Fondue. Have you<WB>
heard of it?<P><C>
Don't forget this now.<P><C>
The only ingredient is Cheese. Use a Knife to cut it into bite-size bits.<P><C>
All you need is a Pot! If you want to make it even better, try adding<WB>
Salt or Wine.<P><C>
You'll love it!<P><END>
You'll need this Blue Feather to propose, so take good care of it. <WB>
Good luck!<P><END>
Do you know that Gourmet who judges the Cooking Festival? He's a real big-shot in<WB>
the cooking world.<P><C>
He's eaten cuisine the world over, you know!<P><END>
Welcome! Oh, it's you, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
How is <NAME_MEMO6>? I'll give him lots of gifts for his next <WB>
birthday!<P><END>
How is Ann doing?<P><END>
I hope Ann isn't causing to much trouble for you!<P><END>
Cliff is a really good guy. He says he might stay here permanently!<P><END>
Ann is happy, and he seems to be in heaven too!<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>. How are things at the farm?<P><END>
As you can see, we're closed for the day! I'm dead tired, too!<P><END>
Hey, how's it going?<P><END>
Take your time.<P><END>
So you've finally decided to pay a visit!<P><END>
Eat up,you need the energy!<P><END>
Did you come for a break, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><END>
I never get a chance for a vacation! Comes with the job,<WB>
I guess...<P><END>
This is a strange hour...<P><END>
Come when we're open! I'd headed for bed.<P><END>
Right now I'm cooking. Watch out for the flame!<P><END>
Right now I'm busy. Wait for me outside, will ya?<P><END>
Hi.<P><END>
Ann's watching the store for me, but I'm worried about her alone...<P><END>
A year passes pretty quick around here, doesn't it, <NAME_MEMO1>....?<P><END>
Don't you ever miss anybody, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><END>
