Ah, so you are <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><C>
My name is Ellen. Much obliged...<P><END>
My legs? They became bad when I got sick years ago, so I can't move <WB>
around very much.<P><END>
A present, for me?<P><C>
My goodness! What a surprise, to be receiving gifts from young men<WB>
at my age! Tee-hee...<P><END>
I appreciate it very much. Come around any time, you hear?<P><END>
Thanks much! What a pleasant surprise!<P><END>
You really didn't have to go to all this trouble.<P><END>
Well...umm... Thanks, I guess...<P><END>
Why would you give something like this to me?<P><END>
Now how cute this is!<P><END>
What a surprising present!<P><END>
What a wonderful gift, young man!...<P><C>
Didn't Saibara once give me something like this...?<P><END>
You're going to give something like this to a little old lady like me...?<P><C>
I feel young again!...<P><END>
Perfume... What a thoughtful present this is, young man!<P><C>
I feel young again!...<P><END>
Do you want a great recipe for Sandwiches?<P><C>
What was it...? Oh yeah, here goes.<P><C>
First, spread Butter on some Bread, then put on some Cucumbers and<P><C>
Tomatoes. Hard-Boiled egg is good, too.<P><C>
Elli tries out lots of new dishes on Stu, you know.<P><END>
This Blue Feather sure does bring me back...<P><C>
I was handed mine more than 50 years ago!<P><END>
I heard that the child of that person living up in Forget-me-not Valley...What<WB>
was their name...? Oh yeah,<P><C>
<MF>,! I heard <MF>,'s child <MF>- was <WB>
just cute as a button!<P><END>
Elli has always helped take care of Stu, especially after my legs went bad.<P><END>
Elli has always liked the Doctor, you know.<P><C>
I'm so glad they got married!<P><END>
Oh, <NAME_MEMO1>. Welcome.<P><END>
And how is <NAME_MEMO6> doing?<P><C>
If only my legs healed, I could go over for a visit!<P><END>
It's certainly gotten warmer, hasn't it? Stu shows me the new bugs<WB>
he catches everyday!<P><END>
This heat makes me so sleepy! Maybe I'll just doze off for a bit...<P><END>
Wow, you sure are sweaty! It's cool indoors, because the sun doesn't <WB>
hit the house.<P><END>
When you get sweaty, you should always wash off in a bath.<P><C>
If you don't, you're liable to catch cold!<P><END>
I love Fall, because there's always so much good to eat!<P><C>
I eat a lot too, you know!<P><END>
Sometimes, the Doctor brings me mushrooms he gathers when he goes to<WB>
pick medicinal herbs.<P><C>
He's so sweet!<P><END>
Notice how the snow is built up outside? That happens every year.<P><C>
It gets so cold Mr. Sun can't melt the snow.<P><END>
Farms are lonely places in the winter time...<P><C>
I've never been to yours, but I bet the Chickens and Cows can't wait <WB>
for Spring<P><END>
