Now, I haven't seen your face around here...<P><C>
Are you the new owner of that farm?<P><C>
I guess I should introduce myself. My name is Elli. Nice to meet you!<P><END>
A birthday present? For me?! How great!<P><END>
Thanks! I'm happy to get birthday presents no matter how old I get!<P><END>
You mean this is a birthday present...for me?<P><C>
Can I really accept something so valuable...?<P><END>
A birthday present? For me? What a nice surprise!<P><END>
This is for me? What a nice gift. Thanks.<P><END>
Thanks, <NAME_MEMO2>. I'm so glad I married you!<P><END>
This is for me? Thanks! You're sweet!<P><END>
Thanks, <NAME_MEMO2>. I love these, you know.<P><END>
Thanks! What a great gift? Is it really for me?<P><END>
You're a always so nice to me! Thanks!<P><END>
Thanks! This is great!<P><END>
Thanks.<P><END>
What's this? Will you get mad if I don't accept it?<P><END>
I really should try to like this, I know...I always tell Stu to accept gifts...<P><END>
I think you need a change in attitude, if you're going around giving things<WB>
like this to people!<P><END>
Why would you give this to me? Do you hate me?<P><END>
Oh...It's so incredibly cuuute!<P><END>
It's so cute! Do you like him too?<P><END>
Eeee!!! Get it away from me! You're too old to be playing pranks like that!<P><END>
Eeee!!! Get it away from me! You're just as bad as Stu!<P><END>
Thanks! You are so kind!<P><END>
Can I really accept it? It looks so valuable!<P><END>
Yeah! Is this really for me? I'll treasure it always!<P><END>
Thanks...! I had no idea I'd get such a wonderful present!<P><END>
Thanks! It must have been very expensive!<P><END>
Wow, this is great! You're really giving me such a nice present?<P><END>
Perfume! What a nice gift. I can't wait to put it on...!<P><END>
Thanks. I can't wait to use it.<P><END>
I've never ever gotten anything so nice! Thank you so much!<P><END>
What...? I don't want... Wait, it looks pretty good!<P><C>
You don't mean anything by this, do you...?<P><END>
Cookies for the Thanksgiving Festival? Thanks!<P><END>
Now I'm embarrassed I didn't give anything to you last year!<P><END>
...Thanks! You really are a gentleman, you know that?<P><END>
I'm so nervous all the sudden...Let's just go to your house, OK?<P><END>
You look nervous. Relax!<P><END>
Sorry, but I can't leave the Doctor's side.<P><END>
Do you want to come to my house tomorrow for the Starry Night Festival?<P><C>
Grandma and Stu will be so pleased!<P><END>
Sounds like fun.<END>
Sorry, I have other plans.<END>
We'll make lots of great food!<P><END>
I guess I should have known you'd already have plans...<P><END>
We'll make lots of delicious food, so just you wait!<P><END>
I'm so glad! I've wanted a baby for so long!<P><END>
Why don't you name him, <NAME_MEMO2>? Or am I taking things too fast?<P><END>
Good morning. The baby is fine.<P><END>
I'm so glad I was born a woman! What a miraculous experience this is!<P><END>
Good morning. I could feel the baby moving last night!<P><END>
It's so active... I bet it's a boy!<P><END>
The Doctor said the baby is due tomorrow, so stick around, OK?<P><END>
Don't worry, you can leave the hard part to the Doctor!<P><END>
Stu is telling everybody that he's going to have a younger brother!<P><END>
Grandma is also so happy about <NAME_MEMO6>!<P><END>
I know everybody thinks their own baby is the cutest, but...!<P><END>
Stu comes often to look at the baby.<P><C>
He's so curious about it!<P><END>
He can already stand up, see! Pretty soon he'll be walking!<P><END>
Now he's so big I get tired holding him!<P><END>
This makes me remember when Stu was small...<P><C>
Now that I think about it, I was a little too strict with him!<P><END>
When he gets older he'll start making friends!<P><END>
Good morning!<P><C>
<NAME_MEMO6> wants to talk to you, see!<P><END>
What if he becomes sassy like Stu always was...?<P><C>
I hope I raise him right...<P><END>
Sorry, but I'm too tired to talk right now...<P><END>
..........<P><END>
Mornin'!<P><END>
How about going to work?<P><END>
Hmmm...<P><END>
How about going to eat at the Inn tonight?<P><END>
Work hard today, dear.<P><END>
Another day, another set of meals to make...<P><END>
Why don't you go work now and leave me alone?<P><END>
Good morning! How are you feeling?<P><END>
Don't overdo it, now!<P><C>
After all, think of all the time you'll waste if you have to check into<WB>
the Clinic?<P><END>
Did you wash your hands yet?<P><END>
I'm sorry! I haven't quite gotten the hang of cooking yet! Don't get sick...<P><END>
Good morning, <NAME_MEMO2>!<P><END>
Another day, 100 more jobs to do!<P><END>
Resting? It is a good idea not to work too hard...<P><END>
What do you think you're doing, <NAME_MEMO2>...?!<P><END>
Don't worry, the baby will be fine! We can count on the Doctor, after all.<P><END>
Instead of worrying, why don't you go work?<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO2>. Is <NAME_MEMO6> behaving without me?<P><END>
After all, we have to work for <NAME_MEMO6>, too!<P><END>
You're getting in my way! If you aren't sick, go home and work!<P><END>
Shhh!!... This is a hospital!<P><END>
What's wrong?<P><END>
I'll be home at the usual time, so you go home now, OK?<P><END>
Shouldn't you be working?<P><END>
Have the Doctor look at you right away if you don't feel well!<P><END>
What's wrong? My cooking didn't give you indigestion, did it?<P><END>
For people who say things like that...we use the extra big needles!<P><END>
Are you feeling bad, <NAME_MEMO2>?<P><END>
You're OK?<P><C>
Thank goodness! Sometimes I get so worried about you!<P><END>
Are you feeling bad, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><END>
If you think you're sick, go see the Doctor immediately!<P><END>
Did you come to buy some medicine?<P><END>
I think it takes real courage to get married.<P><END>
Everyone says I blush like a little girl in front of the Doctor.<P><C>
Almost like we aren't married at all.<P><END>
I want a baby as soon as possible. I took care of Stu, so I think I know how<WB>
to take care of babies!<P><END>
The Doctor asks if I'll stay with him at the Clinic for good.<P><C>
I told him I would for as long as I could...<P><END>
Hi there. Do you need to se the Doctor? Does it hurt somewhere?<P><END>
I just realized recently that the Doctor looks a lot like my dad...<P><END>
Are you OK? Have you caught a cold?<P><END>
Working with a doctor is really interesting, you know.<P><END>
Hello, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
How are you feeling? If you feel bad, don't hesitate to tell the Doc!<P><END>
You seem so happy, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><C>
I smile just looking at you!<P><END>
Say 'hi' to your wife for me, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
Are things going smoothly between you and your wife?<P><END>
Don't fight with your wife, now! Just do what she says, ha ha..<P><END>
My grandmother is so happy about our marriage!<P><END>
Stu is happy, too. He thinks he'll get to play with you more!<P><END>
Is there anything wrong?<P><END>
If you need to buy medicine, talk to me. If you need to be examined, ask<WB>
the Doctor.<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>. Is something the matter?<P><END>
Work on the farm must be so exhausting! I can't believe you do it.<P><C>
<END>
We've always been midwives in our family, all the way up to my great-grandmother!<P><END>
The flu seems to be going around, so wash your hands 5 times a day.<P><END>
You know my grandmother, don't you?<P><C>
I'm hoping I'll learn enough to help her here.<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>. Have you gotten used to farm life, yet?<P><END>
Why did you come to this town, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><C>
I'm curious.<P><END>
Hello, <NAME_MEMO1>! Are you feeling ill?<P><END>
I'm glad to see you, <NAME_MEMO1>, but I worry when you show up here!<P><END>
Maybe I'll quit the Clinic when I get married...<P><END>
I'm not sure I have enough strength to be both a wife and a nurse!<P><END>
Good morning, <NAME_MEMO1>. Today the Clinic is closed, so I'm stay home to<WB>
take care of Grandma.<P><END>
The Doctor likes to search for wild herbs on the mountain, you know.<P><C>
When it's rainy, though, he talks to Carter. I wonder what they talk about?...<P><END>
Good morning, <NAME_MEMO1>. I think the Doctor can see you now.<P><END>
But...wait!<P><END>
Unless you're in a hurry, would you mind waiting until opening time?<P><C>
I like to let him rest in the mornings...<P><END>
Today I'm going shopping. Both for me and the Doctor.<P><END>
Days off sure are relaxing!<P><END>
But...I do find myself missing the Doctor...<P><END>
There's more work tomorrow. Take care!<P><END>
This room has lots of the Doctor's books.<P><C>
I like to come here after work to study.<P><END>
I don't understand the books in that other room. They just make me tired!<P><END>
Hello, <NAME_MEMO1>! The Clinic is closed today!<P><END>
I usually go visit my grandmother on my days off. If you want, come visit us.<P><END>
Good morning, <NAME_MEMO1>!<P><END>
You're up and about quite early! I'm always so sleepy in the mornings...<P><END>
Good evening, <NAME_MEMO1>. I was so glad to see my grandmother and Stu today!<P><END>
Tomorrow's another busy day at the Clinic!<P><END>
Good evening, <NAME_MEMO1>. Work hard today?<P><END>
Isn't this a strange hour to be about?<P><END>
The Doctor insists I relax at home on my days off.<P><END>
The Doctor is probably at the Library or Church. He likes quiet places.<P><END>
Hello. We're closed on Wednesdays.<P><C>
You know, we rarely meet outside the Clinic...<P><END>
Do me a favor and talk to my grandmother, OK? She gets so lonely by herself.<P><END>
Today I'm shopping. I'm also here to pay the Doctor's bill.<P><END>
Sasha is so kind. She always visits my grandmother on her <WB>
days off.<P><END>
