Hi, I haven't seen you around here before!<P><C>
Ah...I know, you're <NAME_MEMO1>, right? Thomas mentioned you.<P><C>
I'm Lillia. Very nice to meet you!<P><END>
Today is my birthday, you know.<P><C>
Thank you so much!<P><C>
How old do I look...?<P><END>
Oh...Thank you so much! My husband used to bring me this...<P><END>
Thank you!<P><C>
I wish Rick knew what I liked, too...<P><END>
Thank you!<P><END>
You've got to be kidding...!<P><END>
............... Ewww!!! That's gross! Get it away from me!...<P><END>
How cute! Hi sweetie!<P><END>
Don't bring that close to me!<P><END>
This is for me? Really?<P><C>
It's been a long time since a man gave me such a nice present! Tee-hee...<P><END>
This is for me...? Thanks...I'm flattered...<P><END>
Once, my husband went to town to get me some Perfume for my birthday, but he <WB>
didn't come back until the birthday after that!<P><END>
While I'm thinking of it, let me tell you the recipe for Scrambled Eggs. It's<P><C>
easy. All you do is put Oil in a Frying Pan, then put in the Eggs.<WB>
That's it!<P><C>
But, it won't taste very good like that.<P><C>
Use a Whisk to fluff up the Eggs, or add Butter and Mayonnaise. Kids love<WB>
it that way.<P><C>
Some people say you should only have one Egg per day, but I say eat <WB>
all you want!<P><END>
Ah, a Blue Feather...<P><C>
My husband went off to look for one for me, but then didn't come back for a <WB>
long time!<P><END>
My husband wrote me a while ago, saying he would write more letters.<P><C>
I wonder where he is now...?<P><END>
Oh, I'm sorry. When I'm taking a rest, the store has to be closed.<P><C>
My children are not home all the time, so only I can mind the store.<P><END>
I can't take care of the Chickens, so I at least have to look after <WB>
the store!<P><END>
The store is closed today, since I have to go to the Clinic.<P><END>
If you came to buy Chicken Feed, I suggest you make it yourself.<P><C>
There's a Mill at your farm, right? You can make Feed in that.<P><END>
How is <NAME_MEMO6>? I bet he's grown so much by now!<P><END>
Sasha says I look very young for my age and don't look like a grandmother.<P><END>
I haven't been feeling very well recently, so I haven't been outside.<P><C>
That's why I haven't seen you much lately.<P><END>
My husband left to find herbs to heal me.<P><C>
I wish he'd just stayed home, though...<P><END>
When we went on a honeymoon, my husband brought back two Chickens<WB>
as souvenirs.<P><END>
Those Chickens laid so many eggs for us, we ended up with more Chickens than<WB>
we knew what to do with!<P><C>
That's why we started a Poultry Farm.<P><END>
The fresh air outside feels good, doesn't it?<P><END>
Ah, <NAME_MEMO1>. How are you today?<P><END>
Medicine can be so expensive...!<P><C>
The Doctor always tells me I can pay later, but still...<P><END>
It would be nice to do something fun for a change...<P><END>
If I am reborn, I hope I become someone as healthy as you, <NAME_MEMO1>!<P><END>
