Hello... Your name is <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><C>
Mine is Staid, budum. Welcome, budum.<P><END>
Our Tea Party is in the Spring, budum.<P><END>
Did you bring an invitation? Everyone! Get the Tea Set ready!...<P><END>
Sorry, but not everyone is here, budum, so we can't have the Tea Party now.<P><END>
Now isn't the time for a Tea Party, budum. Come at the right time!<P><END>
We can't have a Tea Party here, budum!<P><END>
Today's my birthday, budum! Thank you!<P><END>
Yipee!! This is wonderful, budum! Thank you!<P><END>
Thanks! This is great, budum!<P><END>
Thanks, budum...<P><END>
This isn't so great, budum...<P><END>
......!!<P><END>
A small friend for me! I love to work, budum. Just let me know if you need<WB>
my help, budum.<P><END>
Yiiikes! You scared me, budum.<P><END>
Wowww... It sparkles pretty like a diamond, budum...<P><END>
Thanks much! Is this really for me, budum?<P><END>
It smells wonderful! The woods have no smell like this, budum!<P><END>
Weee!  What a pretty feather!  I bet it has special power, budum!<P><END>
I heard a rumor that there are friends of ours in Forget-me-not Valley, budum?<P><END>
Spring is the season for Tea Parties.  I can't wait!<P><END>
Spring is the season for Tea Parties, budum. Work is important,<WB>
but so are Tea Parties!<P><END>
Spring is the season for Tea Parties, budum. Which do you like better,<WB>
work or Tea Parties?<P><END>
Spring is the season for Tea Parties, budum. We look forward to <WB>
having you there!<P><END>
At Tea Parties, we invite our friends for tea and snacks, budum?<P><END>
I could never decide between Tea Parties and work...<P><END>
Tea Parties are best with friends, budum!<P><END>
If you come to our Tea Party, I won't mind missing work as much, budum.<P><END>
Did you come to ask for work, budum?<P><END>
Welcome, budum! Work?<P><END>
Welcome, budum! Need some help?<P><END>
I was expecting you to come, budum!<P><END>
I love to work, but...<P><END>
I like to work, budum.<P><END>
If a true friend asks me to work for him, it's hard to refuse, budum.<P><END>
I can't wait to go to your farm, budum!<P><END>
Do you need something?<P><END>
Can you help me?<END>
Let's play.<END>
Nothing in particular.<END>
I'll get started tomorrow, budum.<P><END>
I'll help you if we become better friends, budum.<P><END>
What should I do?<P><END>
Watering<END>
Harvest<END>
Animals<END>
Exit<END>
How long do you want me to water for, budum?<P><END>
1 day<END>
3 days<END>
1 week<END>
Got it. I'll water for 1 day, budum.<P><END>
Got it. I'll water for 3 days, budum.<P><END>
Got it. I'll water for 1 week, budum.<P><END>
How many days do you want me to harvest for, budum?<P><END>
Got it. I'll harvest for 1 day, budum.<P><END>
Got it. I'll harvest for 3 days, budum.<P><END>
Got it. I'll harvest for 1 week, budum.<P><END>
How long do you want me to look after the animals for, budum?<P><END>
Got it. I'll look after the animals for 1 day, budum.<P><END>
Got it. I'll look after the animals for 3 days, budum.<P><END>
Got it. I'll look after the animals for 1 week, budum.<P><END>
Really, budum? Is that so...?<P><END>
We already played today! Let's play tomorrow, budum.<P><END>
I'll play if we become better friends, budum.<P><END>
How should we play?<P><END>
Let's play the watering game, budum!<P><END>
I think I've gotten better than before, budum!<P><END>
I hope I don't make too many mistakes...<P><END>
Let's play the harvest game, budum!<P><END>
Let's play the animal husbandry game, budum!<P><END>
What? You don't want to play, budum? That's too bad...<P><END>
If you say so. Come again, budum...<P><END>
We're already done working for the day!<P><END>
I haven't gotten very good at it yet, budum...<P><END>
I think I'm getting the hang of it, budum...!<P><END>
Harvesting is fun, budum! Let's do more!<P><END>
Now I'm a master harvester! Just leave it to me, budum!<P><END>
Watering is fun, budum! Let's do more!<P><END>
Now I'm a master waterer! Just leave it to me, budum!<P><END>
Taking care of animals is fun, budum! Let's do more!<P><END>
Now I'm great at taking care of the animals! Just leave it to me, budum!<P><END>
Let's do more tomorrow!<END>
Your job is done for now.<END>
I'll do my best, budum.<P><END>
OK. Tomorrow I'll rest, budum.<P><END>
