Hey, how are you! My name is Zack, and I'm in charge of shipping <WB>
around here.<P><C>
I'll come to pick up whatever you have to ship everyday except holidays.<P><END>
Awww...shucks...! How did you know it was my birthday? I'm touched!<P><END>
Thanks a lot! This is really excellent!<P><END>
Thanks. You really shouldn't have...<P><END>
Thanks a bunch.<P><END>
The thought is appreciated, but I don't really need it...<P><END>
I can't believe you would try to give this away!<P><END>
Cute! I love animals, you know.<P><END>
Eww....Did you know I hate bugs?<P><END>
You're really giving this to me....? I've always wanted one, too!<P><C>
Was it hard to find?<P><END>
You're really giving this to me? I think I'll give it to...<P><END>
Perfume, huh? Thanks!<P><END>
Oh, that's right! I was going to tell you how to make some <WB>
delicious Fried Noodles!<P><C>
All you do is put Oil in a Frying Pan, then fry the noodles! That's it!<P><C>
You can even add Eggs or Vegetables to make it taste even better.<P><END>
Hmmph! You have it lucky, you know that!?...<P><C>
The girl I wanted to marry up and married someone else! And I thought she<P><C>
would wait until I was older...<P><END>
You know the Fishing Rod I gave you?<P><C>
That belongs to Greg, who used to live in my house. He loves fishing.<P><C>
He said he was going to catch every kind of fish there was, and he up and<P><C>
left! I wonder how he's doing on his quest...?<P><END>
Hey, what's up? Busy, lately?<P><END>
Just keep those shipments coming!<P><END>
It's fun shipping things, you know.<P><END>
One perk is that you end up knowing everybody!<P><C>
I like talking to folks.<P><END>
How's the work coming? Keep at it now!<P><END>
I'll come again around 5 to pick stuff up. Ship all you can!<P><END>
Just between you and me... There's a lady I have my heart set on.<P><C>
She's already married, though... I'm not telling who!<P><END>
I wonder when Rod's coming back... It worries me!<P><END>
Hey, <NAME_MEMO1>! Don't work too hard, now!<P><END>
How are your shipments coming? I'm counting on you, now!<P><END>
Good work today. See you tomorrow!<P><END>
Done for today, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><C>
You seem to be a hard worker. Keep at it!<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>. I shipped that Ore off to Saibara for you!<P><END>
It sells better if Saibara makes it into something first, see.<P><END>
Hey, <NAME_MEMO1>, Do you think girls like getting surprise gifts...?<P><END>
Oh, never mind... Forget I mentioned it!<P><END>
Should I go there and pick that up, or to that other place and pick up the <WB>
other thing first...?<P><END>
<NAME_MEMO1>, I'm working now!<P><END>
Is the farming going well? Despite how it seems, I really envy you...<P><END>
The farming life seems to suit you pretty well, <NAME_MEMO1>!<P><END>
