To raise crops, first use your Hoe to till your field.<P><C>
Press the B Button to use equipped Tools.<P><END>
You can't till when there is an obstruction in the way.<P><C>
Use a Sickle to cut Weeds, or pull it out and throw it away.<P><END>
Use the A Button to pull out grass.<P><END>
Use the A Button to throw away what you're holding.<P><END>
Use a Hammer to smash apart Stones, or pick them up and throw them away.<P><END>
However, you can't throw Stones away on your field.<P><C>
You must bring them to the water's edge.<P><END>
You cannot lift large or huge Stones.<P><C>
You will have to upgrade your Hammer at the Blacksmith's to smash them.<P><END>
Hold down the B Button to charge your Hammer, then release it. <WB>
You can't charge your Hammer until you upgrade it.<P><END>
Use your Axe to clear away Branches, or pick them up and throw them away.<P><END>
You cannot throw away Branches on your field. You must bring them to <WB>
the water's edge.<P><END>
You cannot lift up Stumps. You must chop them up with your Axe after the <WB>
blacksmith has upgraded it.<P><END>
Use Seeds on tilled soil to plant them in a 3x3 pattern around you.<P><C>
Be careful not to seed untilled ground.<P><END>
You can purchase Seeds at the Supermarket or other places.<P><END>
Use a Watering Can to water your crops.<P><C>
First you have to fill it with water.<P><END>
Equip the Watering Can, then press the B Button near water.<P><END>
Your crops will grow only if you water them once a day for many days.<P><END>
Continue watering and your crops will bloom.<P><END>
Once crops bloom, press the A Button to harvest them.<P><END>
To ship harvested crops, press the A Button in front of the Shipment box.<P><END>
