I won't take on another job until I finish the first one. That's how I work.<P><END>
I won't take on another job until I finish the first one. That's how I work.<P><END>
I won't take on another job until I finish the first one. That's how I work.<P><END>
I won't take on another job until I finish the first one. That's how I work.<P><END>
You don't have enough Lumber.<P><END>
You don't have enough Lumber.<P><END>
It'll take 3 days to complete. Are you sure?<P><END>
It'll take 3 days to complete. Are you sure?<P><END>
Don't you need anything else?<P><END>
Are you sure now?<P><END>
You sure you don't want to change it?<P><END>
I'll put the Lumber in the Wood bin, then!<P><END>
Thanks. You can't hold anything else, so I'll deliver it to your home.<P><END>
Thanks. You can't hold some of these, so I'll deliver them to your home.<P><END>
Much obliged!<P><END>
Build<END>
Don't build<END>
Upgrade<END>
Upgrade<END>
Don't upgrade<END>
Don't upgrade<END>
Alright, I'll start the upgrade tomorrow, then.<P><END>
Alright, I'll start the upgrade tomorrow, then.<P><END>
Are you sure?<P><END>
Are you sure?<P><END>
Need anything more?<P><END>
