Tools <END>
Items <END>
First, select a Tool to be upgraded.<P><END>
This is...c-cursed! What are you thinking!!<P><END>
This is...c-cursed! What are you thinking!!<P><END>
Next, select an Ore to upgrade that Tool with.<P><END>
Next, select an Ore to upgrade that Tool with.<P><END>
That can't be upgraded.<P><END>
That can't be upgraded.<P><END>
You can't use that to upgrade Tools. You need a better Ore instead.<P><END>
You can't use that to upgrade Tools. You need a better Ore instead.<P><END>
You can't use that to upgrade Tools. You need a better Ore instead.<P><END>
A real man doesn't change his mind, you know.<P><END>
A real man doesn't change his mind, you know.<P><END>
You don't have enough experience to upgrade that Tool.<P><END>
That Tool has already been improved with the same Ore.<P><END>
Hmmph! What are you trying to do, downgrade your Tools?!<P><END>
