Thanks very much! Come again any time!<P><END>
Thanks very much! Come again any time!<P><END>
Thanks very much. The Record Player is old, so I'll have it delivered.<P><END>
Thanks again.<P><END>
Thanks again.<P><END>
Thanks very much!<P><C>
Oh, it looks like you can't carry it! No worries, I'll have it delivered.<P><END>
Thanks very much!<P><C>
Oh, it looks like you can't carry it! No worries, I'll have it delivered.<P><END>
Sure you don't need anythign else?<P><END>
