It looks like you can't hold anything more.<P><END>
Your farm's Chicken Coop is already full!<P><END>
The Chickens like it if you name them, you know.<P><END>
You don't have any Chickens you can sell...!<P><END>
Are you sure you're not interested?<P><END>
So you're not going to buy...?<P><END>
I'll buy it for<END>
Yes<END>
No<END>
Thanks! Come again.<P><C>
I'll tell Rick to put the Feed you purchased in your Feed Bin.<P><END>
Thanks! Come gain.<P><C>
Oh...it looks like you can't hold that many. I'll ask Rick to deliver them.<P><END>
Thanks! Come again. I'll have Rick deliver the Medicine you bought.<P><END>
Thanks! Come again.<P><END>
I'll tell Rick to put the Chicken you purchased in your Chicken Coop.<P><END>
Do you need anything else?<P><END>
Do you need anything else?<P><END>
I'll ask Rick to bring the Chickens you sold from your Chicken Coop.<P><END>
