Welcome, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
I'm glad you came. I have something I wanted to ask you.<P><END>
It's about Ann. You see...Her mom died a long time ago, and I've<WB>
had to raise her by myself.<P><C>
It's only worked out so well because she's such a great girl. <WB>
I'm really grateful to her.<P><END>
That is why I want her to find a good husband. I want her to be happy.<P><END>
Until she met you, she never talked about boys at all. <WB>
Now she talks about you all the time, though.<P><C>
So..what do you think about Ann?<P><END>
I like her.<END>
Only as a friend.<END>
Really! That's great!! I was so nervous...<P><END>
Oh, <NAME_MEMO1>. Welcome.<P><END>
Ann, come over here next to <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
Why? Is something the matter?<P><END>
Just get over here!...<P><END>
Cough... Ann...What do you think of <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><END>
What...?<P><END>
That's none of your business, Dad!<P><END>
Of course it's my business! You're my daughter!<P><END>
.......!<P><END>
Ha ha ha...! It's not often Ann gets embarrassed!<P><END>
Why are you getting red, too? Well, you two should talk about this.<P><END>
That's too bad... Be a good friend to her, then.<P><END>
