La la la.... la la la...<P><END>
Oh, <NAME_MEMO1>! You scared me! Don't sneak up on me like that!<P><END>
That's OK. I'm not really mad.<P><END>
What was I doing? Cleaning, of course!<P><C>
I love to clean. It makes me happy to see everything become so nice and tidy.<P><C>
Do you like to clean, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><END>
I like cleaning.<END>
I hate cleaning.<END>
Ha ha, I knew it! I knew you like it! Good for you.<P><C>
My dad hates cleaning, so I have to do all of it around here.<P><C>
It's a good thing I like it so much!<P><END>
That's too bad. You should really try it. You might like it!<P><C>
My dad hates cleaning, too. What is it with men?...<P><END>
