Hi there, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
Are you surprised to see me at the Beach?<P><C>
We used to come here often when my parents were alive.<P><C>
It has lots of memories for me...<P><END>
I come when I have a lot on my mind.<P><C>
I feel like my parents can hear me here.<P><END>
Today I came about Stu...<P><END>
Stu always makes trouble, and doesn't mind me at all!<P><C>
I've tried to be like a mother to him, but I don't think I've done a good job.<P><END>
You've spoiled him.<END>
You're doing a great job!<END>
I knew I should have been stricter with him...<P><C>
Everyone else in town probably thinks so, too... Ahh...I'm going home now.<P><END>
Thanks, <NAME_MEMO1>! If you say so, then I can be confident I'm doing<WB>
a good job.<P><END>
