I want to show you something nice, Sis!<P><END>
What is it?<P><END>
Here!<P><END>
Stu! Don't play tricks on me like that!<P><END>
Don't get so mad, Sis! You don't want to get grey hair, do you?<P><END>
What!!??...<P><END>
Hey! Where are you going!<P><END>
Hello. You're not from around here, are you?<P><END>
Oh, I'm sorry. You must be the new fellow at the farm, right?<P><C>
I've heard rumors about you!<P><END>
My name's Elli. I work at the Clinic.<P><END>
Are you feeling unwell, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><END>
Really? It's always a good idea to have the Doctor look at you if you're <WB>
feeling very tired. <WB>
Take care of yourself.<P><END>
By the way...<P><END>
Do you realize there's someone hiding behind you?<P><END>
Don't get so mad, Sis!<P><END>
Stu is so much trouble! I'm sorry he's a bother!<P><END>
Don't get so mad. All I did was show you a bug!<P><END>
Don't you know I hate bugs?<P><END>
I thought maybe you would like that one!<P><END>
Don't play games with me, Stu!<P><END>
You understand me, don't you, <NAME_MEMO1>? You're a boy, like me.<P><END>
Sure I do.<END>
Not really.<END>
I like you! Let's play together later.<P><END>
You don't need to humor him, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><C>
He'll just start playing his pranks on you, instead.<P><END>
.......... Waaah!!....<P><END>
Don't worry about his crying. He's just not used to being scolded by other <WB>
people, that's all.<P><C>
Maybe now he'll stop playing so many pranks on me!<P><END>
