...So, we thought it was a good idea.<P><END>
Really?<P><END>
That's great!!<P><END>
Mom..Dad...Thanks!<P><END>
The years have passed just like that...<P><END>
I'm just glad you're so happy about it, Karen.<P><END>
Oh, hey, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
Listen to this! My dad asked Doug to make some Wine for me when I was<WB>
born! Isn't that great?!<P><END>
Jeff does have good ideas doesn't he?<P><C>
It's just about mature by now, so we dropped by to tell you about it.<P><END>
<NAME_MEMO1>, why don't you go with Karen to pick it up?<P><END>
I'd be glad to.<END>
Sorry, I'm busy.<END>
We're much obliged!<P><END>
Let's go, then.<P><END>
Here it is.<P><END>
Thanks, Uncle Duke! Look, it even says "Karen" on the label! I can't wait<WB>
to drink it!<P><END>
Now that you're a woman, it was yours!<P><END>
Let's go home now.<P><END>
Wait a second... What about the wine?<P><END>
We're going to bring it home now...<P><END>
It's not just that one bottle, you know!<P><END>
Well, will you bring it all here for me?<P><END>
Hah! You must be joking.<P><C>
Jeff was so happy when you were born that he asked me to make 3 whole cases!<P><C>
It's down below, but I'm not going to get it myself!<P><END>
I can't believe Dad made so much!! Will you help me carry<WB>
it all?<P><END>
Uggh...I'm so tired...!! Thanks a load for helping.<P><C>
I'm grateful to Dad for the thought, <WB>
but he really didn't need to make so much!<P><END>
It does make me glad to have such a kind father.<P><END>
Oh, yeah. Wait here one second.<P><END>
This is a thank-you for helping me out today.<P><END>
Thanks a lot. I mean it.<P><END>
Well, that's too bad.<WB>
We'll have to go pick it up later ourselves, Karen.<P><END>
OK...<P><END>
