I wonder what I should do with this?...No...Hmm....<P><END>
Oh! I'm sorry I didn't see you there.<P><END>
I've never seen you before...Are you a tourist or something?<P><END>
Oh, you're the new fellow up at the farm...!<WB>
<NAME_MEMO1>, right? I'm Mary. Nice to meet you.<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>. Welcome to the Library.<P><END>
Not many people come to the Library, I'm glad you came!<P><END>
Sorry about that before... When I get lost in thought, I don't notice anything.<P><END>
Can I help?<END>
Be careful.<END>
I'm writing a novel, you see. I was just having a case of writer's block,<WB>
that's all.<P><END>
Just let me know if you want to read anything.<P><C>
I bet I have lots of books you'd like!<P><END>
I'll try to be more careful from now on.<P><END>
