Tomorrow is Beach Day, you know.<P><C>
I came to invite you and your Dog.<P><C>
<END>
Oh, your Dog is still a puppy?<P><C>
I'm sorry, but that means he can't compete.<P><C>
If you have the time, come to the Beach tomorrow at 10AM anyway. Bye now.<P><END>
Tomorrow is Beach Day, you know.<P><C>
I cam to invite you and your Dog.<P><C>
<END>
Compete.<END>
Don't compete.<END>
In that case, I'll take him with me now.<P><END>
If you have the time, come to the Beach tomorrow at 10AM anyway to watch. <WB>
Bye now.<P><END>
