To make this, you need Adamantite Ore and 20,000 gold pieces...<P><C>
So you don't have the money?...Too bad!<P><END>
To make this, you need Orichalc Ore and 1,000 gold pieces...<P><C>
So you don't have the money?...Too bad!<P><END>
It will take me five days to make. Are you sure?<P><END>
It will take me one day to make. Are you sure?<P><END>
To make this, you need Adamantite Ore and 20,000 gold pieces...<P><C>
So you don't have the Ore?...You can find it in the mine near the spring.<P><END>
To make this, you need Orichalc Ore and 1,000 gold pieces...<P><C>
So you don't have the Ore?...You can find it in the mine near the spring.<P><END>
Select a Tool to upgrade and an Ore to upgrade it with.<P><END>
Sorry, but you don't have enough gold.<P><END>
You can't hold anything else.<P><END>
Do you need anything else?<P><END>
You're sure you don't need anything?<P><END>
Thanks a lot!<P><END>
Thanks a lot. You can't anything else, though, so I'll have Gray deliver it.<P><END>
Looking for something else as well?<P><END>
Looking for something else as well?<P><END>
Make it<END>
Don't make it<END>
OK, I have to get to work! Quit bothering me!<P><END>
OK, I have to get to work! Quit bothering me!<P><END>
A man doesn't change his mind, you know.<P><END>
Why don't you come back when you have something for me to upgrade for you!<P><END>
You don't have any Ore for me to use! You can find some in the mine by the <WB>
spring, you know.<P><END>
