Thump!!...Phew, it's a lot harder to sneak into houses than I thought!<P><C>
Wait, there's no stocking here!...<P><C>
That means I can't leave my present. Too bad!<P><C>
I guess I'll have to bring it back with me...<P><END>
Thump!!...Phew, it's a lot harder to sneak into houses than I thought!<P><C>
Good, he remembered to put a stocking up.<P><C>
But it's so dark I can't see which present is his!<P><C>
Oh well, I'll just assume it's this one!<P><END>
Thump!!...Phew, it's a lot harder to sneak into houses than I thought!<P><C>
The present is still there! Some people don't even care for the trouble I go <WB>
through to do this!<P><C>
How depressing...I'll just go home, I guess...<P><END>
