Hmm? Who are you? Oh, you're the new lad at the farm, are you?<P><C>
My name's Duke. Pleased to make your acquaintance.<P><END>
A birthday present? For me?<P><C>
Are you aiming to be popular around here?<P><END>
Thanks! I love being able to eat good food on the job!<P><END>
Thanks a lot! I think I'll hide this from Manna and eat it myself!<P><END>
Thanks a lot! I'll remember this.<P><END>
Hmm? What's this? Is it good?<P><END>
What's this?! Are you trying to pick a fight with me?<P><END>
Now this is cute!<P><END>
These guys make life difficult for me all the time!<P><END>
Are you really giving this to me? But it's so nice!...<P><C>
Maybe I'll send it to Aja? Or should I give it to Manna?<P><END>
Are you really giving this to me? It's kind of strange...<P><C>
Maybe I'll send it to Aja. I doubt Manna would like it!<P><END>
Perfume?! What would a man need with Perfume?<P><C>
What?! You say you're giving it to me?!...<P><END>
Heh heh...Good luck!<P><END>
Howdy, <NAME_MEMO1>. If you want to buy wine, go to the house.<P><END>
Want to do me a favor and go talk to Manna? I'd sure appreciate it!<P><END>
I don't go to the Bar to drink my wine, you see, but to talk to the guys.<P><END>
That Cliff at the Inn... He doesn't drink much, but he sure does know a lot<WB>
about wine!<P><END>
It's always nice for the whole family to go out together on our day off!<P><END>
How are you doing at the farm, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><END>
On days like this I want to have a glass of wine in the afternoon.<P><C>
Too bad the bar only serves at night!<P><END>
How's it going, <NAME_MEMO1>? I haven't had any drinks today!<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
What are you doing here at this hour? I only sell wine during the day.<P><END>
Only Manna and I live here alone, so we love it when guests come!<P><END>
If you want to buy some wine, talk to Manna. She's in charge.<P><END>
Manna likes to talk, so buying wine from her can take a long time.<P><C>
She's lonely, though, so forgive her.<P><END>
Are you enjoying your work? Have a glass of wine and enjoy yourself!<P><END>
You know what they say: A glass of wine a day keeps the doctor away!<P><END>
Today we're all going to eat out! We used to eat out all the time before<WB>
Aja left...<P><END>
Today I'm going to Church with Cliff. <P><C>
I've never been before, but sometimes it's nice to sit in a quiet place, ya know?<P><END>
Did you come to eat, too, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><END>
Sometimes I just don't understand Manna!<P><C>
She'd rather gossip with the neighbors than make us supper!<P><END>
You look like you're working pretty hard. Cliff puts in a lot of<WB>
hours, too.<P><END>
Doug always says that Cliff is a real good guy.<P><C>
He doesn't look like it, but he's one cool customer!<P><END>
Hey there, <NAME_MEMO1>! Done with work?<P><END>
I work hard each and every day, you know!<P><C>
A man can't be blamed for drinking a little bit...!<P><END>
My job is a lot easier, now that Cliff is helping.<P><C>
Thanks a lot, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
Cliff is grateful to you, too. If he didn't have this job, he'd have to <WB>
leave town!<P><END>
What are you doing here in the cellar?<P><C>
If you want to buy wine, buy it at the house.<P><END>
The cellar is pleasant, isn't it? Do you hear that? The sound of wine aging?<P><C>
Wine is alive too, you see.<P><END>
You know, <NAME_MEMO1>, I think both you and Carter are real good guys!<P><END>
Cliff has changed a lot around here, including me.<P><C>
I used to just sit around bored on Saturdays!<P><END>
