Hello, there! You must be <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><C>
My name's Harris, and I'm the constable of this town.<P><C>
It's very safe and peaceful here, so you've nothing to worry about!<P><END>
Thank you so much!<P><C>
It is an honor to receive birthday presents from the people I protect.<P><END>
Thank you. You are really too kind!<P><END>
Thank you for your kindness!<P><END>
Thank you very much.<P><END>
Umm...Thank you..I guess...<P><END>
And you looked like such a respectable citizen!<P><END>
I love cute things... What should I name him?<P><END>
Sorry...Even I am scared of that!...<P><END>
Wow, that's very nice! What? You mean it's a gift for me?!<P><C>
You're not trying to bribe me, are you?<P><END>
Thank you so much! What an unexpected treat!<P><END>
Kai and all the other young folks are so adventurous.<P><C>
It makes me think about Aja...<P><END>
I bet you're like I am: too busy to spend lots of time cooking. Well, here's <WB>
a really convenient recipe for Fried Rice.<P><C>
First, put some oil in a Frying Pan, then add Egg and Rice Ball.<P><C>
You can add other ingredients to taste, but be sure to dice them with your Knife first.<P><C>
Seasoning with Sugar, Salt, and Soy Sauce makes it taste even better!<P><END>
Are you going to get<P><C>
married? I want to get married soon, too...<P><END>
I'm almost done for the day! There's nothing better than an uneventful day <WB>
on the beat!<P><END>
You get home now, too, <NAME_MEMO1>. Wild dogs come out at night.<P><END>
It's raining today, but I don't change my patrol for the weather!<P><END>
I hope you're not going mountain climbing on a day like today! It's dangerous!<P><END>
Has anything been troubling you, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><END>
This is such a peaceful town...<P><END>
Is there any trouble?!<P><C>
No, I guess not...Not in a town like this!...<P><END>
Another tough day on the beat!<P><END>
Good morning! Another day to protect Mineral Town!<P><END>
It makes me so happy to see the townspeople at peace...I love my job!<P><END>
Are you taking the day off, too, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><C>
Everybody needs a break now and then!<P><END>
It's OK. Everybody knows I'm here around this time.<P><END>
I rest at Gotz's house when I'm on patrol.<P><END>
And, on Saturdays, Gotz comes to my house.<P><END>
Is there trouble anywhere!? Ha! Of course there isn't!<P><END>
You'd better get home now,ret><NAME_MEMO1>. Wild dogs come out at night.<P><END>
