So you're the new guy at the farm, eh?<P><C>
<NAME_MEMO1>'s not a bad name, I suppose...<P><C>
My name's Rick. I live here with my mom and sister, Popuri.<P><END>
Whoopee! Today's my birthday! Thanks!<P><END>
Th-thanks a lot. You're a really good guy.<P><END>
Hey, thanks! I'll remember it.<P><END>
Hey, thanks!<P><END>
That's nice of you.<P><END>
Hey! What are you doing!?!<P><END>
Cute! Hey there.<P><END>
Animals scares the Chickens, so we try not to let them in the chicken coop.<P><END>
It sure is pretty. I bet mom will like it!<P><END>
I won't use it, but I bet mom will like it!<P><END>
If you carry stuff like that around...you're going to look like Kai!...<P><END>
Marriage, huh? That's great! The farm should become even more<WB>
fun, then!<P><END>
I heard that <MF>+ has lots of animals. Keep up<P><C>
the good work!<P><END>
Hey, how is Karen?<P><END>
Can I come to your place later on? Thanks!<P><END>
Come to the Store later on. All our Chickens lay delicious eggs!<P><END>
Do you know Karen, the girl who works at the Supermarket?<P><C>
She's very nice.<P><END>
Do you have any idea how much work it is feeding all these Chickens everyday?<P><END>
It'll get easier once my dad gets back, though...<P><END>
Karen and I are best friends. We have been ever since we were kids.<P><END>
Things were fun back then, when we could play all day with no chores!<P><END>
Recently, I've begun to realize how important Karen is to me...<P><END>
But, don't tell her I said that! I'd be so embarrassed!<P><END>
Lately, though, Karen seems awful quiet...But she won't tell me why.<P><END>
Karen's the only one who really understands me,<P><C>
you know. All Popuri does is tell me to shut up!<P><END>
Hey, how're you doing?! We're doing great!<P><END>
My mom wanted me to marry Karen so that she'd part of our family.<P><END>
Lately I feel lonely without Karen...<P><END>
Karen is an only child, so I think Jeff is very lonely...<P><C>
Sasha comes over a lot, though.<P><END>
It's getting dark, isn't it?<P><END>
Hey, <NAME_MEMO1>. My mom asked me to do some shopping.<P><END>
I need some break once a while from work. I'm still young, you know?<P><END>
Is Popuri doing a good job? I bet she complains everyday!<P><END>
I can visit my sister any time at your place!<P><C>
If she married Kai, I'd probably never see her again!<P><END>
That guy Kai... I hate him! He always comes to bug my sis in Summer!<P><END>
I can't believe Popuri likes that guy!...<P><C>
She doesn't know how dangerous he is!<P><END>
Popuri comes back in the summertime.<P><C>
That's why I always look forward to Summer!<P><END>
Mom is always glad when Popuri comes back, too.<P><C>
I just wish she could stay for longer...<P><END>
Popuri seems so happy.<P><C>
She sends letters once a week, and visits during the Summer!<P><END>
But, she only writes about Kai, and he comes with her in the summer...<P><C>
She doesn't care about me any more, it seems...<P><END>
I like everyone in the village...except Kai.<P><C>
He comes to the village every summer just to have fun, and causes lots of<P><C>
trouble. Someday...<P><END>
Mom and Popuri don't dislike him the way I do.<P><C>
He has a way with women, I guess.<P><END>
Pretty bad weather today, eh?<P><END>
Some days, the Chickens seem to be so easy to care for! I wonder what puts them in such a good mood?<P><END>
Strange seeing you around at this hour!<P><END>
Shouldn't you be getting back home?<P><C>
After all, you care for that farm all by yourself, so you need the rest!<P><END>
Good weather today, isn't it?<P><END>
The Supermarket's closed on Tuesdays, so I don't get to go there.<P><C>
Why are Tuesdays always sunny?<P><END>
Done with all your work?<P><END>
It's always nice to have a drink after work!<P><END>
We always tell Saibara how our Tools are doing on Tuesdays.<P><END>
You run a farm, too, so you must see Saibara a lot, right?<P><END>
