Who are you? Oh, I know, the new lad at the farm Thomas was <WB>
mentioning...<P><C>
My name is Sasha, and I run the Supermarket.<P><END>
Well, what a considerate gentleman you are!<P><C>
How did you learn my birthday...?<P><END>
Thanks so much! How did you guess my taste?<P><END>
Thanks so much! What a great surprise!<P><END>
Thanks much.<P><END>
Ohh....I really don't like these at all...<P><END>
Sorry, but I get ill just looking at things like that...<P><END>
How cuuute!<P><END>
How dare you try to scare me like that!<P><END>
How wonderful! This is really for me?!...<P><END>
How wonderful!<P><C>
You really know how to win a girl's heart, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><C>
I bet all the girls are chasing you, aren't they?<P><END>
How beautiful! I can't believe this is really for me.<P><END>
You want to learn how to make some fabulous Chocolate Cookies? Jeff<WB>
just loves this recipe.<P><C>
The ingredients are Flour, Butter, Eggs, and Chocolate.<P><C>
You also need Sugar of course and Honey is optional<P><C>
The only implements you need are a Rolling Pin and Oven.<P><C>
You can also get by with just Chocolate and Cookies, too.Karen likes liquor, but<WB>
not sweets, you know.<P><END>
This really brings back memories...Jeff gave me the same thing, once.<P><C>
I still have it, you know.<P><END>
Welcome, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><C>
How is life with Karen?<P><END>
How is <NAME_MEMO6>? He looks so much like his mother...<P><C>
I can't wait to see him again!<P><END>
How are you?<P><END>
If you need my help about anything, don't be afraid to ask.<P><END>
Jeff says his stomach hurts when it rains or snows. Can you believe that?<P><END>
My stomach has never hurt, so I just don't understand it!<P><END>
Welcome! Enjoying farm life?<P><END>
Everyday is fun for me! There's nothing better than enjoying your work!<P><END>
Jeff let someone run up a tab again today!<P><END>
That's OK, though. Lately I even enjoy collecting money people <WB>
owe us!<P><END>
Welcome! If you need anything, just ask!<P><END>
Come again any time!<P><C>
I always enjoy your visits!<P><END>
Hello, <NAME_MEMO1>. Fine weather, isn't it?<P><END>
I've got to get back home to make dinner! My how the day flies!<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>. Imagine meeting you here!<P><END>
I hear things are tough for Barley and May over at Yodel Farm. It's just the two of them.<P><C>
Go over for a visit if you have the time.<P><END>
Well, hello there! I feel so much better when it's sunny like this!<P><END>
Have you gotten Barley to teach you things yet?<P><C>
He's very kind, you know. He taught me a lot.<P><END>
Lillia's health has always been fragile.<P><C>
When the Doctor's father came to town, he told her she couldn't walk for<WB>
much longer.<P><END>
I was her best friend then. It made me want to cry, but she kept her spirits up somehow...<P><END>
When she lost the ability to walk, I was determined to help out as much <WB>
as I could.<P><END>
Lillia's husband is a good man, but he can become obsessed.<P><C>
I wonder where he is now...<P><END>
Lillia's so lonely with him gone...<P><END>
I like to go to Ellen's house around noon.<P><END>
Karen likes to look after others, but not herself!<P><END>
Stu is a good kid, but he sure keeps Ellen's hands full!<P><END>
Still, it's better to have an active and curious child than a passive one.<P><C>
Kids should be inquisitive!<P><END>
Noo...You don't say....?<P><END>
...did he really....? ...then she said what?... ...I can't believe it!...<P><END>
