I've set up shop here, and I've got great stuff!<P><C>
My name is Won.<P><END>
Today is my birthday! This is so unbelievable!<P><C>
This is the best present since I left China!<P><END>
You are a very good person, giving so nice a gift to someone like me.<P><END>
Thank you. I like these. Want to buy something?<P><END>
Thanks. Want to buy something?<P><END>
Sorry, but I'm not so sure about this! What's it for...?<P><END>
Are you trying to make me mad at you? That's not very nice!<P><END>
Do you like animals? I have some great ones to sell! Secret price only for<WB>
you. Rare bugs, too!<P><END>
Sorry, but I couldn't sell this to anyone! Try giving it to someone else, OK?<P><END>
You mean you're giving this to me for FREE?<P><C>
I can sell this for lots...<P><C>
I mean, er...I'll treasure it forever. Thanks!<P><END>
You mean you're giving this to me for FREE?<P><C>
I can sell this for lots to the right woman...<P><C>
I mean, er...I'll treasure it forever. Thanks!<P><END>
I'll buy that off you for a great price!<P><C>
You mean it's a gift? You are truly a saint!<P><END>
Good luck! If it doesn't work out, I promise to buy it back.<P><END>
What's wrong?<P><END>
I've got one of everything!<P><END>
Well, are you going to buy something, or no?<P><END>
I hate cheap people. People with expensive tastes...those are my kind<WB>
of people!<P><END>
Thanks for coming, <NAME_MEMO1>! Take your time!<P><END>
Where are all the customers? Everyone ignores me but you, <NAME_MEMO1>!<P><END>
