Hello, there. Who are you?<P><C>
...Oh, you're the new person at the farm that the Mayor was mentioning.<P><C>
I'm the Doctor of this village. Nice to meet you.<P><END>
Well, this is a nice surprise!<P><C>
It is my birthday, you know. Thanks!<P><END>
Thanks so much! What a pleasant treat!<P><END>
How thoughtful of you!<P><END>
Thank you!<P><END>
Thanks so much! You really don't need to take the trouble, though.<P><END>
Be sure to wash your hands after touching these things!<P><C>
Oh...you mean...it's ...for me...?<P><END>
Is something the matter with it? No...? That's a relief...<P><END>
...! Wh-what is this?! If it's all the same<P><C>
to you...please take it home with you...<P><END>
This is really for me? You are so kind!<P><END>
This is for me? I really shouldn't accept such a nice gift...<P><C>
Oh...thanks!<P><END>
My mother always used to wear this Perfume...<P><C>
My father would bring it back from town...<P><END>
Thanks so much!<P><C>
As thanks, I'll teach you a great recipe for mixed fruit and vegetable juice.<P><C>
I don't have anything to write it down on, but just remember it, OK?<P><C>
The ingredients you need are Strawberry, Pineapple, Grape, Carrot, Cucumber,<P><C>
Cabbage, and Apple. If you forget any of these, the recipe won't work.<P><C>
You need a Mixer, and a Knife if you have one.<P><C>
If you add Sugar and Salt, it'll taste better, too.<P><C>
You can add any other fruit or vegetable you wish.<P><C>
I hope you like it!<P><END>
A Blue Feather... Anyone I know...?<P><END>
Have you heard of Forget-me-not Valley?<P><C>
Rumors are that another doctor I know lives there.<P><C>
He might look a little strange, but his skills are first rate.<P><END>
So, <NAME_MEMO1>, how is married life?<P><END>
Health really is the most important thing, you know. Come around any time if you<WB>
feel under the weather.<P><END>
How are you feeling lately?<P><END>
Come around any time you don't feel well.<P><C>
Of course, it will cost a little bit, but it's worth it!<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>. I hope you're well?<P><END>
I couldn't do anything around here without Elli, you know.<P><END>
If only I could do more to cure people...<P><END>
Lately I've been feeling my powers as a doctor aren't sufficient...<P><END>
Elli worries too much about me...<P><END>
I'm just not a good enough doctor...<P><END>
I think I could do anything if Elli were by my side...<P><END>
If Elli were with me, we could support each other very well.<P><END>
Being a doctor is so demanding!<P><C>
If I have a child, I hope they don't go into medicine...<P><END>
Stu is a good kid, but he gets into so much trouble!<P><END>
Nothing's happened to Elli, has it?!<P><END>
You're just here for a social visit? You really should get back home!<P><END>
What's wrong...?<P><END>
Sorry, but we're going to bed soon. See you tomorrow!<P><END>
Is something the matter? Are you sick?<P><END>
If nothing's the matter, I'd prefer to rest...<P><END>
Sometimes I see Basil near Mother's Hill. He teaches me about herbs.<P><C>
He's a very kind man.<P><END>
Basil's book is very useful to a doctor!<P><END>
Whenever the Clinic is closed, I go to Mother's Hill to search for herbs.<P><C>
Zack picks some for me, but I need more than that.<P><END>
Let me know if you find a good spot for herbs, OK?<P><END>
That Carter is a little strange, but I trust him.<P><END>
Once I talked to Manna about something, and the next day everyone knew <WB>
about it!<P><END>
