Who are you again? Oh, you're at the farm, eh?<P><C>
I'm Gotz, the woodcutter around these parts.<P><C>
If you ever want to expand your house, just call me!<P><END>
No one has given me a birthday gift in...years...<P><C>
Don't mind the tears... Sniff...Thanks!<P><END>
How did you get so nice?<P><C>
I'll remember this!<P><END>
Thanks! I really appreciate gifts like this!...<P><END>
Thanks much. I can use this.<P><END>
What is this for? What do you expect me to do with it?!...<P><END>
What do you take me for, some kind of a fool?!<P><C>
Take this back where you got it!<P><END>
Ha...I see things like this everyday up on the mountain.<P><END>
Are you trying to scare me, or what!? I don't like playing games!<P><END>
If my daughter were still alive, she'd be of an age to wear this...<P><C>
Why don't you give it to Karen at the Supermarket?<P><END>
My wife used to have something like this...<P><C>
Why don't you give it to Karen at the Supermarket?<P><END>
What's happening? I feel kinda dizzy...<P><END>
Do you like Savory Pancakes? All you do is add the ingredients together and <WB>
fry it up!<P><END>
All you need is... What was that again...?<P><C>
Oh yeah! Flour, and...Eggs, and...Cabbage! That's it!<P><C>
<END>
Mix all that up real well, then put it in a Frying Pan with oil. 'Course, you <WB>
gotta cut the Cabbage up with a Knife first.<P><C>
You can put lots of other stuff in, too!<P><END>
If you're gonna get married, you have to look after your family forever!<P><END>
I hear that the equipment they got up there at <MF>+ is all<WB>
first rate. You should go take a look.<P><END>
Long ago, a man named Louis lived at my house.<P><C>
He studies bugs, and says that Mineral Town is full of rare insects.<P><C>
One day, he went out to catch butterflies and never came back!<P><END>
I'm resting now. Don't bother me. Come back later.<P><END>
Don't bug me if you aren't asking about a job.<P><END>
What do you want,<P><C>
<NAME_MEMO1>? Don't mind me, I'm rude to everyone.<P><END>
Living alone in the mountains, sometimes you see some strange things...<P><C>
I could never explain, though.<P><END>
Be careful when climbing the mountain yourself.<P><END>
There are no bears or wolves, but you can't be too cautious. Know what I mean?<P><END>
It seems you're keeping busy. Keep at it!<P><END>
I'm looking for good Lumber trees. Then I'll see about finding something to eat.<P><END>
Let me give some advice about tree chopping.<P><C>
Don't chop down more than you need.<P><C>
We humans have to respect nature, you know.<P><END>
I'm going to see the Mayor. Gotta keep good relations, you know!<P><END>
Keep up the good work!<P><END>
I like to come to town on Saturday. Buy eggs and milk, stuff like that.<P><END>
If I stayed up in the mountain too long, people'd forget about me, and I'd<WB>
be outa work!...<P><END>
Keeping up the good work, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><END>
You just keep on expanding the farm!<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>. You like it here, too?<P><END>
Ever since I lost my family here...<P><C>
I keep telling Basil not to bring his family hiking in bad weather!<P><END>
You be careful too, now!<P><END>
Oh, it's you, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
If you don't get off the mountain soon, you'll be caught out in the dark.<P><END>
Hey there! How's the work coming?<P><END>
Just you wait and see!<P><END>
