I don't think I've seen you around here before.<P><C>
Oh, you're at the farm, are you? Welcome to the boonies.<P><C>
The name's Gray.<P><END>
Wow! What a surprise!<P><C>
What's a classy guy like you doing in a place like this?<P><END>
Thanks! I like having classy friends like you.<P><END>
Thanks a lot! Anytime you want to give me something, I'm ready to<WB>
receive!<P><END>
Thanks.<P><END>
I'll take this off your hands, but you don't need to give it to me again, OK?<P><END>
What a jerk! Don't give that to me!<P><END>
You're kind of funny, if you think that's a big deal.<P><END>
G-get that away from me...Now!<P><END>
Did gramps make this?<P><C>
Thanks. It's not like I get to see his work or anything...<P><END>
That's very nice! I think I'll send it to my mom.<P><END>
This is a good present for a girl, isn't it?<P><END>
You don't know me if you think I'll like that! Well, maybe...<P><END>
Something you want to tell me?<P><END>
Tell about job.<END>
Don't tell about job.<END>
Ha! If I got a job somewhere else, gramps would tan my hide!<P><END>
How is Mary doing?<P><END>
Tell her hi for me.<P><END>
I hate it around here. There's nothing to do. Don't you think so too?<P><END>
I just get so bored in this town. I want to go back to the city!<P><END>
Hey, <NAME_MEMO1>, what do you think of the girl who works in the Library?<P><END>
I go to the Library a lot these days. I like reading books all the sudden.<P><END>
I had no idea books were so much fun!<P><END>
Did you know Mary writes novels! That's amazing.<P><C>
I hope one day I can craft something, too.<P><END>
Working hard, I see.<P><END>
Lately I've been getting along better with gramps.<P><C>
I'm enjoying working as a blacksmith more and more.<P><END>
Mary's different from the other girls.<P><C>
I want her to like me!<P><END>
All I can do is try my best to learn the blacksmith trade, and read lots of <WB>
books.<P><C>
Hopefully, she'll notice!<P><END>
I hear neat stories from Mary's father alll the time.<P><END>
I like books, too, but I'm never to give up on being a blacksmith.<P><END>
My grampa is so hard on me for every little thing! I can hardly stand it!<P><END>
I wonder how old my grandfather is...<P><C>
How can he still be so strong!?...<P><END>
Hi there. Do you need something?<P><END>
Shouldn't you be getting back to the farm around now?<P><END>
Mary's parents are both so nice to me.<P><END>
My grandfather doens't seem to have much energy, lately. He doesn't even yell at me!<P><END>
I'm going to get that old man to praise me, no matter what!<P><END>
No matter how hard I try, my grandfather never praises anything I make or do!<P><END>
I hear interesting stories from Mary's father all the time.<P><END>
Books have some really interesting stories, you know.<P><END>
Mary always suggests such great books for me to read.<P><END>
Gramps always makes me go hiking on vacation days. He says it's practice for <WB>
concentrating.<P><END>
...Concentrate.... ...Concentrate...<P><END>
