Err...Hello, budum... You're <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><C>
My name's Hoggy. It's a pleasure, budum.<P><END>
Our Tea Party is in the Spring, budum.<P><END>
Did you bring an invitation? Everyone! Get the Tea Set ready!...<P><END>
Sorry, but not everyone is here, budum, so we can't have the Tea Party now.<P><END>
Now isn't the time for a Tea Party, budum. Come at the right time!<P><END>
We can't have a Tea Party here, budum!<P><END>
Today's my birthday, budum! Thank you!<P><END>
Yipee!! This is wonderful, budum! Thank you!<P><END>
Thanks! This is great, budum!<P><END>
Thanks, budum...<P><END>
This isn't so great, budum...<P><END>
.......!! This is the worst present ever, budum...<P><END>
Awww...It's so cute, budum!<P><END>
Wh-why...does it look like it wants to eat me, budum...?<P><END>
Thanks much! Is this really for me, budum?<P><END>
Thank you! I'm happy!<END>
This is a great feather, but it won't fill me up, budum.<P><END>
I heard a rumor that there are friends of ours in Forget-me-not Valley, budum?<P><END>
Spring is the season for Tea Parties. Everyone loves Tea Parties, budum.<P><END>
Spring is the season for Tea Parties. We send invitations to our friends.<P><END>
Spring is the season for Tea Parties. Do you  like tea?<P><END>
Spring is the season for Tea Parties. If you come, we'll have them every day, budum!<P><END>
I like Tea Parties because of the delicious treats, budum.<P><END>
Chef makes the treats for our Tea Parties, budum.<P><END>
We only invite our true friends to Tea Parties, budum!<P><END>
I wish everyday is the Spring so that we can have a tea party everyday.<P><END>
I'm getting hungry, budum...<P><END>
Did you bring anything for me to eat, budum?<P><END>
Ah, <NAME_MEMO1>. What will you give me today, budum?<P><END>
Whenever I get hungry, you seem to come along, budum.<P><END>
I just love to eat!...<P><END>
If I don't eat, I don't have any energy, budum...<P><END>
You know what I like to eat, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
If it were for you, <NAME_MEMO1>, I'd be willing to work even if I got hungry!<P><END>
Did you need something?<P><END>
Can you help me?<END>
Let's play.<END>
Nothing in particular.<END>
I'll get started tomorrow, budum.<P><END>
I'll help you if we become better friends, budum.<P><END>
What should I do?<P><END>
Watering<END>
Harvest<END>
Animals<END>
Exit<END>
How long do you want me to water for, budum?<P><END>
1 day<END>
3 days<END>
1 week<END>
Got it. I'll water for 1 day, budum.<P><END>
Got it. I'll water for 3 days, budum.<P><END>
Got it. I'll water for 1 week, budum.<P><END>
How many days do you want me to harvest for, budum?<P><END>
Got it. I'll harvest for 1 day, budum.<P><END>
Got it. I'll harvest for 3 days, budum.<P><END>
Got it. I'll harvest for 1 week, budum.<P><END>
How long do you want me to look after the animals for, budum?<P><END>
Got it. I'll look after the animals for 1 day, budum.<P><END>
Got it. I'll look after the animals for 3 days, budum.<P><END>
Got it. I'll look after the animals for 1 week, budum.<P><END>
Really, budum? Is that so...?<P><END>
We already played today! Let's play tomorrow, budum.<P><END>
I'll play if we become better friends, budum.<P><END>
How should we play?<P><END>
Let's play the watering game, budum!<P><END>
I think I've gotten better than before, budum!<P><END>
I hope I don't make too many mistakes...<P><END>
Let's play the harvest game, budum!<P><END>
Let's play the animal husbandry game, budum!<P><END>
What? You don't want to play, budum? That's too bad...<P><END>
No?<P><END>
We're already done working for the day!<P><END>
I haven't gotten very good at it yet, budum...<P><END>
I think I'm getting the hang of it, budum...!<P><END>
Harvesting is fun, budum! Let's do more!<P><END>
Now I'm a master harvester! Just leave it to me, budum!<P><END>
Watering is fun, budum! Let's do more!<P><END>
Now I'm a master waterer! Just leave it to me, budum!<P><END>
Taking care of animals is fun, budum! Let's do more!<P><END>
Now I'm great at taking care of the animals! Just leave it to me, budum!<P><END>
Let's do more tomorrow!<END>
Your job is done for now.<END>
I'll do my best, budum.<P><END>
OK. Tomorrow I'll rest, budum.<P><END>
