Ah, are you the new guy at that farm Thomas told me about?<P><C>
My name's Mary. Nice to meet you.<P><END>
Gee, thanks!<P><C>
A birthday present, for me? You're a really sweet guy, <NAME_MEMO2>!<P><END>
A birthday present? What a surprise!<P><END>
Gee, thanks!<P><C>
What a great present! You're a really sweet guy, <NAME_MEMO2>!<P><END>
A birthday gift? Gosh, thanks.<P><END>
What a great present! Thanks so much!<P><C>
All my father ever gives me is books...!<P><END>
Thanks! I'm so grateful!<P><END>
You mean something so nice is really for me?<P><END>
Thanks, <NAME_MEMO2>! This will come in very useful!<P><END>
Gee, thanks  a lot! What a great gift!<P><END>
Thanks a lot.<P><END>
Thanks! I love these!<P><END>
Thank you.<P><END>
Th-thanks...<P><END>
I'm allergic to these, but but I'll give them to someone else, OK?<P><END>
I wish I could say that I liked these...<P><END>
...I don't think I could bring that home!...<P><END>
Umm...What exactly is this?<P><END>
Oh, so cuute! ...Not you, <NAME_MEMO2>...!<P><END>
It's so cute! I love all the animals in this village, don't you?<P><END>
Wh-what is it...?<P><END>
...! ........................... ...........................<P><END>
Gee, thanks!<P><C>
You found this stone yourself, didn't you? That makes it even more special!<P><END>
This is really for me? Seriously?<P><C>
Gray's grandfather made this, didn't he?<P><C>
I wonder if Gray ever will?<P><END>
Thanks so much!...<P><C>
Where did you get this stone? I've never seen one like it!<P><END>
Thanks! But... Wasn't it expensive...?<P><C>
I'm glad I married you, <NAME_MEMO2>!<P><C>
You're a sweety!<P><END>
This is really for me? You mean it? Wow, thanks!<P><END>
This is for me? I've always wanted one like this...Thanks!<P><END>
It's every girl's dream to grow up, get married, and receive Perfume as a gift!<P><END>
This is so romantic! Maybe I'll try writing a romance novel tonight...<P><END>
Yippee! I've never had such nice Perfume before!<P><END>
Why...? Oh, never mind... Thanks, I guess...<P><END>
Thanks. You made these for the Spring Thanksgiving Festival, right?<P><END>
Thanks!<P><C>
But I can't believe I didn't give you anything for the Winter Thanksgiving<WB>
Festival...I'm sorry!<P><END>
Thanks! Giving and receiving gifts are my favorite part of<WB>
the Festivals!<P><END>
Huh? I can't believe... Why don't we talk at your house...?<P><END>
Congratulations! You should really keep that fresh for the important<WB>
girl, though!<P><END>
So this is a Blue Feather, huh?<P><C>
Aren't they used for proposing?<P><END>
If you don't already have other plans...How about coming over to my house<P><C>
tomorrow for the Starry Night Festival...?<P><END>
Sounds like fun!<END>
Sorry, I've got plans.<END>
Great! We'll be waiting for you!<P><END>
Really...? Well...Never mind...<P><END>
Let's spend tomorrow's Starry Night Festival together, OK?<P><END>
I think you'll make father, <NAME_MEMO2>!<P><END>
You look cute with your jaw open, you know!<P><END>
I have another life growing inside me... Isn't that miraculous?<P><END>
Now I have two hearts beating inside me, not just one!<P><C>
I wish I could hear them both...<P><END>
My tummy is getting bigger all the time, isn't it?<P><C>
For some reason it feels like a boy...<P><END>
Mother told me she was this big when she had me!<P><END>
I think the big day might be tomorrow!<P><END>
I think he just wants to meet his dad as fast as he can!<P><C>
So, you be there during the birth, OK?<P><END>
I have an intuition it's going to be a boy.<P><END>
Good boy, <NAME_MEMO6>.<P><C>
I think the name fits him perfectly, don't you?<P><END>
He seems like he's getting big so fast!<P><END>
I just love him so much...<P><C>
He's so adorable!...<P><END>
Raising a child is harder than I thought!<P><END>
It's true what they say, that children look like angels when they're asleep.<P><END>
Can you believe he's already walking?<P><END>
He's cute even when he stumbles!<P><END>
You can tell he's trying to talk! I can't understand what he's saying, though...<P><END>
I just know that he's going to love playing outside with you! He looks<WB>
like a born farmer!<P><END>
...Aren't you a little cold to me, lately?<P><END>
I know you have to work, but it would be nice if you spent a little more<WB>
time with me, too...<P><END>
Mornin'!<P><END>
I'm not mad at you. Really, I'm not!<P><END>
I've got to fix a meal, so I'll talk to you later, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
Don't bother me when I'm trying to do something for you, <NAME_MEMO2>!<P><END>
Work hard, now!<P><END>
I think I was better at working at the Library...<P><END>
I don't know what you think about it, but I really value my job...<P><END>
Good morning. Did you sleep well?<P><END>
Keep up the hard work!<P><END>
Ever since marrying you, I've thought of completely different ideas for novels!<P><END>
I won't tell you right now, but maybe I'll show you when it's done!<P><END>
Good morning, <NAME_MEMO2>! Sometimes I'm just so glad I married you!<P><END>
No one understands me like you do, <NAME_MEMO2>.<P><END>
What?! You're already hungry?<P><END>
You sure do work up an appetite!<P><END>
Oh, <NAME_MEMO2>. Nice to see you here.<P><END>
Don't worry. I'm not lifting anything heavy.<P><END>
Oh, <NAME_MEMO2>. Nice to see you.<P><END>
I'm glad I'll be able to work even with a baby...<P><END>
What?<P><END>
I'm a little busy right now...<P><END>
What? Quiet in the Library!<P><END>
Don't you have any work to do? If you're so bored, go read a book.<P><END>
Thanks for coming. Work is fun, you know, when you like what you do!<P><END>
Thanks for not minding me working...<P><END>
Oh, <NAME_MEMO2>. Did you come to check out a book?<P><END>
Did you come to check on me?<P><C>
I'm not a child, you know! ...Thanks, though.<P><END>
Welcome, <NAME_MEMO2>.<P><C>
Not many people love books as much as you, you know.<P><END>
But then again, your MY hubby!<P><END>
Oh, hello.<P><END>
Gray and I agree on most everything. Maybe he reads the same books I do...<P><END>
Hello, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
Gray and I have hardly changed since our marriage.<P><C>
He works under Saibara and I at the Library.<P><END>
Oh, hello, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
I'm so glad Gray and my dad are getting along!<P><C>
Gray's grandfather is very nice, too.<P><END>
Oh, hello, <NAME_MEMO1>. Come to read a book?<P><END>
Gray always vows to quit his apprenticeship whenever he comes home.<P><C>
The next day, he always goes back, though.<P><END>
Oh, hello, <NAME_MEMO1>. How is farm life going?<P><END>
The other day I went to meet Gray's parents.<P><C>
I was surprised at how close they lived to my old house.<P><END>
I'm glad Gray decided he likes books, but I also wish he'd pick up other<WB>
interests as well!<P><END>
Hi <NAME_MEMO1>! Bet you came to read a book, huh?<P><END>
I like you because you like to read, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><C>
I like it when more people read my books!<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>. How are you today?<P><END>
You look well.<P><END>
Is life on the farm busy these days, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><END>
Is married life easier than life as a bachelor?<P><C>
Now you can concentrate on farm work, right?<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>. How's your wife?<P><END>
Tell your wife I want to come over to chat!<P><END>
Hee hee hee...<P><END>
I can't wait to be married! Ever since I was a little girl, I dreamed of <WB>
myself in a wedding dress...<P><END>
Hi.<P><C>
We built this Library so the townspeople could have access to my dad's books.<P><END>
We get new books in all the time, so you should come back often!<P><END>
Hello!<P><END>
Doesn't this town remind you of a village in a fairy tale...?<P><END>
Hi.  How is life on the farm?<P><END>
Will you teach me about farm stuff?<P><C>
I love to learn new things, you know!<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>! I love it when people come to read our books!<P><END>
I love the smell of books. I think they smell like the inside of a forest...<WB>
or a fairy tale!<P><END>
Oh...Hello.<P><END>
It's too bad that not everybody visits our Library so often.<P><END>
So you came! Thank you!<P><END>
I can't imagine quitting my job here just because I get married.<P><C>
I want more people to come here and read books!<P><END>
Hell-ooh....<P><END>
For some reason I just got queasy all of a sudden!<P><END>
The Library is closed on Thursdays now. Don't forget!<P><END>
I like to go to the peak of Mother's Hill on sunny days around noon.<P><C>
Saibara is there sometimes, too, but for some reason Gray never comes!<P><END>
On Thursdays when the weather isn't nice, Gray and I usually visit his<WB>
grandfather.<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>. Did you come to see Gray?<P><END>
You're always so good to Gray!<P><END>
Sorry, <NAME_MEMO1>, but the Library is closed today.<P><END>
On Mondays the whole family helps out dad on Mother's Hill.<P><END>
Today it's raining, so we can't go hiking. But, the Library is still closed.<P><END>
After all, nobody would come today anyway!<P><END>
Was there a specific book you wanted to read, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><END>
The library is usually open from 10 AM to 4 PM.<P><C>
Why don't you come then?<P><END>
Good morning! What a beautiful day!<P><END>
Is the farm fun for you?<P><END>
Hi there.<P><END>
Be careful not to catch cold now, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
Sorry, but the Library is closed today.<P><C>
Our day off changed to Thursday.<P><END>
Sorry, but the Library is closed today.<P><END>
We all go to help Dad on Mother's Hill once a week.<P><END>
Hi. Today is our day off here at the Library.<P><END>
What a coincidence! Today I'm helping Mom.<P><END>
Mom always buys way too much at the Supermarket!<P><END>
I didn't expect to find you here, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><C>
Are you looking for plants, too?<P><END>
Papa drags us to the mountain even in Winter!<P><C>
He does let us stay home if it's snowing, though.<P><END>
Hi there. Going to the mountain is more fun with Gray than<WB>
with Dad.<P><END>
Of course, Dad never looks up from the ground on Mother's Hill.<P><END>
Working as a Blacksmith is really dangerous, you know.<P><END>
I like Gray's grandfather.<P><C>
He's so hard and disciplined compared with my own family!<P><END>
