Nice to meet you! Your name is <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><C>
Mine is Nappy. How do you do, budum.<P><END>
Our Tea Party is in the Spring, budum.<P><END>
Did you bring an invitation? Everyone! Get the Tea Set ready!...<P><END>
Sorry, but not everyone is here, budum, so we can't have the Tea Party now.<P><END>
Now isn't the time for a Tea Party, budum. Come at the right time!<P><END>
We can't have a Tea Party here, budum!<P><END>
Today's my birthday, budum! Thank you!<P><END>
Yipee!! This is wonderful, budum! Thank you!<P><END>
Thanks! This is great, budum!<P><END>
Thanks, budum...<P><END>
This isn't so great, budum...<P><END>
......!!<P><END>
It's cute, but please don't let animals in the house, budum.<P><END>
Ack! Does it bite, budum?<P><END>
This is great! How do you play with it? Is it a toy, budum?<P><END>
Thanks much! Is this really for me, budum?<P><END>
I'll treasure it always, budum!<P><END>
This is the first time I've seen a Blue Feather, budum. What kind of animal <WB>
does it come from?<P><END>
I heard a rumor that there are friends of ours in Forget-me-not Valley, budum?<P><END>
Spring is the season for Tea Parties.  I can't wait!<P><END>
Spring is the season for Tea Parties. All of our friends come.<P><END>
Spring is the season for Tea Parties, budum. Do you like Tea Parties?<P><END>
Spring is the season for Tea Parties, budum. If we had Tea Parties<WB>
everyday, would you come?<P><END>
When it becomes Spring, Tea Parties become all I can think about, budum!<P><END>
We send our tea paty invitations to our friends.<P><END>
I'm in charge of decorations for the Tea Party, budum.<P><END>
If it were Spring all year... We could have Tea Parties all the time, budum!<P><END>
Oh, welcome, budum.<P><END>
Welcome. I'm kinda bored, budum...<P><END>
Welcome, budum! Want to play?<P><END>
Whooppee! It's <NAME_MEMO1>! I was hoping you'd come!<P><END>
I don't like people who are no fun, budum...<P><END>
I'd take playing over working any day, budum!<P><END>
What should we play today? I'm so excited!<P><END>
You're my favorite play partner, budum!<P><END>
Did you need something?<P><END>
Can you help me?<END>
Let's play.<END>
Nothing in particular.<END>
I'll get started tomorrow, budum.<P><END>
I'll help you if we become better friends, budum.<P><END>
What should I do?<P><END>
Watering<END>
Harvest<END>
Animals<END>
Exit<END>
How long do you want me to water for, budum?<P><END>
1 day<END>
3 days<END>
1 week<END>
Got it. I'll water for 1 day, budum.<P><END>
Got it. I'll water for 3 days, budum.<P><END>
Got it. I'll water for 1 week, budum.<P><END>
How many days do you want me to harvest for, budum?<P><END>
Got it. I'll harvest for 1 day, budum.<P><END>
Got it. I'll harvest for 3 days, budum.<P><END>
Got it. I'll harvest for 1 week, budum.<P><END>
How long do you want me to look after the animals for, budum?<P><END>
Got it. I'll look after the animals for 1 day, budum.<P><END>
Got it. I'll look after the animals for 3 days, budum.<P><END>
Got it. I'll look after the animals for 1 week, budum.<P><END>
Really, budum? Is that so...?<P><END>
We already played today! Let's play tomorrow, budum.<P><END>
I'll play if we become better friends, budum.<P><END>
How should we play?<P><END>
Let's play the watering game, budum!<P><END>
I think I've gotten better than before, budum!<P><END>
I hope I don't make too many mistakes...<P><END>
Let's play the harvest game.<P><END>
Let's play the animal husbandry game, budum!<P><END>
What? You don't want to play, budum? That's too bad...<P><END>
Really? That's too bad, budum...<P><END>
We're already done working for the day!<P><END>
I haven't gotten very good at it yet, budum...<P><END>
I think I'm getting the hang of it, budum...!<P><END>
Harvesting is fun, budum! Let's do more!<P><END>
Now I'm a master harvester! Just leave it to me, budum!<P><END>
Watering is fun, budum! Let's do more!<P><END>
Now I'm a master waterer! Just leave it to me, budum!<P><END>
Taking care of animals is fun, budum! Let's do more!<P><END>
Now I'm great at taking care of the animals! Just leave it to me, budum!<P><END>
Let's do more tomorrow!<END>
Your job is done for now.<END>
I'll do my best, budum.<P><END>
OK. Tomorrow I'll rest, budum.<P><END>
