Hello, my name is Popuri. What's your's?<P><C>
Nice to meet you!<P><END>
Really? A birthday present? For me? Thank you so much!<P><END>
Thank you so much! What a great birthday!<P><END>
Really? This is a birthday present for me?<P><C>
I'm so surprised! I'll treasure it forever!<P><END>
I'm so happy! What a great birthday! I'm so lucky ot have been<WB>
born in Summer!<P><END>
Really? A birthday present for me?<P><C>
If I told my mom about this, she's be so surprised!<P><END>
Thanks, <NAME_MEMO2>! I'm so glad I married you!<P><END>
I just love it! Thank you so much!<P><END>
Thanks, <NAME_MEMO2>. You're the greatest!<P><END>
Thanks! I love it!<P><END>
Thank you, <NAME_MEMO2>. I'm so happy...<P><END>
Thank you so much!<P><END>
Thank you so much! I'm so glad!<P><END>
Thank you!<P><END>
What's this? I don't like this at all! Here's your dinner.<P><END>
I don't like this!<P><END>
Hmmph! How could you be so stupid!?...<P><C>
Throw this away yourself!<P><END>
Who would want this!?...<P><END>
Cute!<P><C>
I grew up on a farm with Chickens, so I love <WB>
animals...<P><END>
So cuuuute!!<P><END>
I...I can't believe you would try to give me this! I don't even want to <WB>
look at it...!<P><END>
No, I'm scared!<P><END>
This is for me!? Thank you so much! I love it!<P><C>
You're the best, <NAME_MEMO2>!<P><END>
You're giving this to me?...How sweet!<P><C>
Don't worry, Kai won't get upset about it!<P><END>
This is for me?!... Awesome!...I feel so... ...like a woman!<P><END>
You're giving this to me? I love it! Thank you so much!<P><C>
You're great, <NAME_MEMO2>.<P><END>
This is for me?! Thanks! I can't wait to show it to Mom!<P><END>
This is for me?! Thanks! It smells so good!<P><END>
You know what? Kai already gave me the same kind of Perfume...<P><C>
Give this to someone you really like instead.<P><END>
You're giving this Perfume to me? Really?...<P><C>
Thank you so much!<P><END>
Thak you! Are you giving presents to everybody, or just me?...<P><END>
Thanks!<P><C>
I can't wait to eat them! I knew today was going to be great!<P><END>
Wow...Thank you so much! Are you sure it's OK?<P><C>
And I didn't even give you anything at the Winter Thanksgiving Festival!<P><END>
This is for me? Thanks! But...You really shouldn't have gone to<WB>
the trouble...<P><END>
Wait one second! Let's talk at your place!<P><END>
You're sweet, but you should really give this to someone you want to marry.<P><END>
I just don't feel that way about you. I like you as a friend, though!<P><END>
Tomorrow is the Starry Night Festival, right? Why don't you come<WB>
over to my house...?<P><END>
Sounds like fun.<END>
Sorry, I have other plans.<END>
Great! I'll make you the best dinner ever!<P><END>
I guess you're too busy...Oh well...<P><END>
Tomorrow is the Starry Night Festival, so let's have a party at my house!<P><C>
I just learned a great new Cake recipe from Anna!<P><END>
I thought I felt strange...I'm just glad I'm not sick!<P><END>
I'm just a little hungrier than usual, that's all!<P><END>
Good morning! I roll around a lot in my sleep, so I was so worried<P><C>
about the baby I didn't sleep at all...!<P><END>
Or...Is there such a thing as being too happy to sleep?  I thought so...<P><END>
The Doctor at the Clinic said everything was going well! I can't wait until<WB>
it's born!...<P><END>
Honestly, I'm a little scared, though...<P><C>
Mom told me labor was so painful!<P><END>
............................ ............................<P><END>
<NAME_MEMO2>!!! Elli at the Clinic said the baby would be born<WB>
tomorrow! I'm so excited!!<P><END>
Ahhh....He's so cuuute!<P><END>
<NAME_MEMO6> is so adorable...<P><END>
He's so cuuute! I think he'll be so handsome when he grows up!<P><END>
When you were a baby, I bet you looked just <NAME_MEMO6> now!<P><C>
I think he takes after you!<P><END>
Now he's making baby noises! I love him so much...!<P><END>
I'd do anything for <NAME_MEMO6>....Don't you agree, <NAME_MEMO2>?<P><END>
<NAME_MEMO6> can already walk! He's so advanced for his age, don't you think?<P><END>
When he gets older, he'll take over the farm.<P><C>
Won't that be wonderful?<P><END>
He talks a little bit, now! Whom do you like more, Papa or Mama?<P><END>
Who do you like more, me or <NAME_MEMO6>?<P><END>
............................<P><END>
I'm sick of this! I just want to go home!<P><END>
Good morning, <NAME_MEMO2>.<P><END>
I get bored if you don't talk to me, you know!<P><END>
Can I go back home... Just for a little bit?...<P><END>
You don't spend very much time at home lately, <NAME_MEMO2>.<P><END>
Good morning! Everyone on the Poultry Farm wakes up early, so<WB>
I'm used to it!<P><END>
Put in a good day's work, now!<P><END>
I got lots of Eggs from Mom, so I hope you like them!<P><END>
I make great fried eggs!<P><END>
Good morning, <NAME_MEMO2>!<P><END>
Should we walk <NAME_MEMO4>?<P><C>
Well, I guess the farm is so big we don't have to!<P><END>
I like living on farms because the food is so fresh!<P><END>
The only fresh things we have on the Poultry Farm are Eggs and Corn!<P><END>
Good morning!<P><C>
Did you dream of me, <NAME_MEMO2>?<P><END>
Work hard, but not too hard, OK!?<P><END>
I love watching you enjoy the food I make you, <NAME_MEMO2>.<P><C>
You just gobble it up!<P><END>
My brother is so picky about his food!<P><C>
Poor Karen!<P><END>
Welcome, <NAME_MEMO2>.<P><C>
My mom says my face looks softer these days.<P><C>
I guess it's true what they say about that happening when you get pregnant!<P><END>
You don't have to worry about me working too hard!<P><C>
I do have some sense, you know!<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO2>! How is <NAME_MEMO6>?<P><C>
Is he lonely without me?<P><END>
Take good care of <NAME_MEMO6> now!<P><END>
.........................<P><END>
What did you come here for, anyway!<P><END>
I'm trying to get some work done, so quit bothering me!<P><END>
I keep telling you to stop distracting me!<P><C>
You're impossible sometimes, <NAME_MEMO2>.<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO2>. What's up?<P><END>
I'm trying to get some work done! You get to work, too!<P><END>
Welcome, <NAME_MEMO2>! Hee-hee...<P><END>
I don't know why, but I get embarrassed when you show up at the store!<P><END>
Welcome, <NAME_MEMO2>! See how hard I'm working?!...<P><END>
I'm working very hard for you, <NAME_MEMO2>!<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>. The Poultry Farm is closed today. Sorry.<P><END>
Me? No, my mom never even lets me touch the store money!<P><END>
Rain...? It doesn't rain this much where I live...<P><END>
Nothing to do but relax, I suppose.<P><C>
Kai must be off today, too...<P><END>
Ah, <NAME_MEMO1>. How are you today?<P><END>
I only get to come in the Summer, so I miss the people here!<P><END>
You look like you're busy as ever, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
It's like it's always Summer where I live with Kai. Do I look tan to you?<P><END>
Howdy, <NAME_MEMO1>! How are you faring?<P><END>
Sometimes I want to come back here in the Spring or the Fall...<WB>
Even Winter!<P><C>
If I leave Kai alone, though, pretty soon the other girls will be all<WB>
over him!<P><END>
How is your farm, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><END>
I wish I were still surrounded by animals like you are, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>. I hear you're doing a good job on your farm.<P><END>
I used to always want to leave this town... But now I appreciate it<WB>
more.<P><END>
You seem more grown up every year, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><C>
I guess that's natural, though...<P><END>
I try to make Kai stay with us at the house, but he insists on staying<WB>
at the inn!<P><C>
I wonder why...?<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>. I wish I could come here for more than just <WB>
Summers, sometimes!<P><END>
I always hope my dad will be back this time when I come back, but he <WB>
never is...<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>. How are you doing?<P><END>
Say hello to your wife for me.<P><END>
Still toiling away at the farm, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><END>
What are you doing here? You are married now.<P><C>
Why don't you go back home to your cute wife?<P><END>
How is farm life treating you, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><END>
You treat your wife so well! I'm jealous...<P><END>
Hee-hee... We're getting married...!<P><END>
I just wish Dad would come back...<P><C>
How can he miss his own daughter's wedding!<P><END>
You've never met my father, have you, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><C>
I wonder what he would think of you...?<P><END>
...Hello!<P><END>
Did you need something?<P><END>
Are you having fun on your farm? I'm so bored...<P><END>
Don't tell anyone, though!<P><END>
You're much nicer than my brother, you know that?<P><END>
My brother is so attached to me! Can you believe it?<P><END>
What is it like where you live, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><END>
I want to visit lots of different places!<P><END>
I'm so impressed you're managing your farm all by yourself!<P><END>
My brother likes you, and so do I!<P><END>
What do you think of me...?<P><END>
Everyone thinks I'm still a kid...<P><C>
Do you think so, too?<P><END>
You had better treat me like an adult, <NAME_MEMO1>!<P><END>
I used to like only handsome men, but now I think I like quite men, <WB>
like you...<P><END>
I always relax more in my own room...<P><END>
I'm getting sleepy...<P><END>
What do you think Churches are for?<P><C>
Whenever I ask Carter, he won't give me a straight answer!<P><END>
This church was built when I was just a kid.<P><C>
My brother used to take me here all the time.<P><END>
My Mom minds the store, and my brother looks after the Chickens.<P><END>
My father trusts my brother so much!<P><C>
He wouldn't teach ME anything, though.<P><END>
I love the ocean. Mineral Beach is the best place of all!<P><END>
Kai's father owns restaurants in lots of towns.<P><C>
I had no idea!<P><END>
I love Summer! The beach during Summer is my favorite!<P><END>
Have you ever eaten at the Beach House?<P><C>
They have things there you can't find in town.<P><END>
