I've never seen your face around these parts before.<P><C>
You're new at the farm, you say? That's tough for one man, but you can do it<WB>
if you try.<P><C>
I'm Saibara, the blacksmith.<P><END>
Heh heh, what's this?<P><END>
A man doesn't expect to get birthday gifts at my age!<P><C>
My thanks, though!<P><END>
You're kind to an old man, to give me such a gift.<P><C>
I only wish Gray would learn from you.<P><END>
Thanks very much. You're a generous man.<P><END>
Much obliged.<P><END>
Sorry, but I've never needed anything like this.<P><END>
Just what are you thinking!? Young people these days have the worst manners!<P><END>
This little guy is small, but his will to live is great. We could all learn<WB>
from it!<P><END>
Sorry, but I'm busy right now. Go show that to somebody else.<P><END>
What's this? Was there something wrong with the workmanship?<P><C>
I've never had anybody try to give something back...<P><END>
Now just what do you expect me to do with this?<P><END>
Perfume? I don't see this much in my line of work!<P><C>
Why give this to me?<P><END>
You should eat simple foods, you know. You'll live longer, like me.<P><C>
If you agree, I'll tell you a great recipe for Pickled Turnip. It's delicious!<P><C>
All you need is Turnip, Vinegar, and a Knife.<P><C>
A youngin' like you might want to flavor it with Sugar, Salt, and Soy Sauce.<P><END>
A Blue Feather, eh? I hope that's not for me!!...<P><END>
My father used to tell me rising with dawn was the key to a long life.<P><END>
The most important work on a farm is done early in the morning. Sleep in and you <WB>
fail, son.<P><END>
D'ya need something?<P><END>
Don't loiter around here now, young man!<P><END>
A farm requires steady work now, don't forget!<P><END>
All life is study, you understand.<P><END>
Good morning! We've been blessed with a fine day!<P><END>
Sorry, but I'm going out shopping now.<P><END>
I'm about to go out now, but why don't you come with me?<P><C>
Those who work hard get to play hard!<P><END>
Well, I should be getting back now.<P><END>
I can see you're doing well. Farm life suits you, but don't get carried away.<P><END>
You like crafted things, don't you? Well, what do do you want now?<P><END>
Sorry, <NAME_MEMO1>, but I'm off to buy ingredients for supper!<P><END>
When my wife died, I didn't know how to do anything around the house.<P><C>
Now, I can do it as well as anyone!<P><END>
Have you ever tasted the wine from around here?<P><C>
It's worth a try.<P><END>
I've tried rice wine, but I couldn't tell you which one tasted better.<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>. A nice evening we have tonight, eh?<P><END>
I'm getting old, and I want to teach Gray so much before I die...!<P><END>
Can you believe... He won't even go mountain climbing with me now <WB>
that he's married!<P><END>
It's easier without Gray around anyway! It was like that before...<P><END>
You like mountain climbing, too, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><C>
I always close the store to go hiking on Thursdays.<P><END>
You should find a way to get some rest, too!<P><END>
