Hello there.<P><END>
Hello.<P><END>
Thanks for coming! The other people in this town never read books, you know.<P><END>
Really? But there are so many great books here!<P><END>
It's nice of you to say that.<P><END>
I'm writing a novel, actually. Do you want to read it?<P><C>
I'd love to hear your opinion.<P><END>
You're writing a book? That's incredible!<P><END>
It's not such a big deal. Do you want to read it?<P><END>
If you really want me to read it, I'd love to!<P><END>
Great! I'll bring it to you later on.<P><END>
OK.<P><END>
