Have you heard from your dad?<P><END>
Not recently.<P><END>
How could he leave my mom like that!<P><END>
You know the only reason he's away is to find a way to heal your mom!<P><C>
He's just trying to protect his family, you know.<P><END>
...I guess you're right.<P><END>
We have to take care of  things until he comes back, right?!<P><END>
Yeah, I know...<P><END>
Then stop getting so depressed! Let's head home.<P><END>
OK...<P><END>
