Hi there. I look kind of down?<P><C>
I was just remembering my parents, you see.<P><END>
My family have always been doctors. My father was a doctor and my mother <WB>
a nurse.<P><END>
They were so busy that they didn't have much time for me when I was a child.<P><C>
I was lonely, and I blamed them for not paying enough attention to me.<P><END>
But, now that I'm a doctor myself, I understand them much better.<P><C>
It's a sacred duty, being responsible for someone's life!<P><C>
Now I wish I hadn't rebelled against them so much! What a fool I was!...<P><END>
