Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>. Tomorrow we're harvesting Wine Grapes. <WB>
Do you want to help out?<P><END>
Sure!<END>
I'm too busy.<END>
Great! In that case, come by around 10AM.<P><C>
We'll pay you, of course.<P><END>
Oh yeah. We need one more person, so invite someone if you think of it.<P><END>
That's understandable. You do have your own farm to run!<P><C>
Will you ask someone for me, then? You can still come too, of course!<P><END>
