Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
Hi, Popuri.<P><END>
Hello, Zack.<P><END>
Hello, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
Have the packages arrived?<P><END>
You mean this?<P><END>
Yes, that's it.<P><END>
Would I forget your package, Popuri?<P><END>
Thanks so much! Just don't tell my mother.<P><END>
Of course not. I'm sure she'll love being surprised.<P><END>
I know. I can't wait!<P><END>
I know I'm not usually here, but I wanted to order a gift for my mom, but keep<WB>
it a secret.<P><C>
That's why I had Zack mail- order it for me.<P><END>
What is it? Can you keep a secret?<P><END>
Of course!<END>
I don't think so.<END>
OK. You have to swear not to tell anyone, though.<P><END>
My mom's birthday is coming up soon.<P><C>
I didn't want her to know I'm buying her something, so I used mail-order.<P><END>
Just don't tell Lillia!<P><END>
In that case I won't tell you!<P><END>
I can't tell someone who can't keep their lips sealed!«9»«9»«9»«9»«9»<P><END>
I'm going home now. Thanks, Zack.<P><END>
Any time, Popuri.<P><END>
Bye now!<P><END>
