You and Jeff have been married a long time, haven't you?<P><END>
Yes.<P><END>
You've known each other since you were kids, right?<P><END>
Yeah...Jeff never used to be able to do anything without me!<P><END>
He used to cling to you when we were kids, didn't he?<P><END>
He was always scared of things without me...<P><END>
Ha ha...He used to run to you when Duke bullied him too, didn't he?<P><END>
That's right! Jeff never knew how to stand up for himself to Duke...<P><C>
That's why he came running to me...<P><END>
Still, I am grateful to him for everything.<P><C>
He's been a great husband and a great dad to Karen.<P><END>
Huh, thanks for the mushy. story. Hee hee hee!<P><END>
Come by any time.<P><END>
