Let's go have the Doctor look at you, Stu.<P><END>
I think we'd better...<P><END>
But I feel fine!<P><END>
You have a fever!<P><END>
You worry about me too much, Sis!<P><END>
Please come with me to the Clinic?...<P><END>
Well, since you beg like that...OK.<P><END>
Ah, <NAME_MEMO1>. Good timing.<P><END>
all of a sudden.<P><C>
Will you do me a favor and take him to the Clinic?<P><C>
I'll go find the Doctor. It's his day off, but he'll help us out, I'm sure.<P><END>
Thanks a lot. I owe you one!<P><END>
It's just a cold. Give him rest and plenty of fluids, and he'll be fine.<P><END>
Really? I'm so relieved!<P><END>
See? I told you so!<P><END>
Is that what I get for worrying about you?<P><END>
Sorry, Sis...<P><END>
Don't forget to thank <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
Thank you, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
Will you take Stu back to his house now, please?<P><END>
