This is a very beautiful house! It deserves something special...<P><END>
What this house lacks is a Vase! Believe me, I know about such things!<P><C>
I happen to have one here I can sell for just 5000G.<P><END>
Buy Vase.<END>
Don't Buy.<END>
It's a very rare vase from the Ming Dynasty!<P><END>
Of course, you'll have to find some flowers for it yourself.<P><END>
It's good for your soul to surround yourself with beauty!<P><END>
