Healthy <END>
Unhappy <END>
Sick    <END>
Spring<END>
Summer<END>
Fall  <END>
Winter<END>
Y <END>
D <END>
Is this Chicken OK?<END>
Yes<END>
Yes<END>
Yes<END>
Yes<END>
Yes<END>
Yes<END>
No<END>
No<END>
No<END>
No<END>
No<END>
No<END>
Is this Cow OK?<END>
Is this Sheep OK?<END>
Baby Chicks can't compete. Choose another one?<P><END>
Only adults can enter. Please select another Cow.<P><END>
Only adults can enter. Please select another Sheep.<P><END>
Sorry, but this Chicken is sick. Choose another one?<P><END>
Sorry, but this Cow is sick. Choose another one?<P><END>
Sorry, but this Sheep is sick. Choose another one?<P><END>
Pregnant Cows can't enter. Please select another.<P><END>
Pregnant Sheep can't enter. Please select another.<P><END>
Shorn Sheep can't enter. Please select another.<P><END>
It's a deal, then. I'll bring it to you.<P><END>
It's a deal, then. I'll bring it to you.<P><END>
It's a deal, then. I'll bring it to you.<P><END>
In that case, select a Chicken to compete.<P><END>
In that case, select a Chicken to compete.<P><END>
In that case, select a Cow to enter.<P><END>
In that case, select a Cow to enter.<P><END>
In that case, select a Sheep to enter.<P><END>
In that case, select a Sheep to enter.<P><END>
So you don't want to enter?<END>
So you don't want to enter?<END>
So you don't want to enter?<END>
Alright. Think about it next time.<P><END>
Alright. Think about competing next time.<P><END>
Alright. Think about competing next time.<P><END>
