Hey, <NAME_MEMO1>! Listen to this!<P><END>
I was kneeling in the confession room, like I always do, and I thought<WB>
I heard a voice.<P><END>
It told me that I would meet with good fortune.<P><C>
I wonder if it was a dream, or what...?<P><END>
Are you awake, Carter?<P><END>
What's wrong at this hour?<P><END>
That thing you wanted is finally yours.<P><END>
What? You finally found one?<P><END>
I had a hard time locating it, but I finally managed to lay my hands on one.<P><END>
Thanks very much.<P><END>
Come pick it up soon. Bye now.<P><END>
I guess the voice I heard was right about the good fortune!<P><C>
I'll have to spend more time in the confessional!<P><END>
