Hey!! Where did you find this!?<P><END>
Oh...I see... You told Ann and the others for me.<P><C>
This photo shows my mother any my sister...<P><END>
You see...I...<P><C>
I didn't like where I lived, so I left my mother and sister to strike <WB>
on my own.<P><C>
When I came back, my mother had died and my sister had gone somewhere...<P><C>
Where, I just don't know...<P><C>
This town reminds me of that other one, long ago...<P><END>
I'm sorry to bother you with my story. I'm sure you don't want to hear it...<P><END>
Cliff is sleeping well...<P><END>
Bed<P><END>
