I always remember the day I left my home when it snows.<WB>
It was snowing then, too.<P><END>
Welcome. Quite a snowy day, isn't it?<P><END>
What? Cliff!?<P><END>
Dad! Come quick! It's about Cliff!!<P><END>
Thank goodness you happened by when you did, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
Thank goodness he's safe! What was he doing there?<P><END>
Thank you so much...<P><END>
Just rest, and he should be fine. Everyone should go home now.<P><END>
