Is something the matter?<P><END>
Can I help you with anything else?<P><END>
Remove a cursed tool.<END>
I want to confess.<END>
Just saying 'hi'.<END>
That will be 1,000 G.<END>
OK.<END>
No, thanks.<END>
In that case, let us pray...<P><C>
Oh Harvest Goddess, please help us remove this unjust curse...<P><END>
Sorry, but you don't seem to have enough Gold. Come back another time.<P><END>
Are you sure now?<P><END>
But nothing you have is cursed!<P><END>
Repent once each day.<P><END>
What do you wish to repent for?<P><END>
I hardly get any sleep.<END>
I'm overworking the HS.<END>
I want to marry the HG.<END>
Sleep is very important for everyone, you know!<P><C>
I know you're very busy, but you really should get some rest once in a while.<P>The Harvest Goddess has now forgiven you.<P><END>
Failing to sleep is to reject the nature granted you by the Harvest Goddess!<P><C>
You have displeased Her!<P><C>
She has not forgiven you, and someday you will pay the price.<P><END>
Do not fret. The Harvest Sprites help you because they wish to.<P><C>
However, I suggest giving then a present for their efforts to keep them happy.<P><C>
The Harvest Goddess has now forgiven you.<P><END>
What do you mean, you make the Harvest Sprites work too hard?! How dare you repay<WB>
their kindness by exploiting them! Don't you give them gifts, you scoundrel?<P><C>
The Harvest Goddess has not forgiven you, and someday you will pay the price!<P><END>
So you want to marry the Harvest goddess, do you? I'm sure she is very <WB>
flattered by your attention.<P><C>
The Harvest Goddess has now forgiven you.<P><END>
Wh-what!?...You say you want to marry the Harvest Goddess!? That's blasphemy!<WB>
Of course, I do too, but... Wait! Forget I said that!<P><C>
The Harvest Goddess has not forgiven you, and someday you will pay the price!<P><END>
I don't care for animals.<END>
Worked until I collapsed.<END>
Townspeople don't like me.<END>
Don't forget that your animals give you their own milk, eggs, and wool to use!<P><C>
Express your gratitude by caring for them well!<P><C>
The Harvest Goddess has now forgiven you.<P><END>
What do you think the animals were put into your care by the Harvest Goddess<WB>
for?!<P><C>
They give of themselves to you, so you must repay this debt by treating them as<WB>
well as you can! Oh those poor animals!<P><C>
The Harvest Goddess has not forgiven you, and someday you will pay the price!<P><END>
Your desire to work hard is very admirable. However, your body has its limits.<P><C>
If you work until you collapse, you are ignoring the limits the Harvest <WB>
Goddess has placed on us.<P><C>
Next time, take some sustenance or rest before working so hard.<P><C>
The Harvest Goddess has now forgiven you.<P><END>
What do you mean, working the body given to you by your parents into the<WB>
ground? You must show more respect and gratitude to your body!!<P><C>
The Harvest Goddess has not forgiven you, and someday you will pay the price!<P><END>
If the townspeople do not favor you, it's for a<P><C>
reason. Look inside your own heart first, then seek to make amends with those <WB>
around you.<P><C>
The Harvest Goddess has now forgiven you.<P><END>
Now even I don't like you very much! Let us end this conversation now!<WB>
The Harvest Goddess has not forgiven you, and someday you will pay the price!<P><END>
I was cruel to my animals.<END>
I slept in late.<END>
I littered in the road.<END>
The human heart is a weak thing, and often we seek to make ourselves feel better<WB>
by cruelty to those weaker in strength.<P><C>
Remember that true strength lies in kindness to fellow creatures, especially those weaker than you.<P><C>
The Harvest Goddess has now forgiven you.<P><END>
I can't believe this! How can you be so...so... cruel to poor, helpless<WB>
animals! Oh, the humanity!<P><C>
I think there is no saving such a dark soul!<P><C>
The Harvest Goddess has not forgiven you, and someday you will pay the price!<P><END>
Do not worry. Sometimes the flesh is weak even when the spirit is<WB>
willing.<P><C>
The Harvest Goddess has now forgiven you.<P><END>
Sleeping in is the sign of sloth in the heart!<P><C>
Who knows how many others you inconvenience by your laziness! You will not gain <WB>
friends living like that!<P><C>
The Harvest Goddess has not forgiven you, and someday you will pay the price!<P><END>
Throwing away your own garbage should be natural.<P><C>
Throwing away others' garbage is smiled upon by the Harvest Goddess.<P><C>
The Harvest Goddess has now forgiven you.<P><END>
........................... ........................... I'm so flabbergasted, I lost the power of speech!<P><C>
What would you think if someone threw their garbage away in your bedroom!?<WB>
You wouldn't like it, would you?!<P><C>
The Harvest Goddess has not forgiven you, and someday you will pay the price!<P><END>
That is enough for today's confession.<P><END>
Hello. How are you?<P><END>
Come again any time.<P><END>
It's locked.<P><END>
The curse on the Hoe has been lifted!<P><END>
The curse on the Watering Can has been lifted!<P><END>
