I'm starving!<P><END>
Can you try this then?<P><END>
Hey, this is great!<P><END>
You really think so?<P><END>
Oh, <NAME_MEMO1>. Welcome.<P><END>
Hi there.<P><END>
You say it's unusual for me to be at Kai's place?<P><C>
I guess so, but he invited me.<P><END>
Gray is the only person around here who knows what food in the city tastes <WB>
like.<P><C>
So, I value his opinion.<P><END>
I have to say I'm impressed with your skill, Kai!<P><END>
Thanks. Hearing that from you gives me confidence.<P><END>
I better get back to work before gramps starts complaining.<P><END>
Thanks for coming.<P><END>
Bye now.<P><END>
See you later, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
Gray's a great guy, don't you think?<P><END>
