Yo, <NAME_MEMO1>. Welcome.<P><END>
Not many people here, as usual ...<P><END>
I don't care, but that's just the way it is.<P><END>
I wonder why...? I think my cooking is good.<P><END>
Kai...!!<P><END>
What's wrong, Popuri?<P><END>
I brought lots of customers for you, Kai.<P><END>
??....Really?<P><END>
Come in, everybody!<P><END>
There are even more coming!<P><END>
Ha ha ha!! I think you invited too many to fit!<P><END>
I can't cook for so many people alone, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><C>
Will you help out?<P><END>
Boy am I tired!<P><C>
I'm glad you invited all those people for me, but it sure was hard work to <WB>
cook for all of 'em!<P><END>
I just wanted to do you a favor, Kai. I'm sorry if I overdid it...<P><END>
Maybe having so few customers is a good thing, after all!<P><END>
Thanks a lot for your help today, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
I'm beat, too! Time to go home and sleep.<P><END>
