Welcome.<P><END>
I've never seen you around here before. Are you a tourist?<P><END>
So you're the new guy at that farm? I heard about you.<P><C>
My name is Karen. How do you do.<P><END>
Hi there, <NAME_MEMO1>. Did you come to shop?<P><END>
Take your time now.<P><END>
If you just started, then you must need lots of things, right?<P><END>
I could use some help.<END>
No problem.<END>
Just wait one second.<P><END>
Dad, can we give him one bag of Seeds?<P><END>
Oh, come on!...<P><END>
Whatever happened to kindness to strangers!<P><END>
Why don't you show him some hospitality...Please?<P><END>
...OK.<P><END>
Thanks, Dad.<P><END>
See? There is a reason why you are my husband!<P><END>
Here you are. This is on the house. Don't mention it.<P><END>
It takes a lot of work to start up a farm. I'm rooting for you.<P><END>
Just let me know if you need any help.<P><END>
