Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
 telling me yesterday..."<SB>
"You mean about the<SB>
 Blue Feather?"<SB>
"What happens if a man<SB>
 gives it to another man?"<SB>
"Well, there are many<SB>
 kinds of love..."<SB>
".........."<SB>
"Who do you want to get<SB>
 one from, little sis?"<SB>
"From you, of course!"<SB>
"Aww..."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I planted Tomato Seeds,<SB>
 but nothing is happening!<SB>
 Why not?"<SB>
"Did you till the soil<SB>
 before you planted?"<SB>
"Umm...No."<SB>
"Well, that's why! You have<SB>
 to till the soil with your<SB>
 Hoe before planting. You<SB>
 also have to clear the<SB>
 field before planting if<SB>
 there is something on it.<SB>
 You can cut grass with the<SB>
 Sickle or pull it out.<SB>
 You can use a Hammer to<SB>
 break Stones or move them<SB>
 by hand.<SB>
 Finally, you can chop up<SB>
 Branches with your Axe or<SB>
move them with your hands."<SB>
"Now I see!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I tilled the earth like<SB>
 you said, then planted, but<SB>
 the next day the Seeds<SB>
 were gone! Why?"<SB>
"Did you plant the right<SB>
 Seeds? If you plant Fall or<SB>
 Summer Seeds in Spring,<SB>
they won't grow, you know."<SB>
"Really...Now that you <SB>
 remind me, Tomatoes only<SB>
 grow in Summer."<SB>
"That's why, silly!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I tilled my field, then<SB>
 planted the right Seeds<SB>
 for the season, but they<SB>
 still won't grow!"<SB>
"Have you watered them with<SB>
 the Watering Can?"<SB>
"You mean I have to<SB>
 water them, too?!"<SB>
"Of course! Nothing will<SB>
 grow without water.<SB>
 Except farm grass, of<SB>
 course."<SB>
"So that's what the<SB>
 Watering Can was for..."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I try using the Watering<SB>
 Can, but no water comes<SB>
 out! Why?"<SB>
"Well, first you have to<SB>
 fill it up, you know."<SB>
"How do you do that?"<SB>
"First you equip it, then<SB>
 go to water - like a pond,<SB>
 river, or lake - and use<SB>
 it. That's all."<SB>
"No one ever told me I had<SB>
 to fill it up..."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I used to be able to walk<SB>
 over my Seeds, but not<SB>
 when they start growing."<SB>
"Yes, you can't walk over<SB>
 crops when they grow.<SB>
 You can if you run,<SB>
 though."<SB>
"Really?"<SB>
"Yes, you can jump over one<SB>
 square of anything if you<SB>
 run, like Stones, Fences,<SB>
 or Branches."<SB>
"That's good to know."<SB>
"Just remember that you<SB>
 can't jump over things if<SB>
 there's something on<SB>
 the other side."<SB>
"Got it, brother."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"You were telling me I<SB>
 can't walk on things when<SB>
 they grow, but I can walk<SB>
 on farm grass."<SB>
"Oh yeah, I forgot. You can<SB>
 walk on grass however much<SB>
 it grows, of course."<SB>
"Grass is for walking on,<SB>
 I guess."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I think my Turnips are<SB>
 ready to harvest, so what<SB>
 do I do now?"<SB>
"If you face your crop and<SB>
 press the A Button, you<SB>
 can lift it up to harvest<SB>
 it.<SB>
 After you harvest the<SB>
 Turnip, the field will go<SB>
 back to its tilled state.<SB>
 If your crop can be<SB>
 harvested more than once,<SB>
 though, it will go back to<SB>
 a seedling."<SB>
"So you can harvest some<SB>
 crops lots of times?<SB>
 I can't wait to try."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"Can I turn a field back<SB>
 to its untilled state?"<SB>
"Sure. Just use a Hammer on<SB>
 a tilled field, then it<SB>
 won't be tilled any more."<SB>
"That's great!"<SB>
"You can also return a<SB>
 field to its untilled state<SB>
 by putting Stones,<SB>
Branches, or Lumber on it."<SB>
"That seems like another<SB>
 good way. Does it work<SB>
 if the field is watered?"<SB>
"Yes, it doesn't matter if<SB>
 the field is watered<SB>
 or not."<SB>
"Got it."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I tried to return my field<SB>
 to its untilled state like<SB>
 you said yesterday, but<SB>
 it didn't work."<SB>
"I don't know why...<SB>
 Oh! Maybe you had already<SB>
 seeded it...?"<SB>
"That's right."<SB>
"Well, if you seeded it,<SB>
 then you have to use your<SB>
 Hoe to remove the<SB>
 Seeds first. After that you<SB>
 can use your Hammer."<SB>
"Seems like an awful<SB>
 lot of work..."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"Last time you told me<SB>
 about returning a field<SB>
 to its original state.<SB>
 But, what about farm grass?<SB>
 Even when I cut it, some<SB>
 stubble remains, and then<SB>
 it grows back."<SB>
"I forgot to say. If you<SB>
 use the Hoe on a field<SB>
 after you've cut it with a<SB>
 Sickle, then it will<SB>
 become a tilled field with<SB>
 nothing on it."<SB>
"So I should use the Hoe<SB>
 right after cutting the<SB>
 grass, right?"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I put a Cucumber in the<SB>
 Basket to ship, then<SB>
 changed my mind. I can't<SB>
 take it out, though!"<SB>
"That's right. Once you put<SB>
 something in the Basket to<SB>
 ship, it's in there for<SB>
 good. You can't change<SB>
 your mind."<SB>
"And I wanted that Cucumber<SB>
 for lunch, too...!"<SB>
"Now you've learned your<SB>
 lesson. By the way, to<SB>
 ship what's in the Basket,<SB>
 hold it up, then press the<SB>
 A Button while facing the<SB>
 Shipment Box."<SB>
"I never wanted to ship it<SB>
 to begin with..."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It seems that I can only<SB>
 put shippable things in my<SB>
 Basket..."<SB>
"Of course!"<SB>
"Why is that?"<SB>
"Because you can't fill up<SB>
 the Basket with things you<SB>
 can't ship anyway, silly!"<SB>
"And I wanted to use it as<SB>
 a garbage can, too..."<SB>
"That's what you have a<SB>
 garbage can for!"<SB>
"I guess you're right."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"Cough...cough..."<SB>
"What's wrong? And why are<SB>
 you putting your hand out<SB>
 like that?"<SB>
"Today is the Spring<SB>
 Thanksgiving Festival.<SB>
 You're supposed to give<SB>
 me a Cookie!..."<SB>
"That's right! I<SB>
 did bring you a Cookie,<SB>
 I just forgot to give it<SB>
 to you. Here you are."<SB>
"I knew you wouldn't forget!<SB>
 I can't wait to give you<SB>
 something for the Winter<SB>
 Thanksgiving Festival."<SB>
"I look forward to it."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I heard that if you throw<SB>
 away trash in town, people<SB>
 won't like you."<SB>
"Of course! Not just trash,<SB>
 though. If you throw any-<SB>
 thing away in town,<SB>
 people will get upset.<SB>
 I don't blame 'em!"<SB>
"What should I do when I<SB>
 want to throw something<SB>
 away, then?"<SB>
"No one will care if you<SB>
 throw something away on<SB>
 your own farm. There's also<SB>
 a garbage can in Rose<SB>
 Square. Finally, you can<SB>
 throw things away in the<SB>
 mine and no one will<SB>
 mind."<SB>
"Let me get this straight:<SB>
 My own farm, the garbage<SB>
 can in the Square, or the<SB>
 mine, right? "<SB>
<END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I can't chop up a Stump,<SB>
 no matter how many times I<SB>
 hit it with my Axe."<SB>
"What kind of Axe are you<SB>
 using?"<SB>
"You meant there's more<SB>
 than one kind?"<SB>
"So you're using an Iron<SB>
 Axe, I guess. You can<SB>
 upgrade your Axe, as well<SB>
 as your Hoe, Sickle,<SB>
 Hammer, Watering Can, or<SB>
 Fishing Rod."<SB>
"How do I do that?"<SB>
"First you find either<SB>
 Copper, Silver, Gold, or<SB>
 Mystrile in a mine, then<SB>
 you bring the Ore along<SB>
 with the Tool to Saibara<SB>
 the blacksmith.<SB>
 Of course, the tool also<SB>
 has to be of a certain<SB>
 experience level before<SB>
 you can upgrade it. Some<SB>
 Ores will make for better<SB>
 upgrades than others."<SB>
"What do you mean by<SB>
"experience level"...?"<SB>
"I'll explain tomorrow."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
 telling me yesterday..."<SB>
"Tool experience level,<SB>
 right? You see, any time<SB>
 you use a Tool, it<SB>
 accumulates experience.<SB>
 This works even if you<SB>
 just pretend to use it,<SB>
 although it will build up<SB>
 experience quicker if you<SB>
 use if for a real job."<SB>
"I think I get it..."<SB>
"So, the level of your Axe<SB>
 was too low to use on a<SB>
 Stump. You need a Level 2<SB>
 Axe or better to chop up<SB>
 a Stump, you see. You<SB>
 can't smash a large Stone<SB>
 with an Iron Axe, either."<SB>
"So I need better Tools!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I still can't chop up that<SB>
 Stump..."<SB>
"Did you upgrade your<SB>
Axe?"<SB>
"Yes! I made it a Copper<SB>
 Axe and everything..."<SB>
"Are you charging the Axe<SB>
 before you use it?"<SB>
"I'm pressing the B Button<SB>
 lots of times..."<SB>
"That won't work. To break<SB>
 a large Stone or a Stump,<SB>
 what you need to do is hold<SB>
 down the B Button to<SB>
 charge your Tool first."<SB>
"I didn't know that..."<SB>
"If you want to cut up a<SB>
 Stump with a Copper Axe,<SB>
 you have to use it about 6<SB>
 times, even with<SB>
charging."<SB>
"That's a lot of work!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I bought a Chicken, but it<SB>
 won't lay Eggs for me!"<SB>
"Are you feeding it, sis?"<SB>
"..........."<SB>
"You're not, I see.<SB>
 Chickens need to eat, just<SB>
 like you.<SB>
Actually, they lay Eggs<SB>
 even if you don't feed<SB>
 them, as long as they don't<SB>
 become unhappy."<SB>
"How do I feed them,<SB>
then?"<SB>
"I'll explain tomorrow."<SB>
"My Chicken will be<SB>
hungry!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
 telling me yesterday..."<SB>
"Feeding Chickens, right?<SB>
 They sell Chicken Feed at<SB>
 the same place as you<SB>
 bought the Chicken."<SB>
"......"<SB>
"What's wrong?"<SB>
"They're closed today."<SB>
"Don't worry. There's<SB>
 another way. Do you have<SB>
 Corn?"<SB>
"Umm...No."<SB>
"In that case, just let<SB>
 your Chickens out for a<SB>
 few hours, and they'll<SB>
 find worms and things to<SB>
 eat on their own."<SB>
"Great! I'll go do it<SB>
now!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"You mentioned Corn<SB>
 yesterday. What if I<SB>
 did have some...?"<SB>
"There's a way to turn<SB>
 Corn into Chicken Feed.<SB>
 You know the Water Mill<SB>
 Next to the Chicken Coop?"<SB>
"What about it?"<SB>
"It will grind up Corn into<SB>
 30 bushels of Chicken<SB>
 Feed for you!"<SB>
"Where do I throw the<SB>
Corn?"<SB>
"You can throw it from<SB>
 anywhere, as long as it<SB>
 lands in the Water Wheel."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I let my Chickens out to<SB>
 eat, but they still don't<SB>
 lay any Eggs!"<SB>
"You didn't let them out<SB>
 whet it was raining, did<SB>
 you?"<SB>
"Yeah...Why?"<SB>
"They become very unhappy<SB>
 when they get rained on!"<SB>
"Really?"<SB>
"Of course! It has to be<SB>
 sunny when you let them<SB>
 out, little sis!"<SB>
"I get it now."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"How do I feed my Chickens<SB>
 the regular way?"<SB>
"Do you have Chicken Feed<SB>
 in the Feed Bin?"<SB>
"Yeah, I went out and<SB>
 bought 825 bushels from<SB>
 the Poultry Farm!"<SB>
"825 bushels! That's a<SB>
lot!"<SB>
"Well, I had 8,250G with<SB>
 me, so...."<SB>
"Just was long as you don't<SB>
 waste it."<SB>
"I won't."<SB>
"Until tomorrow, then."<SB>
"OK."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
 telling me yesterday..."<SB>
 It was about how to feed<SB>
 your Chickens, right?"<SB>
"All you do is throw<SB>
 Chicken Feed into the Feed<SB>
 Box in the Chicken Coop."<SB>
"I can put it in any Feed<SB>
 Box I want to?"<SB>
"Yeah, as long as you put<SB>
 Feed in one Feed Box for<SB>
 each Chicken in the Coop."<SB>
"I see."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"How do I get the Chicken<SB>
 Feed to put in the Feed<SB>
 Box?"<SB>
"Just press the A Button<SB>
 in front of the Feed Bin<SB>
 Door in the Chicken Coop.<SB>
 The same thing is true for<SB>
 the Feed Bin Door in<SB>
 the Barn."<SB>
"Now I think I finally know<SB>
 everything about feeding<SB>
 my Chickens!"<SB>
"Don't forget to do it,<SB>
 now!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I ran out of Chicken Feed.<SB>
 What do I do now?"<SB>
"...What do you mean,<SB>
 exactly?"<SB>
"I put Chicken Feed in all<SB>
 of the Feed Boxes in the<SB>
 Chicken Coop. Then, it was<SB>
 gone the next day, even<SB>
 though I only have 1<SB>
 Chicken..."<SB>
"Chicken Feed always only<SB>
 lasts for 1 day. So, be<SB>
 sure not to put more in<SB>
 than the number of Chickens<SB>
 in your Coop. If you do,<SB>
 it'll go to waste."<SB>
"I see."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"How can I get more<SB>
Fodder?"<SB>
"You buy it at Yodel Farm<SB>
 for 20G a bushel."<SB>
"Is that it?"<SB>
"If you plant farm grass<SB>
 Seeds, then harvest it<SB>
 with a Sickle when it's<SB>
 full grown, it'll wind up<SB>
 in the Feed Bin as Fodder.<SB>
 It will even grow back<SB>
 after a while!<SB>
 After that, all you have<SB>
 to do is pick it up at<SB>
 the Feed Bin Door,<SB>
 just like Chicken Feed."<SB>
"I get it now."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I bought a Ball, but I'm<SB>
 not sure what to do<SB>
 with it."<SB>
"If you throw it, your<SB>
 Dog will go fetch it. This<SB>
 trains your dog, you see."<SB>
"Trains him for what?"<SB>
"For instance, he'll be<SB>
 able to chase away wild<SB>
 dogs if they try to sneak<SB>
 in at night."<SB>
"How will I know if the<SB>
 wild dogs come?"<SB>
"You won't. That's why it's<SB>
 important to train your<SB>
 Dog. You can also do one<SB>
 more thing."<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"I'll tell you tomorrow."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
 telling me yesterday..."<SB>
"How to protect your<SB>
 animals from wild dogs at<SB>
 night, right?<SB>
 But first, I forgot one<SB>
 thing. You can only train<SB>
 your dog when he becomes<SB>
 fully grown."<SB>
"You can't train puppies?<SB>
 They don't like fetch?"<SB>
"No. Dogs grow quickly,<SB>
 though, so don't worry."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
 telling me yesterday..."<SB>
"Oh yeah, protecting your<SB>
 animals from wild dogs."<SB>
"First of all, don't let<SB>
 them outside. Wild dogs<SB>
can't cat inside the Barn."<SB>
"What else?"<SB>
"You can also build a Fence<SB>
 with Lumber. Wild dogs<SB>
 can't get through the<SB>
 Fence unless part of it<SB>
 is broken."<SB>
"Maybe I'll try it!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"Is there any way to keep<SB>
 wild dogs away from my<SB>
 animals other than building<SB>
 a Fence or keeping them<SB>
 inside?"<SB>
"There is one more way..."<SB>
"Like what?"<SB>
"You can use your Sickle,<SB>
 Hoe, Axe, or Hammer to<SB>
 attack the dogs."<SB>
"That sounds so violent<SB>
...!"<SB>
"In that case, do what I<SB>
 said yesterday."<SB>
"I will, bro."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"The Turnips and Cucumbers<SB>
 I was growing turned a<SB>
 funny color suddenly."<SB>
"That's because the season<SB>
 has begun to change. If the<SB>
 season changes, then some<SB>
 things will wilt if it<SB>
 becomes the wrong season<SB>
 for them."<SB>
"But they were so close to<SB>
 being harvested!"<SB>
"Too bad, but they're<SB>
 wasted now. To avoid this,<SB>
 make sure to harvest your<SB>
 crops in the correct<SB>
 season."<SB>
"And they looked so<SB>
 good, too..."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
 telling me yesterday..."<SB>
"Can wilted crops be used<SB>
 for anything?"<SB>
"Nothing at all. Just cut<SB>
 them up with your<SB>
 Sickle as soon as<SB>
 you can."<SB>
"That's it...?"<SB>
"Yes. Cut them up with your<SB>
 Sickle and plant Summer<SB>
 vegetables as soon as<SB>
 you can. "<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"How do I use my Fishing<SB>
 Rod?"<SB>
"Just equip it and press<SB>
 the B Button, right?"<SB>
"I try that, but it doesn't<SB>
 work!"<SB>
"Are you trying in a place<SB>
 where you can fish?"<SB>
"Like where?"<SB>
"Like a river, or the sea,<SB>
 or the lake behind the<SB>
 mountain. Where were you<SB>
 trying it?"<SB>
"In my house, or out in<SB>
 the field..."<SB>
"No, you definitely can't<SB>
 fish there, ha ha!"<SB>
"OK. I'll go try again."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I still can't manage to<SB>
 catch any fish."<SB>
"Are you sure to push the<SB>
 Button again when the<SB>
 lure bobs?"<SB>
"No...I was just sort of<SB>
 waiting."<SB>
"When a fish bites the<SB>
 hook, the lure will bob up<SB>
 and down. Push the button<SB>
 quickly to reel in the<SB>
 fish."<SB>
"I didn't know about that<SB>
 part..."<SB>
"Sometimes it turns out<SB>
 even then that the fish<SB>
 got away, or it was only<SB>
 garbage to begin with.<SB>
 Fishing requires lots of<SB>
 patience."<SB>
"I see."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"Typhoons are really scary,<SB>
 aren't they?"<SB>
"You bet. You can't go<SB>
 outside at all! That means<SB>
 you can't take care of your<SB>
 animals or crops. The wind<SB>
 can also destroy your crops<SB>
 or Fences."<SB>
"I can't do anything about<SB>
 it?"<SB>
"Nope. Not even the Harvest<SB>
 Sprites will go outside<SB>
 during a typhoon. All you<SB>
 can do is keep the animals<SB>
 safe in their barn."<SB>
"I'll just pray one never<SB>
 comes, then!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It looks like my Fence<SB>
 broke. How do I fix it?"<SB>
"Sorry, but you can't fix<SB>
 a broken Fence. You have<SB>
 to throw it away."<SB>
"What a waste! How do I<SB>
 do that? I tried to pick<SB>
 it up, but I can't."<SB>
"You can't pick up broken<SB>
 Fences. You have to smash<SB>
 them with your Hammer.<SB>
 Once you do, you can build<SB>
 a new Fence."<SB>
"I have to smash the Fence<SB>
 with my Hammer, huh?"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I heard that the Hot<SB>
 Spring can recuperate<SB>
 Stamina and Fatigue. Is the<SB>
 effect greater the longer<SB>
 you stay in?"<SB>
"Up to a point. One hour is<SB>
 usually plenty. Staying in<SB>
 much longer won't make<SB>
 a difference."<SB>
"I see."<SB>
"Do you know what else you<SB>
 can do in the Hot Spring?"<SB>
"No, what?"<SB>
"I'll tell you tomorrow."<SB>
"I knew you'd say that!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
 telling me yesterday..."<SB>
"I was telling you about<SB>
 other things you can do<SB>
 in the Hot Spring, right?<SB>
 You can throw an Egg in<SB>
 to make a Spa-Boiled Egg."<SB>
"That sounds delicious!"<SB>
"Just throw the Egg in<SB>
 from the hole in the Fence<SB>
 near the Hot-Spring."<SB>
"That's all?"<SB>
"That's it. By the way,Spa-<SB>
 Boiled Eggs are the same<SB>
 no matter what kind of Egg<SB>
 you throw in."<SB>
"It would be shame to use a<SB>
 Golden Egg, then!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I want my Eggs to hatch<SB>
 into baby Chicks. How do<SB>
 I do that?"<SB>
"There's a place you can do<SB>
 it in the Chicken Coop,<SB>
 you know."<SB>
"You mean the thing on the<SB>
 left side of the Chicken<SB>
 Coop?"<SB>
"That's it! It's the<SB>
 Incubator. If you put Eggs<SB>
 in it, they'll hatch in<SB>
 about 3 days.<SB>
 You can't use the Incubator<SB>
 if the Coop is already<SB>
 full, though."<SB>
"The Chicken Coop can hold<SB>
 4 Chickens before<SB>
 expanding and 8 after,<SB>
 right? Got it."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"How do I become friends<SB>
 with the townspeople?"<SB>
"That will happen naturally<SB>
 if you talk to them every<SB>
 day."<SB>
"I try, but they don't seem<SB>
 to like me much..."<SB>
"Don't worry.  They'll warm<SB>
 up to you eventually.<SB>
 If you want them to like<SB>
 you even sooner, though,<SB>
 you should give them<SB>
 presents.<SB>
 Everybody has different<SB>
 likes and dislikes,<SB>
 though, so you should<SB>
 be careful."<SB>
"I see."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I increased the size of my<SB>
 house, but it doesn't seem<SB>
to make much difference..."<SB>
"You can buy more things<SB>
 on TV Shopping, for one<SB>
 thing."<SB>
"Like what?"<SB>
"Like a Refrigerator,<SB>
 Shelf, Kitchen, and other<SB>
 Kitchen goods."<SB>
"I know I can cook with a<SB>
 Kitchen, but I don't have<SB>
 much experience cooking!"<SB>
"It's easy, sis. To start<SB>
 out, just follow recipes."<SB>
"Will you teach me?"<SB>
"Tomorrow."<SB>
"I'll be waiting, bro."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
 telling me yesterday..."<SB>
"Sure, I'll teach you how<SB>
 to cook. What Utensils<SB>
 do you have? Wait, if you<SB>
 don't even have a Kitchen,<SB>
 then you won't have any<SB>
 Utensils either."<SB>
"Why do I need Utensils?"<SB>
"You can cook many more<SB>
 things if you have<SB>
 Utensils."<SB>
"But they don't sell them<SB>
 at the Supermarket..."<SB>
"They sell them on the<SB>
 TV Shopping Network."<SB>
"I see."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
 telling me yesterday..."<SB>
"Oh yeah...Cooking,<SB>
right?"<SB>
"But first, I don't even<SB>
 have a phone in my house.<SB>
 How do I order from the<SB>
 TV shopping Network?"<SB>
"Isn't there a phone some-<SB>
 where close to you?"<SB>
"There is one at the Inn,<SB>
 now that you mention it."<SB>
"Just use that one, then."<SB>
"OK. Thanks for your<SB>
help."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I bought a Kitchen and I<SB>
 tried cooking, but every-<SB>
 thing I make turns out<SB>
 a "Failure". Why?"<SB>
"Do you actually follow a<SB>
 recipe, or just throw some<SB>
 things together?"<SB>
"Umm...The second,<SB>
I guess."<SB>
"You have to follow a<SB>
 recipe, silly! Otherwise<SB>
 you're likely to get a<SB>
"Failure"."<SB>
"But I don't know any<SB>
 recipes! Where do I<SB>
 learn them?"<SB>
"I'll teach you that<SB>
 tomorrow."<SB>
"OK. I'll be waiting."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
 telling me yesterday..."<SB>
"About learning recipes,<SB>
 right? It's easy. You can<SB>
 learn from the people in<SB>
 town, or from the TV,<SB>
 or other places, too.<SB>
 A cooking progrm is on<SB>
 on Tuesdays on the<SB>
 left channel."<SB>
"Thanks, brother! I can't<SB>
 wait to make something<SB>
 good for a change!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I finally succeeded!"<SB>
"What did you make?"<SB>
"Fried Rice."<SB>
"Did you see the recipe on<SB>
 TV?"<SB>
"Yes."<SB>
"With Fried Rice, you can<SB>
 improvise and add lots of<SB>
 other ingredients, you<SB>
 know. Try it yourself."<SB>
"Once you gain some<SB>
 experience, you can begin<SB>
 to improvise and even<SB>
 invent your own dishes."<SB>
"I can't wait to try!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"You told me before about<SB>
 watering my vegetables,<SB>
 but do I have to even when<SB>
 it rains?"<SB>
"No. That's why you welcome<SB>
 the rain when you grow<SB>
 lots of crops."<SB>
"But, the animals will get<SB>
 unhappy out in the rain,<SB>
 right?"<SB>
"Right. You can't have<SB>
 everything your way!"<SB>
"By the way, snow is<SB>
 basically like rain in<SB>
 these ways."<SB>
"I can't grow crops in<SB>
 Winter, though."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I finally bought a Cow!"<SB>
"Great!"<SB>
"But...I don't know how to<SB>
 take care of it!"<SB>
"First I'll tell you how<SB>
 to feed it.<SB>
 Just take Fodder made from<SB>
 cut farm grass to the<SB>
 Feed Box in the Barn and<SB>
 put it in."<SB>
"What if I don't have any<SB>
 farm grass?"<SB>
"Then you'll have to buy it<SB>
 from Yodel Farm. It costs<SB>
 20G a bushel, which is<SB>
 pretty expensive. So, it's<SB>
 better to make it<SB>
 yourself."<SB>
"Got it. What next?"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
 telling me yesterday..."<SB>
"Taking care of Cows,<SB>
 right?<SB>
 Today I'll tell you about<SB>
 grazing your Cows outside.<SB>
 First of all, you can't<SB>
 pick Cows up, so you have<SB>
 to push them from behind<SB>
 to get them to leave the<SB>
 Barn."<SB>
"But, sometimes I can't<SB>
 get behind them!"<SB>
"That's when you use a<SB>
 Bell to get them to move<SB>
 toward you. Once they move<SB>
 a few steps, you can move<SB>
 behind them and push.<SB>
 If the Cow's affection for<SB>
 you isn't very high, it<SB>
 might now come when it<SB>
 hears the Bell, though."<SB>
"I see."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
 telling me yesterday..."<SB>
"Today I'll tell you more <SB>
 about grazing your Cows.<SB>
 If you have a field of<SB>
 farm grass ready to be<SB>
 harvested, your Cows will<SB>
 graze on that. This saves<SB>
 you the effort of cutting<SB>
 it and bringing to to their<SB>
 Feed Boxes. It takes a<SB>
 few hours for them to<SB>
 eat, though. "<SB>
"OK."<SB>
"Also, grass grows back<SB>
 sooner after Cows graze<SB>
 on it than when you cut it<SB>
 with your Sickle."<SB>
"That's good to know!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
<SB>
"My brother is taking the<SB>
day off today, so no<SB>
Life on the Farm. Sorry."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it? But first,<SB>
 let me apologize for<SB>
 yesterday. I feel fine<SB>
 now."<SB>
"In that case, can you<SB>
 tell me some more?"<SB>
"Sure. More about taking<SB>
 care of cows, then. Today<SB>
 I'll tell you about<SB>
 brushing them. First you<SB>
 equip the Brush --"<SB>
"I don't have one!"<SB>
"The blacksmith will sell<SB>
 you one. Just face the Cow<SB>
 and use the Brush. The<SB>
 Cow will love it if you<SB>
 brush her once each day.<SB>
 That's enough, though."<SB>
"Got it."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
 telling me yesterday..."<SB>
"Taking care of Cows,<SB>
 right? Today I'll tell you<SB>
 about milking them.<SB>
 First you use the<SB>
 Milker --"<SB>
"I don't have one!"<SB>
"The blacksmith will sell<SB>
 you one. Just equip it,<SB>
 then face the Cow and use<SB>
 it to Milk her.<SB>
 Cows only give Milk once<SB>
 each day, remember."<SB>
"OK. Got it."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
 telling me yesterday..."<SB>
"Taking care of Cows,<SB>
 right? There's something<SB>
 about milking them I forgot<SB>
 to tell you."<SB>
"What?"<SB>
"You can only milk<SB>
 adult, non-pregnant Cows."<SB>
"Makes sense. I can't wait<SB>
 to drink some nice fresh<SB>
 Milk!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
 telling me yesterday..."<SB>
"Taking care of Cows,<SB>
right?<SB>
I tried milking my Cow, but<SB>
 I couldn't get any Milk."<SB>
"It was an adult?"<SB>
"Of course."<SB>
"And she was healthy?"<SB>
"She was, but she was<SB>
 unhappy."<SB>
"I should have mentioned<SB>
 that only happy Cows<SB>
 give Milk, not sick or<SB>
 unhappy Cows."<SB>
"I see."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
 telling me yesterday..."<SB>
"Taking care of Cows,<SB>
 right? Today I'll tell you<SB>
 about the size of Milk that<SB>
 Cows give.<SB>
 There are 3 sizes:<SB>
 S, M, and L."<SB>
"How are they different?"<SB>
"They look different, and<SB>
 their size is different<SB>
 as well."<SB>
"What does that mean?"<SB>
"I'll explain tomorrow."<SB>
"I knew it!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
 telling me yesterday..."<SB>
"Different sizes of Milk,<SB>
 right?<SB>
 Size determines the price<SB>
 of Milk when you sell it.<SB>
 The bigger the size, the<SB>
 more gold you get."<SB>
"How do I get bigger<SB>
sizes?"<SB>
"I'll tell you all about<SB>
 that tomorrow."<SB>
"Not again!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
"telling me yesterday..."<SB>
 About how to get bigger<SB>
 sizes of Milk, right?<SB>
 If you take good care of<SB>
 your Cows everyday, their<SB>
 Milk will get better<SB>
 naturally.<SB>
 That means talking to them,<SB>
 brushing them, and feeding<SB>
 them everyday."<SB>
"Sounds like a lot of<SB>
work!"<SB>
"By the way, when the Milk<SB>
 reaches G size --"<SB>
"What's that?"<SB>
"That's Golden Milk, which<SB>
 only comes from Cows who<SB>
 come in first place in<SB>
 the Cow Festival.<SB>
There are other sizes too."<SB>
"I've only gotten S, M, and<SB>
 L through regular daily<SB>
 care."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I think my Cow got sick!"<SB>
"But I thought I told you<SB>
 all about how to take care<SB>
 of your Cows!"<SB>
"Well, I spent so much time<SB>
 listening to you, this one<SB>
 got sick!"<SB>
"In that case, I'll tell<SB>
 you how to cure sick<SB>
 Cows.<SB>
 First, buy Animal Medicine<SB>
 from Yodel Farm, then use<SB>
 it on the sick Cow."<SB>
"Sounds easy to me."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                         <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I want more Cows. How do<SB>
 I do that?"<SB>
"You can buy another Cow<SB>
 from Yodel Farm, or use<SB>
 Cow Miracle Potion."<SB>
"That's sold at Yodel Farm<SB>
 too, right?"<SB>
"Right. If you use it on an<SB>
 adult Cow, it'll become<SB>
 pregnant. In about 20 days<SB>
 a baby Calf will be born."<SB>
"Only adult Cows can get<SB>
 pregnant? Makes sense<SB>
 to me."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
 telling me yesterday..."<SB>
"How to make new Cows,<SB>
 right?"<SB>
"Right. I used Cow Miracle<SB>
 Potion, but it didn't<SB>
 work."<SB>
"It's an adult Cow,<SB>
right?"<SB>
"Right."<SB>
"Is it healthy, then?"<SB>
"No, it's the Cow that was<SB>
 sick."<SB>
"I should have said before,<SB>
 but Cows must be healthy<SB>
 to get pregnant."<SB>
"OK."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"You know..."<SB>
"What's wrong? You don't<SB>
 seem very well."<SB>
"I think I got sick..."<SB>
"Are you sure you aren't<SB>
 exhausted? Are you doing<SB>
 things like using Tools<SB>
 in the rain or late at<SB>
 night, or staying up too<SB>
 late, or using Tools even<SB>
 though you have no<SB>
 Stamina left...?"<SB>
"Maybe...All of those."<SB>
"Some things you can do to<SB>
 keep from getting sick are<SB>
 bathing in the Hot Spring,<SB>
 or sleeping well, or<SB>
 lighting a fire in winter<SB>
 with Lumber or Branches,<SB>
 or even putting flowers in<SB>
 your Vase."<SB>
"OK. I got all that."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I finally bought a<SB>
Sheep!"<SB>
"Congratulations!"<SB>
"But I'm not sure about how<SB>
 to take care of it."<SB>
"It's not so different from<SB>
 taking care of a Cow.<SB>
 Only shipping is what you<SB>
 can ship from it."<SB>
"How so?"<SB>
"You can use Clippers to<SB>
 shear Wool from a Sheep.<SB>
 Unlike Cows, though, you<SB>
 can't shear Wool from<SB>
 Sheep everyday."<SB>
"If you say so."<SB>
"I'll tell you more about<SB>
 it tomorrow."<SB>
"I hate waiting..."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
 telling me yesterday..."<SB>
"Caring for Sheep, right?"<SB>
"After you shear a Sheep<SB>
 once, its coat won't grow<SB>
 back for a full 7 days.<SB>
 You can't get more Wool<SB>
 from it until then."<SB>
"I see."<SB>
"By the way, you can<SB>
 buy Clippers from the<SB>
 blacksmith."<SB>
"OK. I'll remember."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"Is there anything<SB>
 different about Sheep and<SB>
 Cows, other than Wool?"<SB>
"Well...The Fodder is the<SB>
 same, grazing them is the<SB>
 same, brushing is the<SB>
 same, giving them Animal<SB>
 Medicine is the same --"<SB>
"What about making them<SB>
 pregnant?"<SB>
"For that you need Sheep<SB>
 Magic Potion. Cow Magic<SB>
 Potion won't work, of<SB>
 course!"<SB>
"Makes sense to me!"<SB>
"That's the only difference<SB>
 I can think of."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I'm asking the Harvest<SB>
 Sprites to do some work<SB>
 for me --"<SB>
"That's great!"<SB>
"But, they don't do as<SB>
 much as I want them to!"<SB>
"They just aren't used to<SB>
 it yet. They have to learn<SB>
their jobs, too, you know."<SB>
"Once they get used to it,<SB>
 they'll work better,<SB>
 you mean?"<SB>
"Of course! Also, don't<SB>
 forget to give them small<SB>
 gifts as a thank-you when<SB>
 they're done."<SB>
"I'll remember!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I heard that you can train<SB>
 the Harvest Sprites.<SB>
 Is it true?"<SB>
"Yes."<SB>
"How do you do it?"<SB>
"You do it through Mini-<SB>
 Games. When you talk to a<SB>
 Harvest Sprite, you get to<SB>
 choose between asking them<SB>
 to work or playing Mini-<SB>
 Games. Choose the<SB>
 Mini-Game."<SB>
"So I can just play Mini-<SB>
 Games with them all day<SB>
 to train them really<SB>
 quickly!"<SB>
"No, you can only play once<SB>
 a day. Sorry."<SB>
"That's too bad."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
 telling me yesterday..."<SB>
 About training the Harvest<SB>
 Sprites, right? You see,<SB>
 different Mini-Games train<SB>
 different skills."<SB>
"Like what?"<SB>
"The "Harvest" Mini-Game"<SB>
makes them better at<SB>
harvesting, and the "Animal<SB>
Husbandry" and "Watering"<SB>
Mini-Games help them<SB>
improve at those things,<SB>
too."<SB>
"Makes sense to me."<SB>
"But, if you make them<SB>
 fail at the game, they'll<SB>
 actually get worse, so<SB>
 be careful."<SB>
"I will!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I guess the Mailbox isn't<SB>
 just for decoration, huh?"<SB>
"No, you'll get notices of<SB>
 new items at the store,<SB>
 or letters and cards.<SB>
 So, it's a good idea to<SB>
 check it every so often."<SB>
"You're right about that."<SB>
"Once you read letters,<SB>
 they're stored in your<SB>
 Bookshelf in case you want<SB>
 to read them again."<SB>
"Thanks. I'll keep that<SB>
 in mind."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"The town is so big, I<SB>
 still get lost sometimes!"<SB>
"If you get lost, look at<SB>
 the World Map on the Menu<SB>
 Window after pressing<SB>
 START.<SB>
 That will show you the<SB>
 layout of the town, as<SB>
 well as where you are.<SB>
 Soon enough you'll have<SB>
 it all memorized."<SB>
"That's sure handy!"<SB>
"It will also show you<SB>
 where your Dog is, which is<SB>
 useful if you can't find<SB>
 him."<SB>
"Great!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"Can I buy back a Cow that<SB>
 I've sold?"<SB>
"Sorry, but you can't.<SB>
 I guess this means you<SB>
 sold your Cow, right...?<SB>
"Yes, because I couldn't<SB>
 afford Seeds for Fall<SB>
 planting!"<SB>
"You still can't buy her<SB>
 back, whatever the<SB>
 reason. Sorry.<SB>
"And I had finally gotten<SB>
 her to give me G size<SB>
 Milk, too! What a waste!"<SB>
"Now you'll have to start<SB>
 all over with a new Cow.<SB>
 Good luck!"<SB>
"Oh, man..."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"What does the World Map<SB>
 show, aside from me and<SB>
 my Dog?"<SB>
"It also shows the location<SB>
 of your Ball and Basket."<SB>
"Why those two?"<SB>
"Well, your animals always<SB>
 stay on the farm, and the<SB>
 Harvest Sprites only work<SB>
 on the farm. What else<SB>
 would you want on there?"<SB>
"How about the location of<SB>
 all the townspeople?"<SB>
"Sorry, that's just<SB>
 not possible."<SB>
"Too bad!..."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I heard you can have<SB>
 presents giftwrapped at<SB>
 the Supermarket. What will<SB>
 they wrap, exactly?"<SB>
"Just about anything you<SB>
 could give to somebody."<SB>
"Even Stones or Weeds?"<SB>
"If you wanted to!<SB>
 But, noboody wants to<SB>
 receive Stones or Weeds.<SB>
 And, if you wrap them up,<SB>
 they'll be even less<SB>
 happy with you.<SB>
 They'll expect something<SB>
 nice, you see."<SB>
"OK."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"My Dog is growing up nice<SB>
 and strong!"<SB>
"That's great! So, he'll<SB>
 chase away wild dogs when<SB>
 they come?"<SB>
"You bet! He also comes<SB>
 when I use my Bell to call<SB>
 the Sheep and Cows that<SB>
 I have grazing."<SB>
"You've been training him,<SB>
 I see."<SB>
"I have. Right now we're<SB>
 training everyday for the<SB>
 Frisbee Tournament in<SB>
 Summer."<SB>
"He must love all the<SB>
 attention."<SB>
"He does. It's fun for me,<SB>
 too."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"My Dog has grown up<SB>
 big and strong, but my<SB>
 Horse hasn't gotten very<SB>
 much bigger."<SB>
"What? You have a Horse<SB>
 now?"<SB>
"I forgot to tell you, I<SB>
 guess. Sorry."<SB>
"That's OK. Anyway, Horses<SB>
 take longer to grow than<SB>
 Dogs. It takes them about<SB>
 a year to get become full-<SB>
 grown."<SB>
"What can I do with it<SB>
 then?"<SB>
"I'll tell you tomorrow."<SB>
"If you say so."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
 telling me yesterday..."<SB>
"About what fully grown<SB>
 Horses could do, right?"<SB>
 First, you can use Saddle-<SB>
 bags to ship things.<SB>
 Face the Horse and throw<SB>
 what you want to ship,<SB>
 and it will be done!"<SB>
"That's great! That means<SB>
 I don't have to put every-<SB>
 thing in my Rucksack,<SB>
 go out to the Shipment box,<SB>
 then take it all out again.<SB>
 How convenient!"<SB>
"That's right."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
 telling me yesterday..."<SB>
"About what fully grown<SB>
 Horses could do, right?"<SB>
"You can also ride the<SB>
 Horse, of course."<SB>
"That sounds fun!"<SB>
"It makes moving around<SB>
 much faster. You can also<SB>
 enter in Horse Races."<SB>
"That means I can bet on<SB>
 myself to win, and then<SB>
 win tons of prizes, too,<SB>
 right!"<SB>
"That's right, sis."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"Is there anything else a<SB>
 fully grown Horse is good<SB>
 for?"<SB>
"Not apart from shipping<SB>
 Items or entering the<SB>
 Horse Races, no."<SB>
"That's too bad..."<SB>
"I should tell you how to<SB>
 take care of it, though.<SB>
 Your Horse will like it if<SB>
 you talk to it and ride it<SB>
 everyday.<SB>
 You should brush it every<SB>
 day, too.<SB>
 Also, put it in the Barn<SB>
 on rainy days, just like<SB>
 your other animals."<SB>
"All that seems easy<SB>
 enough."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"What's a "Cottage?"<SB>
"It's an extra house for<SB>
 yourself that you can ask<SB>
 Gotz the Woodcutter to<SB>
 build for you. I hear<SB>
 there's another way to<SB>
 get one, but I'm not sure<SB>
 what it is."<SB>
"How is a Cottage different<SB>
 from my regular house?"<SB>
"Well, you can sleep there,<SB>
 but there is no Kitchen,<SB>
 so no Refrigerator or<SB>
 Shelves. It's basically<SB>
 just for fun."<SB>
"It's so expensive,<SB>
though!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about this really big<SB>
 fish that I caught in<SB>
 the sea last Summer.<SB>
 It looked almost like a<SB>
 squid, but huge..."<SB>
"That sounds like one of<SB>
 the legendary "King<SB>
 Fish." I bet you had to<SB>
 have a really high level<SB>
 Fishing Rod to catch it.<SB>
 I hear they only come out<SB>
 in Spring or Winter.<SB>
 There are some other<SB>
 conditions for catching<SB>
 them, but I'm not sure<SB>
 what they are."<SB>
"How many King Fish are<SB>
 there?"<SB>
"6 in all, but that's all I<SB>
 know about them. What<SB>
 did you do with the fish<SB>
 once you caught it?"<SB>
"I'll tell you that<SB>
 tomorrow."<SB>
"That's my line!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what I was<SB>
 telling you yesterday..."<SB>
"What you did with the<SB>
 King Fish, right?"<SB>
"Right. It was way too<SB>
 heavy for me to carry home,<SB>
 so I just took an ink<SB>
 rubbing of it and then<SB>
 released it back into<SB>
 the ocean."<SB>
"I can't wait to see that<SB>
 rubbing! I'm proud of you,<SB>
 sis."<SB>
"Gee, thanks!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I heard that no crops will<SB>
 grow during Winter.<SB>
 Is that true?"<SB>
"It is. Not even farm grass<SB>
 will grow under all that<SB>
 snow."<SB>
"So all I can do on the<SB>
 farm during winter is take<SB>
 care of my animals?"<SB>
"Yes. You can also do<SB>
 other things you don't<SB>
 normally have time for."<SB>
"I see."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"You said that since I<SB>
 can't grow crops in Winter,<SB>
 I ought to use the time for<SB>
 something I usually don't<SB>
 have time for.<SB>
 Do you have any<SB>
 suggestions?"<SB>
"How about digging in one<SB>
 of the mines?"<SB>
"Now that you mention it,<SB>
 I haven't done that<SB>
 at all!"<SB>
"Or, you could spend all<SB>
day fishing, for instance."<SB>
"That sounds like fun,<SB>
too!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
 telling me yesterday..."<SB>
"About what to do in<SB>
 Winter, right?"<SB>
"Is there anything else to<SB>
 do, besides fishing and<SB>
 mining?"<SB>
"Let's see...You can't farm<SB>
 anyway, so you could<SB>
 upgrade your Tools. Or,<SB>
 you could spend the time<SB>
 talking with the towns-<SB>
 people."<SB>
"I guess there are lots of<SB>
 things to do in Winter!"<SB>
"What do you want to<SB>
 do most, sis?"<SB>
"Let's see..."<SB>
"Think about it, and tell<SB>
 me tomorrow."<SB>
"OK."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I know what I want to do<SB>
 most in Winter, now."<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I think I want to dig lots<SB>
 in the mines."<SB>
"That's a good idea.<SB>
 Should I tell you more<SB>
 about them?"<SB>
"Yes please!"<SB>
"OK. That'll be<SB>
 tomorrow's subject."<SB>
"I can't wait!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
 telling me yesterday..."<SB>
"About mining, right?<SB>
 First, there are two mines<SB>
 you can go to. One is past<SB>
 the Hot Spring behind the<SB>
 mountain."<SB>
"Next to the waterfall,<SB>
 right?"<SB>
"That's it. The other one<SB>
 is on the island on the<SB>
 far side of the lake."<SB>
"Wait a second!<SB>
 How do I get to it,<SB>
 then?"<SB>
"You have to wait until<SB>
 Winter for the lake to<SB>
 freeze, then walk over<SB>
 it then."<SB>
"I hope I don't slip..."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
 telling me yesterday..."<SB>
"About mining, right?<SB>
 Today I'll tell you about<SB>
 stairs going down that you<SB>
 find when digging in the<SB>
 mine.<SB>
 Go down the stairs to get<SB>
 to deeper levels of the<SB>
 mine.<SB>
 The deeper you go, the<SB>
 more valuable things you'll<SB>
 find, so take these stairs<SB>
 whenever you find them."<SB>
"How do I get back to<SB>
 the surface, though?"<SB>
"Don't worry. You'll see<SB>
 stairs going up, too."<SB>
"Thanks. I feel much<SB>
 better now!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
 telling me yesterday..."<SB>
"About mining, right?<SB>
"Today I'll tell you how to<SB>
 do actual digging.<SB>
 Use your Hoe to dig up the<SB>
 ground of the mine.<SB>
 You'll be able to tell<SB>
 where you've dug because<SB>
 it will look the same as<SB>
 a tilled field.<SB>
 You only need to dig the<SB>
 same piece of earth once.<SB>
 Digging more than that<SB>
 won't have an effect.<SB>
"So, if nothing comes out,<SB>
 go on to the next patch<SB>
 and try. I get it!"<SB>
"Also, use your Hammer to<SB>
 smash Stones in the mine.<SB>
 Sometimes Ore will come<SB>
 out."<SB>
"OK."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"Can I wear the jewelry<SB>
 Saibara makes myself?"<SB>
"Why? Do you think that<SB>
 doing so would increase<SB>
 your HP or something?"<SB>
"I thought it might...<SB>
 Or, maybe just make me<SB>
 look prettier...<SB>
"Sorry, but you can't wear<SB>
 the jewelry yourself.<SB>
 You can ship it, though.<SB>
 I wouldn't want to sell it!<SB>
 Not after using all that<SB>
 Orichalc and gold to have<SB>
 it made in the first<SB>
 place!"<SB>
"You can sell it for a lot<SB>
 of money, though!"<SB>
"Hmm...Naww, I couldn't.<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I found something else in<SB>
 the mine, but I'm not sure<SB>
 whether it's rare and<SB>
 valuable or not."<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"An ore called<SB>
Adamantite."<SB>
"That's great, sis! You can<SB>
 give it to Saibara and<SB>
 ask him to make you a<SB>
 Maker with it."<SB>
"What's a Maker?"<SB>
"There are three kinds of<SB>
 Makers: Cheese, Yarn, and<SB>
 Mayonnaise."<SB>
"You'll tell me more about<SB>
 them tomorrow, right?"<SB>
"How'd you know, sis?"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
 telling me yesterday..."<SB>
"The Makers, right?"<SB>
"Right. Will you tell me<SB>
 what they do?"<SB>
"The Mayonnaise Maker makes<SB>
 Mayonnaise, the Cheese<SB>
 Maker Cheese, and the Yarn<SB>
 Maker Yarn! That's all<SB>
 there is to it, sis!"<SB>
"Now I feel a little<SB>
 foolish for asking...How do<SB>
 you use them, though?"<SB>
"I'll tell you that<SB>
 tomorrow."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
 telling me yesterday..."<SB>
"About using the 3 kinds of<SB>
 Makers, right?<SB>
 Well, to use the Mayonnaise<SB>
 Maker, just toss in Eggs.<SB>
 To use the Cheese Maker,<SB>
 just throw in Milk.<SB>
 Finally, to use the Yarn<SB>
 Maker, just throw in some<SB>
 Wool. That's it.<SB>
 By the way, the size of the<SB>
 Mayo, Cheese, or Yarn that<SB>
 comes out is equivalent to<SB>
 the size of what you put<SB>
 in the Maker to begin<SB>
with."<SB>
"I get it now."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"Where do the Makers go?"<SB>
"The Mayonnaise Maker goes<SB>
 in the Chicken Coop, and<SB>
 the Cheese and Yarn Makers<SB>
 in the Barn."<SB>
"That makes it easy to put<SB>
 the Eggs, Milk, or Wool in<SB>
 them, doesn't it?"<SB>
"Right. That way you don't<SB>
 have to carry them far.<SB>
 Except maybe if you're<SB>
 grazing your animals."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"How much does it cost<SB>
 to have one of those<SB>
 Makers made?"<SB>
"It requires 20,000G and<SB>
 a piece of Adamantite."<SB>
"That's very expensive!"<SB>
"It is indeed. But, once<SB>
 you buy one, it never<SB>
 breaks, and you can use it<SB>
 forever to increase the<SB>
 sale price of your farm<SB>
 goods. You'll also be able<SB>
 to cook more things."<SB>
"I see. That's still a lot,<SB>
 though...!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"Snowstorms are really<SB>
 scary, aren't they?"<SB>
"You bet. You can't go<SB>
 outside at all! That means<SB>
 you cant take care of your<SB>
 animals or crops. The wind<SB>
 can also destroy your crops<SB>
 or Fences."<SB>
"I can't do anything about<SB>
 it?"<SB>
"Nope. Not even the Harvest<SB>
 Sprites will go outside<SB>
 during a snowstorm. All you<SB>
 can do is keep the animals<SB>
 safe in their barn."<SB>
I'll just pray one never<SB>
 comes, then, just like a<SB>
 typhoon!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"Can I only find Orichalc<SB>
 and Adamantite Ores in<SB>
 the mine by the Spring?"<SB>
"That's right.<SB>
 In that mine, all you'll<SB>
 find is Mystrile,<SB>
 Adamantite, and Orichalc."<SB>
"What about in the mine<SB>
 on the lake?"<SB>
"There you can find other<SB>
 Ores that you can ship."<SB>
"So, if I want to make<SB>
 money, I should go to the<SB>
 lake, and if I want to<SB>
 upgrade or make things,<SB>
 I should go to the spring,<SB>
 right?"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I bought a Sheep and a Cow<SB>
 at Yodel Farm. The Sheep<SB>
 is full grown, but<SB>
 not the Cow. Why?"<SB>
"Cows grow more slowly than<SB>
 Sheep. That's why the Cows<SB>
 that Yodel Farm sells<SB>
 aren't full grown yet."<SB>
"But Cows won't give Milk<SB>
 unless they're full grown,<SB>
 right?<SB>
 I guess I'll just have to<SB>
 wait until it gets older!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"You can't watch TV when<SB>
 there's a typhoon or a<SB>
 snowstorm, right?"<SB>
"Right. Why?"<SB>
"Will TV programs I miss<SB>
 because of the weather be<SB>
 shown the next day, or<SB>
 maybe the next week?"<SB>
"No, they just skip those<SB>
 shows and go on with the<SB>
 next one."<SB>
"So, there's no way I can<SB>
 see shows I missed?"<SB>
"Not until they<SB>
 re-broadcast the whole<SB>
 series, no."<SB>
"That's disappointing!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I've been wondering...<SB>
 what is it I eat every<SB>
 morning?"<SB>
"Don't you know yourself?<SB>
 Basically, Bread or Rice<SB>
 Or, anything else that<SB>
 you've ever made before."<SB>
"So, I should just make<SB>
 something that recuperates<SB>
 a lot of Stamina and<SB>
 Fatigue every morning<SB>
 then, right?"<SB>
"That sounds about right."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I was up late at night<SB>
 and wanted to watch TV,<SB>
 but nothing was on.<SB>
 Why not?"<SB>
"All programs stop at<SB>
 midnight. That's why."<SB>
"Aww...And I used to like<SB>
 to stay up late watching<SB>
 TV, too."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"What determines how<SB>
 affection level changes<SB>
 when you give gifts?"<SB>
"Well, whether they like<SB>
 the gift or not, for one<SB>
 thing. Also, if you give<SB>
 them gifts too often,<SB>
 they'll have less effect.<SB>
 And, people will be more<SB>
 appreciative if the gift is<SB>
 on their birthday (assuming<SB>
 they like it, of course)."<SB>
"How do I figure out<SB>
 people's birthdays?"<SB>
"You could give them<SB>
 gifts everyday and watch<SB>
 their reaction...?"<SB>
"There's got to be a<SB>
 better way!"<SB>
"Maybe there's someone<SB>
 you can ask, then...?"<SB>
"I can't believe even you<SB>
 don't know, bro!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
 telling me yesterday...<SB>
 Do you know what people<SB>
 in town like and don't<SB>
 like?"<SB>
"Sorry, but I don't.<SB>
 But, it's also impossible<SB>
 to give everyone every-<SB>
 thing and watch their<SB>
 reactions..."<SB>
"You bet it is!"<SB>
"Still, it's a good idea to<SB>
 try giving people some<SB>
 things, and you may get<SB>
 the hang of it."<SB>
"I see."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"Do you know what day it is<SB>
 today?"<SB>
"Sure. It's the Winter<SB>
 Thanksgiving Festival."<SB>
"Yes. That mean...<SB>
 Here you go, Chocolate!"<SB>
"Gee sis, thanks! I'll try<SB>
 it right now...Mmm....<SB>
 It's delicious! "<SB>
"I'm glad you like it!"<SB>
"I do. Now I'll have to<SB>
 top it for the next Spring<SB>
 Thanksgiving Festival!"<SB>
"Great!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"The Harvest Goddess came<SB>
 and told me when my<SB>
 Pedometer reached 10,000<SB>
 steps."<SB>
"Oh yeah, I thought I heard<SB>
 something like that.<SB>
 She might also come when<SB>
 you ship a certain number<SB>
 of things, or catch a<SB>
 certain number of fish."<SB>
"Well, she herself told me<SB>
 that I didn't receive<SB>
 anything special for it.<SB>
It's no big deal, I guess."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"You don't save when you<SB>
 sleep this time, right?"<SB>
"Right. Instead, select<SB>
 Diary in the Menu Window<SB>
 or investigate the<SB>
 Diary in your house.<SB>
"So I can save anywhere<SB>
 and anytime, right?"<SB>
"Well, you can't open up<SB>
 the Menu Window when<SB>
 you're on your Horse,<SB>
 remember."<SB>
"OK, so that's the only<SB>
 time I can't save, right?<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"What's the difference<SB>
 between my Refrigerator<SB>
 and Shelves?"<SB>
"You use them for different<SB>
 things. Basically, things<SB>
 you eat go in the<SB>
 Refrigerator and every-<SB>
 thing else goes in the<SB>
 Shelf."<SB>
"I see."<SB>
"Also, you can't put Dogs,<SB>
 Chickens, or Baskets in<SB>
 either one."<SB>
"That makes sense."<SB>
"Also, you can put 99 of<SB>
 each Item in each space,<SB>
 which is more than the<SB>
 Rucksack."<SB>
"That's a lot!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"You told me yesterday that<SB>
 I could fit 99 Items in<SB>
 each space in my Shelves<SB>
 or Refrigerator. I tried,<SB>
 but it doesn't work."<SB>
"That doesn't make any<SB>
 sense...What was it?"<SB>
"Eggs..."<SB>
"If they were different<SB>
 kinds of Eggs, then you<SB>
 can't put them in the<SB>
 same space."<SB>
"I should have thought<SB>
 of that myself!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"Can you use something<SB>
 other than food Items to<SB>
 cook with?"<SB>
"Sure. Just put it in your<SB>
 Rucksack and then select<SB>
 it. But I've never heard<SB>
 of anything like that<SB>
 in a recipe!"<SB>
"But if you can use some-<SB>
 thing other than food in a<SB>
 recipe, then maybe there's<SB>
 something good you can<SB>
 make..."<SB>
"It's a possibility, I<SB>
 guess..."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"My Chicken died..."<SB>
"Of sickness?"<SB>
"Yes..."<SB>
"I forgot to put it in the<SB>
 Barn when it started<SB>
 raining...I feel awful!"<SB>
"You know, these things<SB>
 cause your reputation in<SB>
 town to go down."<SB>
"Really?"<SB>
"When it's your fault.<SB>
 Not when animals die of<SB>
 old age, of course."<SB>
"I'll be more careful<SB>
 in the future!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I ate a "Power Berry",<SB>
 but I'm not sure exactly<SB>
 what it is."<SB>
"It increases your maximum<SB>
 Stamina."<SB>
"So I can eat as many as<SB>
 I can?"<SB>
"There are only 10 in all,<SB>
 and each one increases your<SB>
 Stamina by 10. That makes<SB>
 100 in all."<SB>
"How much do I start<SB>
 out with?"<SB>
"100."<SB>
"So I can increase my"<SB>
 Stamina by 100%.<SB>
 That's great!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"Is there any way to find<SB>
 out how many Power<SB>
 Berries I've eaten?"<SB>
"If you look at the Farm<SB>
 Property page in your<SB>
 Earnings, then there's a<SB>
 picture of you and your<SB>
 name, right?"<SB>
"Right."<SB>
"Under that are some red<SB>
 circles."<SB>
"Uh-huh."<SB>
"Each one of those means<SB>
 one Power Berry that<SB>
 you've eaten."<SB>
"That's easy enough,<SB>
 I suppose.<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"If the red circles in my<SB>
 Earnings mean Power<SB>
 Berries, what do the blue<SB>
 circles next to them mean?"<SB>
"Those are the number of<SB>
 Mysterious Berries you've<SB>
 eaten. You get them from<SB>
 the Kappa. Which, I see<SB>
 you've already done..."<SB>
"What do the Mystic Berries<SB>
 do then?"<SB>
"They make you slower to<SB>
 Fatigue, so you'll collapse<SB>
 from overwork less."<SB>
"I didn't know that! I just<SB>
 thought it tasted good!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"What are the heart-shaped<SB>
 symbols on different pages<SB>
 of my Earnings book?"<SB>
"Those show you levels of<SB>
 affection people have for<SB>
 you. There can be as many<SB>
 as 10."<SB>
"So, if someone has 10<SB>
 hearts for me, then they<SB>
 like me incredibly much?"<SB>
"That's about it."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I saw something strange on<SB>
 sale at Gotz's place."<SB>
"What was it?"<SB>
"It was called "Golden"<SB>
 Lumber." Do you know<SB>
 what that is?"<SB>
"I've heard that putting<SB>
 that in your field can get<SB>
 the townspeople really<SB>
 mad at you for showing<SB>
 off."<SB>
"But why is it so<SB>
 expensive?"<SB>
"Think about it this way:<SB>
 only someone who wanted<SB>
 to boast about how rich<SB>
 they were would buy a piece<SB>
 of Golden Lumber, much less<SB>
 put it in their yard for<SB>
 everybody to see!"<SB>
"I'm tempted..."<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I bought the Golden Lumber<SB>
 and put it in my yard --"<SB>
"Why would you do that!"<SB>
"Don't get so mad at me!<SB>
 It wouldn't fit in the<SB>
 Woodbin, you see."<SB>
"That's because it's not<SB>
 like regular Lumber. You<SB>
 can put it in your Shelves<SB>
 instead, show-off..."<SB>
"I don't like everybody<SB>
 calling me names like you,<SB>
 so I think I'm going to<SB>
 move it as soon as I can!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"I heard that I can<SB>
 communicate with the Game-<SB>
 Cube version of the game."<SB>
"That's true."<SB>
"How do I do it?"<SB>
"First, do you know how to<SB>
 find the Harvest Goddess?<SB>
"No."<SB>
"I'll tell you that first,<SB>
 then.<SB>
 You know where the mine by<SB>
 the spring on Mother's Hill<SB>
 is, right?"<SB>
"Behind the Hot Spring,<SB>
 right?"<SB>
"Right. Well, the Harvest<SB>
 Goddess appears in the<SB>
 spring to the right of<SB>
 that."<SB>
"Got it. Be sure to tell me<SB>
 how to communicate<SB>
 tomorrow, OK?"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
 telling me yesterday..."<SB>
 About how to communicate<SB>
 with the GameCube, right?<SB>
 First, you have to throw an<SB>
 offering into the Goddess's<SB>
 spring to make her appear.<SB>
 Then,select"Communicate".<SB>
 That's about all there is<SB>
 to it, sis.<SB>
 I've never done it, but<SB>
 that's what I hear,<SB>
 anyway."<SB>
"I can't wait to give it<SB>
 a try and see if She<SB>
 really does appear!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"What's the Blue Feather?"<SB>
"What?! You mean they're<SB>
 already selling it at the<SB>
 Supermarket?"<SB>
"Yeah, I've seen boys give<SB>
 it to girls a few times,<SB>
 now."<SB>
"Oh, I see. The Blue<SB>
 Feather is what people use<SB>
 when they want to propose<SB>
 marriage."<SB>
"So, when those girls<SB>
 accepted the Feather, they<SB>
 were saying "Yes" ?<SB>
 How romantic!"<P><END>
Life on the Farm<SB>
                   BEGINNER<SB>
                          <SB>
"Hey big bro!"<SB>
"What is it?"<SB>
"It's about what you were<SB>
 telling me yesterday..."<SB>
"Is there something about<SB>
 the Blue Feather you don't<SB>
 understand yet?"<SB>
"I told you they were<SB>
 selling it at the Super-<SB>
 market, but they didn't<SB>
 have any when I went to<SB>
 look!"<SB>
"They wouldn't sell one to<SB>
 a girl, sis!"<SB>
"So the only way I can get<SB>
 one is to have someone<SB>
 propose to me?"<SB>
"That's right."<SB>
"That's no fair!"<P><END>
