I heard that this was the best spot for moon viewing. Can we sit together?<P><END>
Today is moon viewing, you know. Want to go together?<P><END>
Imagine meeting here! Shall we watch together?<P><END>
Today is moon viewing day, when the moon looks extra beautiful.<P><END>
Tonight the moon will be full. Do you want to go moon viewing with me?<P><END>
Yes.<END>
No.<END>
Let's sit together, shall we?<P><END>
Let's sit together, shall we?<P><END>
OK, let's watch together.<P><END>
Alright, let's watch together.<P><END>
Hee hee. You can't stay up late?<P><END>
Even though tonight's moon will be so pretty...?<P><END>
You didn't come to watch the moon?<P><END>
What a waste! It's only once a year...<P><END>
That's too bad. Are you tired?<P><END>
I'm going to bed early tonight.<P><END>
