It's so beautiful...<P><END>
I love the moon.<P><END>
It's so beautiful!<P><END>
It's wonderful...<P><END>
The moon is so pretty...<P><END>
I love gazing at the moon like this... It makes me so calm.<P><END>
It looks so BIG tonight!...<P><END>
The full moon is so bright! It's like a huge flashlight...<P><END>
The moon is so mysterious... I think we all have some deep connection to it, but<WB>
I can't put it into words.<P><END>
I've always loved the moon. Especially the pale moon visible in the morning. <WB>
Isn't that lovely?<P><END>
Is it just me, or does the moon look even more beautiful tonight than <WB>
usual?<P><END>
It's light makes everything different.<P><END>
It looks so close... Like I could reach out and touch it.<P><END>
Dad said he would come with Mom, but maybe they found a better spot.<P><C>
Or, maybe Mom decided not to come a all. She hates the mountain at night.<P><END>
The moon's so bright, I can see everything just like during the day!<P><END>
I love spending all night moongazing like this...<P><END>
Wow! Look at these! They look delicious. Thank you so much for <WB>
making them!<P><END>
You made these to share with me? Thanks!<P><C>
Mmmm...They're really good!<P><END>
You made Moon Dumplings for me? You're so sweet!<P><C>
Mmmm...They're delicious!<P><END>
Moon Dumplings? For me?<P><C>
Thanks so much! I love eating these while watching the moon! <WB>
They're delicious!<P><END>
Moon Dumplings! I tried to make some myself today, but they didn't <WB>
turn out so well...<P><C>
You mean I can have yours?<P><C>
Mmmm...They're delicious!<P><END>
The moon looks extra beautiful tonight, doesn't it?<P><END>
The moonlight makes everything look so pale and mysterious!...<P><END>
Dad said he would come with Mom, but maybe they found a better spot.<P><C>
Or, maybe Mom decided not to come a all. She hates the mountain at night.<P><END>
Moon Dumplings! I tried to make some myself today, but they didn't turn out so well...<P><C>
You mean I can have yours?<P><C>
Mmmm...They're delicious!<P><END>
Why can we see the moon so clearly tonight?<P><C>
Why is it just tonight?<P><END>
I love spending all night moongazing like this...<P><END>
