This is tomorrow's forecast!<SB>
It will be<SB>
sunny and a little hot.<P><END>
This is tomorrow's forecast!<SB>
Tonight will be cloudy,<SB>
with rain falling all day<SB>
tomorrow.<P><END>
This is tomorrow's forecast!<SB>
A typhoon will be passing<SB>
through, so lock all your<SB>
doors and windows, and put<SB>
your animals in the Barn!<P><END>
Snow<P><END>
A snowstorm!<P><END>
This is tomorrow's forecast!<SB>
Morning will bring fair<SB>
skies throughout the<SB>
entire region.<P><END>
This is tomorrow's forecast!<SB>
It will begin raining in<SB>
the morning and not stop<SB>
all day.<P><END>
Typhoon!<P><END>
This is tomorrow's forecast!<SB>
It will be a nice, crisp<SB>
and clear Fall day.<P><END>
This is tomorrow's forecast!<SB>
Morning will bring rain, and<SB>
it will be a cold day.<P><END>
Heavy thunder and lightning!<SB>
Tonight will be cloudy,<SB>
with rain falling all day<SB>
tomorrow.<P><END>
This is tomorrow's forecast!<SB>
A typhoon will be passing<SB>
through, so lock down all<SB>
doors and windows, and put<SB>
your animals in the Barn!<P><END>
This is tomorrow's forecast!<SB>
It will be a pleasant<SB>
early Spring day.<P><END>
Rain!<P><END>
Typhoon!<P><END>
This is tomorrow's forecast!<SB>
It will snow, so be careful<SB>
not to catch cold.<P><END>
This is tomorrow's forecast!<SB>
A snowstorm will hit, so<SB>
lock down all doors and<SB>
windows, and put your<SB>
animals in the Barn!<P><END>
