I'm glad your mom enjoyed my food.<P><END>
Thanks for keeping your promise.<P><END>
I just hope it did her some good.<P><END>
Me, too.<P><END>
I'm glad Rick wasn't home, though. He sure would have got mad if he saw you<P><C>
at my house!<P><END>
Yeah...<P><END>
Popuri!<P><END>
Just where do you think you're going with my sister, Kai?!<P><END>
Don't get so mad! We were just talking, and it's none of your business!<P><END>
Well, you should get back to help at the store, anyway!<P><END>
Why don't you do it yourself!<P><END>
This is your fault, Kai! You shouldn't come near my sister, ever!<P><END>
You can't talk to Kai like that!<P><END>
Popuri...<P><END>
You should get back anyway. Think about your mom.<P><END>
...But...Well, I guess so.<P><END>
You leave Popuri alone from now on, Kai!<P><END>
Sorry... See you later, Kai...<P><END>
OK...<P><END>
