That was great!<P><C>
You sure have a lot of food I've never seen before.<P><END>
Why do you know so much about other towns?<P><END>
I really hate the cold, so I always spend winters in the south.<P><C>
So, I've eaten foods from all over the world!<P><END>
Really...<P><END>
I wonder if my mom would get better if she ate your cooking...?<P><END>
Should I go make some for her?<P><END>
Would you really?<P><END>
Just leave it to me!<P><END>
Thank you, Kai!<P><END>
