We used to play here all the time.<P><END>
We played games like tag, kick the can, hide and seek...everything.<P><END>
We also wrestled... Although...I never could beat you.<P><END>
What do you mean?! I don't remember any of it!<P><END>
Don't you remember how I used to cry when you threw me to the ground?<P><END>
I told you I don't remember, so I don't remember! I'm going home now!<P><END>
What are you mad for? Wait up!<P><END>
