Carter's not here. I wonder where he is...?<P><END>
The door's open. Might as well go in...<P><END>
I love Fall, because then even I can have a little treat...<P><END>
I just can't let anyone find out about this!<WB>
Mmm...It looks delicious!<P><END>
<NAME_MEMO1>, what are you doing here?<P><END>
The door was open, so you just wandered in... It's alright...<P><END>
What was I doing...?<P><C>
I was just...um...cleaning up around here.<P><END>
Don't look at me like that! OK, I'll stop lying.<P><C>
I was hunting for Mushrooms, you see.<P><END>
This area has always been great for Mushroom hunting.<P><C>
In the Fall the Mushrooms come out, and even someone like me with no money can <WB>
have a delicious meal.<P><C>
You won't tell anybody about this spot, will you?<P><END>
Will you please keep this my secret, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><END>
Yes<END>
No<END>
You have my gratitude. As a thanks, I'll leave this back door open for you<WB>
around this time everyday.<P><C>
Come and go as you please.<P><END>
Now back to the Mushrooms...<P><END>
Don't forget about this door!<P><END>
I guess you're right... It's not right to keep a place like this all to <WB>
myself. It's too selfish.<P><C>
From now on, I'll leave this back door open for you around this time everyday.<P><C>
Come and go as you please.<P><END>
