Can you help out until about 5PM?<P><END>
Of course.<END>
Sorry, I can't.<END>
You can't work with something in your hand, you know!<P><END>
Do a good job, now!<P><END>
Do a good job, you two!<P><END>
No sloughing off, now!<P><END>
Thanks for helping out. I've deposited your pay.<P><END>
Thanks for all your help. Here is fresh grape juice.<P><END>
Look forward to tasting the Wine made of the Grapes you picked!<P><END>
Cliff, what do you think about working here at Aja Winery full time?<P><C>
The harvest is over, but Wine making is a year- round job!<P><END>
Really!?... You're serious?<P><END>
With Aja gone off to the city, it's awful hard for just Manna and me.<P><END>
Thanks. You won't regret it!<P><END>
This is all thanks to you, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
I'm glad to have you with us, Cliff.<P><C>
Now, let me show you how some other things are done around here...<P><END>
Back to work, I guess!<P><END>
Thanks for thinking of inviting Cliff, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
Now...Back to work!<P><END>
It's good to see Cliff so happy about his work.<P><END>
