Hey! The owner of this farm died a while back.<P><C>
You can't just come waltzing in here!<P><END>
What? You knew him?<P><C>
And you didn't know that he had died...?<P><END>
He died about...<P><C>
Oh, 6 months ago, I reckon. When I was cleaning out his place I found his will.<P><C>
In it, he said "I'm leaving my farm to <NAME_MEMO1>."<P><C>
So, until whoever that is shows up, I'm taking care of the farm.<P><END>
What? You say you're <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><END>
Will you tell me how you met the old man...?<P><END>
You were writing letters to each other, eh?<P><C>
And when he stopped writing back, you came to check on him, did you?<P><END>
Since he left you the farm, it's yours if you want it.<P><C>
Well, what do you think?<P><END>
Great! From here on out this place is yours!<P><END>
It won't be easy, but if you try hard you can do a job to make him proud.<P><END>
 Then, the next day...<P><END>
