Good morning, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><C>
I hear you're new to farm life, so let me explain some basics.<P><C>
Use the A Button to lift up Items in front of you, throw Items, or talk to <WB>
people.<P><C>
You can buy things if you talk to people behind a counter in a store.<P><C>
No one will sell you any- thing if the store isn't open, though, so <WB>
don't bother trying.<P><C>
Use the B Button to use an Item or Tool.<P><C>
You can't use anything if you're not holding it.<P><END>
Do you want to here even more instruction?<P><END>
Yes<END>
No<END>
OK, here goes.<P><END>
Crops<END>
Animals<END>
Useful tips<END>
Quit<END>
Are you sure? You don't have to hold back on my account.<P><C>
Well, if want to hear more later, you can just press START at any time. Got it?<P><END>
It's your farm, and you can do whatever you like.<P><C>
But, your first goal should be to make some money to live on.<P><C>
For example, you can gather various things on the mountain to sell.<P><END>
After you get a hang of the farm, try exploring the town.<P><C>
Just turn right on the street outside your farm, and you'll see Yodel Farm<WB>
and the Poultry Farm.<P><C>
Try asking there.<P><END>
Oh yes, I left you my old Pedometer in the Tool Box at your farm.<P><C>
It's always useful to know how far you've walked, don't you think?<P><END>
See you later!<P><END>
The name is Zack. I'm in charge of shipping for Mineral Town.<P><C>
Let me show you how you ship things to be sold.<P><END>
This is your Shipment Box. <WB>
Put things here you want to sell, and I'll come pick them up by 5PM everyday.<P><C>
I'll pay you money when I do.<P><END>
I don't work on holidays, though!<P><C>
Remember, I need a break once in a while, too!<P><END>
OK...<P><END>
You also have the Chicken Coop for your Chickens and Barn for Cows and Sheep.<P><END>
You can ship anything you grow or find on the mountain.<P><C>
Or, of course, Eggs, Wool or Milk from livestock.<P><END>
Work hard, but not too hard!<P><C>
If your face turns blue, that means you're about to collapse.<P><C>
If that happens, you get sent to the Clinic, and you'll be out of commission<WB>
for a while!<P><END>
Bye now. And remember: 5PM everyday!<P><END>
