I'm not feeling very well today, so the store is closed.<P><C>
Sorry, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
Rick and Popuri? They both rushed off somewhere, but I don't know where...<P><END>
Pant...wheeze...gasp...<P><END>
Rick! What's wrong! Where did you run to?...<P><END>
You weren't feeling well, so I ran to the Clinic to buy some medicine!<P><END>
You're so thoughtful...<P><END>
Pant...gasp... I brought you some medicine, Mom!<P><END>
So you went too?!<P><END>
You went too, Rick? Looks like we bought twice as much as <WB>
you need...<P><C>
Sorry, Mom...<P><END>
Don't worry about it. I'm just glad my children are so concerned about me!<P><C>
Thank you both, dears...<P><END>
Just take care, Mom...<P><END>
