There's something I want your advice on...<P><END>
What is it?<P><END>
It's about Aja.<P><END>
Your daughter? I've never seen her.<P><END>
She fought with Duke, then ran away from home.<P><END>
Really...<P><END>
Do you hear from her?<P><END>
We hear from her now and then. I wish she'd return home so we could all sit down and work it out. I can't bear to let it go on like this.<P><END>
It must be tough...<P><END>
I have an idea. I'll try convincing Aja to come back home.<P><C>
Sometimes these things work better if it's not the parent doing the talking.<P><END>
That's a good idea. I think we'd just drive her further away if we tried to<WB>
convince her ourselves.<P><END>
Thanks, Sasha and Anna. I'm glad I got this off my chest. <WB>
Friends really are important, aren't they.<P><END>
Don't mention it! That's what we're here for!<P><END>
Yeah. We love to help.<P><END>
Thanks again.<P><END>
