Welcome.<P><END>
Thank you for your coming.<P><END>
I only carry highest quality Items. Take your time.<P><END>
Hi!<P><END>
Hello, Karen. Don't see you around here very much.<P><END>
I was at the beach anyway, and wanted to check out your new shop.<P><C>
I'd heard rumors about it.<P><END>
What a beauty...!!<P><END>
Who is this?<P><END>
Umm...This is...<P><END>
My name is Won, a travelling salesman.<P><END>
Oh, I've heard about you! My name's Karen.<P><END>
Karen...That's a very beautiful name!<P><END>
Thanks!<P><C>
Why don't you show me what you have!<P><END>
Good idea!<P><END>
<NAME_MEMO1>! Get out of my way!<P><END>
You are an obstruction to business!<P><END>
You have many interesting things!<P><END>
You have good taste! Right now is golden service time,<WB>
so you can take home any one thing for free.<P><END>
Really?! Gee, thanks! I'll take this.<P><END>
Just come back, OK?<P><END>
I will! Bye now.<P><END>
Golden service time, eh? What should I take...?<P><END>
Golden service time is over! You want something, you must pay!<P><END>
