I brought 3 rare and valuable items for you today! These are special<WB>
for you.<P><END>
These 3 kinds of Apples are no ordinary Apples, you understand?<P><END>
This is the first kind. It's called SUGDW Apple.<P><END>
It's real name is very long: Super Ultra Great Delicious Wonderful Apple!<P><END>
Sometimes I can't remember all of it...!<P><END>
This is the second one: the HMSGB Apple!<P><END>
That's short for Hyper Miracle Sweet Gorgeous Beautiful  Apple!<P><END>
That one is hard to remember, too!<P><END>
Finally, I have this. It's an AEPFE Apple!<P><END>
That's short for: Angel Eternal Pure Fresh Elegant Apple.<P><END>
See? Even the name is wonderful!<P><END>
Of course, you have to eat each one to see how wonderful it really is!<P><END>
Price is 500G. Very cheap, very cheap.<P><END>
Which will it be?<END>
SUGDW<END>
HMSGB<END>
AEPFE<END>
No thanks.<END>
Thanks very much! I didn't think anyone would ever -- I mean...<WB>
You have a fine eye, sir! I'll be going now!<P><END>
You don't even have 500G? What a poor man you are!<P><END>
