Um...well...You don't seem to have enough Gold...<P><END>
Thank you very much!<P><END>
Thank you very much!<P><END>
Thank you very much!<P><END>
Really? Are you sure?<P><END>
Do you need anything else?<P><END>
Thank you very much.<P><C>
Wait a minute. Your Rucksack is full. I'll have it delivered.<P><END>
Thank you very much.<P><C>
Wait. You can't carry any more. I'll have it delivered.<P><END>
Thank you very much.<P><C>
Wait. You can't carry any more. I'll have it delivered.<P><END>
