Now, you're a new face around here...Oh, I know. you're that new boy at <WB>
the farm!<P><C>
My name is Anna, and it's a pleasure to meet you!<P><END>
Really? This is for me?<P><C>
Usually only my family gives me gifts...Thanks!<P><END>
Thank you so much! This is a wonderful surprise birthday present!<P><END>
Thanks for such a nice gift!<P><END>
Thanks! I love these!<P><END>
I hate to tell you, but... I really hate these!<P><C>
Still, it is a present, so I'll take it...<P><END>
Gross! What is it...?<P><END>
It's so cute!<P><C>
My dad says plants are cute... I don't know why.<P><END>
Why would you show something so nasty to me...?!<P><END>
How lovely! Is it a designer brand...?<P><C>
Just kidding, I bet Saibara made it, right?<P><C>
<END>
Thanks! I was just thinking I wanted one of these...<P><C>
Unlike my husband, you know what women want!<P><END>
What a nice fragrance! Women just love to receive Perfume, you know.<P><END>
Ah...a Blue Feather... I wish Basil had used one to propose to me...<P><END>
Oh, <NAME_MEMO1>. How is <NAME_MEMO6>? I can't wait to meet him!<P><END>
Can you believe it?<P><C>
Basil wants to take <NAME_MEMO6> to the mountains to make a <WB>
botanist out of him!<P><END>
Hello, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><C>
Have you ready Basil books? He has lots in the Library.<P><END>
He says that the books about this town are more popular than the ones about<WB>
plants...<P><C>
I think he wishes it were the other way around!<P><END>
Hello, <NAME_MEMO1>. I was just remembering the time when Basil chased a <WB>
butterfly off a cliff!<P><END>
Basil likes to go drinking at night...<P><C>
Men!<P><END>
Good morning, <NAME_MEMO1>. Another tough day, huh?<P><END>
I kind of envy you, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><C>
You see...I get bored with nothing to do!<P><END>
I see it's raining today. I hope Basil doesn't catch cold!<P><END>
I was praying for good weather last night, but look at this!<P><END>
That Basil doesn't care if it rains or pours.  He loves looking at plants!<P><END>
I wonder what I should do when I get home...<P><C>
Basil won't play with me anyway...Hmmph!<P><END>
Most of the wives in town gather at Rose Square around noon.<P><C>
I don't bring Basil, though. He only talks about plants!<P><END>
Hello, <NAME_MEMO1>. I'm happy to see you looking happy and healthy!<P><END>
Today is my shopping day.<P><C>
I like going to the Supermarket to buy things.<P><END>
Have you been watching the TV Shopping Network?<P><C>
I suggest a Pot. You can't cook anything without it!<P><END>
Jeff works so hard, too.<P><C>
It must be hard, running a store!<P><END>
I don't run up a tab! But...Sometimes I do forget my wallet...<P><END>
Mister......did.... ...Can you believe.... then...his wife...<P><END>
In order to heal her, Lillia's husband went off to find a flower that only<WB>
blooms in the desert once every ten years.<P><C>
I think she's lonely him...<P><C>
Maybe I shouldn't have told him about that flower!...<P><END>
Our Monday hiking days are prime family time.<P><END>
But, all we do is talk about plants! I'm worried Mary won't know about<WB>
normal things!<P><END>
Still, Mother's Hill is fun because so many things grow there.<P><END>
Maybe I'll make some more jam...<P><END>
