What's this? A new face in town? How intriguing!<P><C>
The name is Barley. How do you do.<P><END>
A birthday present for an old geezer like me?<P><C>
My granddaughter May just gave me flowers, too!<P><END>
I've loved these since I was a young whipper- snapper like yourself.<P><END>
You don't have to try to curry favor with me, young man! Thanks, though...<P><END>
Thanks. You're a thoughtful kid.<P><END>
Thanks, but I really don't need things, like this, especially at my age.<P><END>
Just what's the idea of giving me something like this?<P><END>
Thanks for showing this to me. I hope May grows up healthy and happy like you.<P><END>
Foxes can be dangerous, you know. Better to set that one free.<P><END>
What a pretty bauble. I think I'll give it to May when she gets older.<P><END>
I'll give this to May when she gets older. Thanks!<P><END>
Ahh...What a beautiful smell!<P><END>
Want to learn how to make ice cream?<P><C>
May makes me make it for her all the time.<P><C>
All you need is Sugar, Milk, and Eggs, and of of course a Whisk and <WB>
a Pot.<P><C>
May loves it when I slice up Pineapple and Apple with my knife and add it in <WB>
with Honey. Myself, I like it with Wild Grapes. You should give it a try.<P><END>
A Blue Feather, huh? Who's the lucky girl? Don't lose your nerve, now!<P><END>
Ever heard of a place called Forget-me-not Valley?<P><C>
I hear <MF>, over there is great with horses.<P><END>
I like to visit the Mayor's House on Mondays.<P><END>
Today is my Hot Spring day. Thank goodness it's sunny.<P><END>
I always feel much better after time in the Hot Spring!<P><END>
And I was going to the Hot Spring today! It always rains at the worst times!<P><END>
What are you doing here?<P><END>
It's only me and May living here, so it must be boring for someone like you.<P><END>
I check on the animals each and every morning.<P><C>
If you slack off, you never know what could happen!<P><END>
Dogs really are smart, you know. The more you play catch with a dog, the <WB>
better it'll get.<P><END>
Did you remember to Put your Cows and Chickens in the Barn?<P><END>
You'll catch cold if you're not careful!<P><END>
Did you come to play?<P><END>
Come any time you want, now!<P><END>
Is the farm working out well for you? It must be quite a job to restore that<WB>
place, but good luck!<P><END>
I bet you could do anything if you put your mind to it!<P><END>
I think the Mayor does a great job, don't you?<P><END>
Thomas' father was the Mayor too, you know. I wonder what Harris will do.<P><END>
I wonder how Saibara and Ellen are faring. We all should see each other more.<P><END>
Make lots of friends here, <NAME_MEMO1>. You won't regret it.<P><END>
Do you want to take a dip in the Hot Spring, too?<P><END>
May says the waters are too hot, so she always waits outside.<P><END>
I just love the Hot Spring! It's great to have it so close to my house!<P><END>
If I didn't have the Hot Spring to keep me going.... I don't think I could keep <WB>
up any more!<P><END>
Kids these days like to stay up late. May hates going to bed.<P><END>
I've got to get to bed. Good night...<P><END>
