Hey there? Are you a tourist? No, you're new in town?<P><C>
This town is beautiful, and the people are nice, so I bet you'll like it here.<P><C>
Me? Oh, sorry, the name's Basil. I'm studying the flora of this area.<P><C>
<END>
This is a fabulous gift. Who told you my birthday?<P><END>
Thanks a lot! Were my tastes that obvious?<P><END>
Thanks! The people of this town really are so kind...<P><END>
Thanks!<P><END>
Ahh-chew! This just triggered my allergies!<P><END>
...? Is this to throw away?<P><END>
I like animals and insects just as much as I like plants!<P><END>
Sorry, but this kind of gives me the creeps...! Why not set it free?<P><END>
Gee, thanks for the thought!<P><C>
I usually don't do much for Anna, so I'll give this to her. She'll love it.<P><END>
Thanks. I'll try giving this to Anna!...<P><END>
This smells nice... Almost like a plant!<P><END>
I've been meaning to tell you this recipe...It's for a delicious Fruit Latte.<P><C>
Take fruit like Pineapple, Apple, Wild Grape, or other fruit and put it in a <WB>
Mixer with Milk.<P><C>
It also tastes excellent with Strawberry, Grape Juice, or Honey.<P><END>
Hmm.... What an interesting custom this is!...<P><END>
You look like there's something you wan to talk about. Is there?<P><END>
Tell about job.<END>
Don't tell about job.<END>
Thanks for telling me, but I can't. I may look like I have a lot of free time,<P><C>
but I'm very busy studying plants!<P><END>
Great weather we're having today!<P><END>
Humans are just like plants. They need sunshine or they wither away...<P><END>
Plants can feel what we're thinking you know.  That's what I explain in<WB>
my new book.<P><END>
It's been raining all day!<P><END>
Plants have the most amazing life force! If you find a seed from 100 years ago,<P><C>
then give it water and sun, it'll bloom!<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>. How is <NAME_MEMO6>?<P><END>
I can't wait to bring <NAME_MEMO6> hiking! Do you think he'll like it?<P><END>
Mothers Hill is home to many different species of flora.<P><C>
That's why we came to this town in the first place!<P><END>
There are plants around here which don't grow anywhere else!<P><END>
You grow crops, don't you?<P><C>
What a great endeavor that must be!<P><END>
I'm so busy writing my books I barely have time for field work!<P><END>
What great weather we have today!<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>. Are you done for the day?<P><C>
Don't try to do everything too perfectly, or you won't hold up!<P><END>
I just love outdoor air!!<P><END>
Plants change a lot in just one week, you know. Especially if it rains or <WB>
snows!<P><END>
I just love my work!<P><END>
I thought I would be able to spend all my time with plants, but I only get to <WB>
about once a week.<P><END>
This town has great wine. I shouldn't partake as often as I do...<P><END>
This town has great air and great water, which means the plants are happy.<P><C>
It also makes for great wine!<P><END>
Do you drink wine? Mary doesn't drink much,<P><C>
but she can put a lot away when she does!<P><END>
Mary likes plants, too, but I think she wants something<P><C>
passionate, like what you have for your farm.<P><END>
