Are you <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><C>
Yes, I've heard about you. From Thomas, of course. I'm Carter. I'm delighted <WB>
to finally meet you.<P><END>
This is for me? How embarrassing!... May the Harvest Goddess bless you.<P><END>
Thank you so much.<P><C>
I get no salary, so things like this are appreciated.<P><END>
Thank you. I'm in your debt.<P><END>
May the Harvest Goddess bless you.<P><END>
Umm...Thanks...<P><END>
I'm not sure why you have chosen this as a present...<P><C>
I will ask the Harvest Goddess for guidance.<P><END>
It's so very cute!...<P><END>
I really...hate...those....<P><C>
I know they are creatures of the Harvest Goddess, but I can't help it...<P><END>
Thank you so much.<P><C>
Is it really OK to receive such a rare gift...?<P><END>
Thank you very much.<P><C>
I'm not sure what to do with it, but I'll ponder the matter with care...<P><END>
I thought something smelled lovely! Perfume, is it? Thanks so much!<P><END>
Let me tell you the recipe of something I often make for the kids.<P><C>
It's easy, so you should be able to remember it.<P><C>
All you need to do is put Strawberries and Milk in a Mixer! It's delicious!<P><C>
Sometimes I also put in Honey, Sugar, and Salt.<P><END>
I am glad for you.<P><C>
I will pray for it to go well.<P><END>
I happened to hear that the couple who run <MF>+ get along famously.<P><C>
At least, that's the rumor.<P><END>
A part-time job at the winery sounds like a lot of fun.<P><END>
Tell about the Job.<END>
Don't tell.<END>
I think Cliff needs that job more than I do.<P><C>
Why don't you tell him?<P><END>
This is indeed a Church, and I am its priest, but my faith has changed greatly.<P><END>
Now I no longer refuse those whose greatest desire is to seek compassion.<P><C>
If you want, come to confessional to see.<P><END>
Do you think that the body is trapped forever in the grave?<P><C>
No! We live on in memory, which is the heart of joy.<P><END>
In the forest behind the Church live the Harvest Sprites.<P><C>
If you make friends with them, they will aid you.<P><END>
Hello, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><C>
We have been blessed with a beautiful day indeed.<P><END>
Watching May and Stu, it's obvious to me how the people of this town have <WB>
turned out so well!<P><END>
We seem to have run into a bit of foul weather, no?<P><END>
Seems like most people, especially the children, are staying home.<P><C>
You get home, too, before you catch a cold!<P><END>
Ah, great timing. Want to hear my sermon? It can get long.<P><END>
Listen.<END>
Don't listen.<END>
In that case...<P><C>
<END>
This is the story of a perfectly normal family.<P><END>
The mother, father and their young son lived together happily. However, one day the mother took ill and died suddenly.<P><C>
The son looked at the dead body of his mother, and, being too young to truly understand, asked his father what happened.<P><C>
The father knew not what to say, but told his son that she slept very deeply.<P><C>
The son asked his father to use his allowance to buy a large alarm clock to wake her up...<P><C>
<END>
What do you think this story tells us?<P><END>
Perhaps the father learned that avoiding the word 'death' with his son failed<WB>
to solve his problem.<P><C>
<END>
Now let me see...<P><END>
Now let me see....<P><END>
Once, there was a beautiful girl. She had lips as red as cherries, and skin as white as snow.<P><C>
The girl's stepmother was a witch, who had a mirror that would answer any question.<P><C>
<END>
One day, the stepmother asked the mirror who the most beautiful person in the world was. "You, of course", said the mirror, without hesitation, and the witch was happy.<P><C>
<END>
If the mirror had answered that the little girl was the most beautiful of all, surely the witch would have killed her out of jealousy.<P><C>
<END>
The mirror knew this, and so spared the girl's life with a lie.<P><C>
<END>
Was it immoral of the mirror to lie in this case? Think about it carefully.<P><END>
This is a story of before I became a priest. I had no money, and lived in a tiny apartment.<P><C>
From my window, I could see inside the next apartment.<P><C>
There lived a couple there, and every day the woman would go out to work, leaving the husband behind.<P><C>
<END>
Over time I noticed that the husband never moved. He sat in the same place every day, sometimes talking to his wife, or shaking his head. His body never moved, though.<P><C>
One day, I saw that a fire had started in that apartment. I expected the man to flee, but he still sat there, unmoving!<P><C>
In a panic, I rushed over to the apartment to save him. When I opened the door, the place was full of smoke, but the man gazed at me with a blank expression.<P><C>
I tried to move him, but he was mysteriously heavy! When I looked down at the floor, I saw that his arms and legs were growing out of the floor!!!<P><C>
<END>
Eeeee!!!!!!!<P><C>
<END>
Sometimes I like to tell these stories just to see if you're paying attention!<P><C>
<END>
Cliff has left this town, but his destiny rests on his shoulders alone...<P><END>
I'm sure part of the reason he left was that he didn't have enough money.<P><C>
I wish I could have helped him out more...<P><END>
Cliff is doing so much better since getting the job at the winery.<P><C>
It's all thanks to you.<P><END>
You were the one who saved Cliff.<P><C>
Lately, I've been thinking that the power of humans to save other humans is truly immense.<P><END>
Do you know that Cliff comes to the Church nearly every day to confess?<P><END>
All of our sins are forgiven as soon as we desire to confess for them!<P><END>
Sometimes I wonder about Jeff.  He doesn't seem to handle stress too well...!<P><END>
It's silly to build up stress by spending time with those we don't truly like.<WB>
There is no need for it!<P><END>
Whenever the weather is bad on Wednesdays, the Doctor brings me a bottle of wine<WB>
and we talk.<P><END>
So...I actually hope it rains on Wednesdays now!<P><END>
We don't talk about anything in particular, but I still enjoy it immensely.<P><END>
Good evening to you.<P><END>
I sleep in the Church basement.<P><END>
Ha ha. Just kidding.<P><END>
Do you want to know why I don't preach in town?<P><END>
The people here live as the Harvest Goddess wants them too anyway.<P><C>
There is nothing for me to teach!<P><END>
But, this is where I live, so now I have to find another path to follow.<P><END>
