.........Hi....<P><END>
So you're the new guy at that farm, huh?<P><C>
My name? It's Cliff. Nice to meet you.<P><END>
For me?!... Thanks a lot!<P><C>
Today's my birthday, you know!<P><END>
Thanks much! You're a great guy!<P><END>
Really?... Thanks!<P><END>
Thanks!<P><END>
What in the world is this...?<P><END>
If you don't like me, you can just come out and say so, you know!<P><END>
I just love animals! Where I live, we often go up in the mountains to <WB>
catch bugs or watch deer!<P><END>
Eewwwww!!... Those things give me the creeps!<P><END>
! Where did you find something like that!?...<P><END>
Ahh..So you told Ann and the others for me.<P><C>
This photo shows me with my mother and sister.<P><C>
<END>
I didn't like the town we lived in, so I left my mother and my sister to<WB>
strike off on my own.<P><C>
When I went back, my mother had died and my sister was gone...<WB>
This town reminds me of that one very much...<P><END>
Sorry! I'm sure you don't care about my story... Thanks for the photo!<P><END>
What a pretty bauble! Can I have it? Thanks!<P><END>
Thanks!...I never thought you'd give me something so nice!<P><END>
That's very interesting what you have there... Can I have it?...Thanks!<P><END>
Ah, a Blue Feather! In the town where I grew up, we used a Blue Feather<WB>
to propose as well!<P><END>
What's up?<P><END>
Tell about part-time job.<END>
Don't tell.<END>
Hmmm...A part time job at the Winery?...You know, my money IS running out...<P><END>
I'll go ask about it tomorrow!<P><END>
Duke and Manna treat me practically like their own child!<P><END>
But...Manna always asks me to meet their daughter. I wonder why...<P><END>
Ann always makes deliveries. She's fun to talk to!<P><END>
I'm a great worker, you know! I got great plans, too!<P><END>
I'm really pleased with the job at Aja Winery!<P><END>
Everyone keeps asking if I'll be there permanently...<P><END>
Hey, <NAME_MEMO1>! How are you doing?<P><END>
How is married life? I'm sure things come up, but you two are great.<P><END>
I've been thinking about my future goals in this town...<P><END>
As long as I have enough money, I'll keep staying at the Inn.<P><END>
Ann is a good girl, and she's very nice to me...<P><END>
Her smile reminds me of something...<P><END>
I have no idea why Ann is so nice to a guy like me...<P><END>
Ann looks a lot like my sister...Especially her smile.<P><END>
What would you think if I told you I was going to stay here forever...<WB>
...at the Inn!<P><END>
I just like this town, that's all...<P><END>
I'm so grateful to Ann...<P><C>
She has always been so nice to me compared to the others!<P><END>
I used to think Ann looked like my sister, but not anymore...<P><END>
Am I going to stay at this Inn forever?<P><C>
Ha ha! Good question.<P><END>
Ann and I are getting along very well. Still... I think she pays me too<WB>
much attention...<P><END>
I used to go to Church to blame myself...But now I go to give thanks.<P><END>
I have much to be grateful for...coming to this town, meeting Ann...<WB>
...Even meeting you!<P><END>
.......................<P><END>
Hey, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><C>
I'm almost out of the money I brought with me, so I might have to leave town!<P><END>
My job at the Winery is going great! Thanks, <NAME_MEMO1>!<P><END>
Carter said my new job was a sign I belonged in this town!<P><END>
.........................<P><END>
I haven't found a job, so I've decided to leave.<P><C>
Thanks for everything.<P><END>
Is this really what I want...?<P><END>
Hey! Isn't the cellar nice and cool?<P><C>
No wonder the wine ends up tasting so good!<P><END>
This is a good town because the people who live in it are good, too.<P><END>
Hey, how are things at the farm? Never give up is your policy, right?<P><END>
Lately, I've been eating all my meals at the Inn.<P><C>
It's just like what my mom used to make me!<P><END>
