H-Hi... Umm...Can I be of service?<P><END>
Oh, so you've come to say you've just moved in?<P><C>
My name is Jeff. Pleasure to meet you!<P><END>
This is a present? For me...?<P><C>
How did you even know it was my birthday?!<P><END>
Thanks a lot! You're a swell guy!<P><END>
Gee, thanks. This is great.<P><END>
Thanks. You're very friendly!<P><END>
Sorry, but I can't say I really like things like this...<P><END>
Umm...Are you trying to make me an enemy...?<P><END>
How incredibly cute!<P><END>
Just don't bring that near me, OK...? I don't know how you can <WB>
stand it...<P><END>
You mean this is for me? Thanks, what a swell present!<P><END>
You mean this is for me? Thanks! I'm sure Sasha will love it!<P><END>
Perfume, huh? Thanks!<P><END>
So you've reached that age already, have you?<P><C>
Good luck! I'll be rooting for you!<P><END>
Do you need anything?<P><END>
Tell about part-time job.<END>
Don't say anything.<END>
Work at Duke's Winery...?<P><C>
Actually, he was kind of a bully when we were kids, so I don't like him too <WB>
much...<P><C>
Just our secret, OK?<P><END>
I hear that at the <MF>+ farm they have a flower that<P><C>
can talk, and other rare crops.<P><C>
Gosh, I'd like a flower like that at the store...<P><END>
Welcome to the store, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><C>
How goes life on the farm?<P><END>
Ahh...I'd love to meet <NAME_MEMO6>!<P><C>
Maybe I'll skip work one day to go down and see him!<P><END>
Ughh...The day is finally over! But, tomorrow is going to be tough, too!<P><END>
I'm in a fix, here. Too many people owe me money for their tabs!<P><END>
It's really not fair to Sasha, I know...We both saved up money to open the store together...<P><END>
Ah, sorry, didn't mean to unload my problems on you! Did you need something?<WB>
I'm on a break now!<P><END>
A man can really relax at home...<P><END>
Well, if it isn't <NAME_MEMO1>! Take your time, now.<P><END>
I like you because you always pay cash, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
Welcome!<P><C>
At first you should really buy seeds, you know.<P><C>
Don't worry about spending all your money, it'll come back!<P><END>
It's true! You just have to choose very carefully!<P><END>
You look like you're working too hard, just like me!<P><END>
It's a small town, so we should all try to get along. Even if there are <WB>
people we really don't...<P><END>
Ah, <NAME_MEMO1>. How is the farm coming?<P><C>
You look more and more like a farmer everyday!<P><END>
It inspires me to see you work so hard and do such a good job!<P><C>
After all, running a farm by yourself can't be easy!<P><END>
I'm going to Church now. It's my favorite place in this whole town!<P><END>
I'm going to the Clinic now.  I've got a belly ache...<P><END>
Right now I'm going to visit Doug. He gives great advice, you know.<P><END>
I like how quiet it can be, here.<P><END>
It calms the heart.<P><END>
I haven't been feeling very good, lately.<P><END>
For some reason, I feel better when I come to the Clinic.<P><END>
I don't like Wine... The taste is OK, but I can't stand the smell!<P><END>
I don't get it. Duke makes Wine himself,<P><C>
but then he pays money to Doug to drink it at the Inn! Strange...<P><END>
