Hi... Are you new around here...?<P><END>
Really? This is for me?<P><C>
...I've never received a birthday present from another guy before...<P><END>
Gee...Thanks. You're the only guy who's ever nice to me, you know.<P><END>
Thank you.<P><END>
Thanks!<P><END>
...Sorry, but I really hate these. Nothing personal.<P><END>
You should go throw this away somewhere!<P><C>
You're kinda weird...<P><END>
Ha ha ha... Such a joker...!<P><END>
Who do you think you are?! You trying to pick a fight?<P><END>
Gosh, thanks! Girls like this kind of thing.<P><C>
And, they like it when guys give it to them even more...<P><END>
This is really nice! I think I'll give it to a girl and see what happens.<P><END>
That's a nice one. You mean it's for me? Thanks!<P><END>
You want to learn how to make popcorn?<P><C>
If you want, I'll tell you. Don't forget, now!<P><C>
All you need is Corn and a Frying Pan, although it tastes better with Salt or Butter on top.<P><END>
So you're going through with the big gamble, eh? Good luck, you'll need it!<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
How's Popuri doing? I'll go visit soon.<P><END>
Hey, how's it going?<P><END>
This Inn is better than any other Inn I've ever slept in! The food is great, and <WB>
it's real cheap.<P><C>
So, I stay here every year.<P><END>
Popuri's such a sweet girl...<P><END>
If only she didn't have a brother...!<P><END>
Popuri's brother is so annoying!<P><END>
All Rick ever does is complain and insult me!<P><END>
Hmm...<P><END>
Someday, I'm gonna give Rick what he deserves!<P><END>
It's hard to be so popular with the girls, you know?<P><END>
She really likes me, too... What should I do?<P><END>
I wonder why Popuri gets so jealous all the time.<P><C>
Sometimes I think I had it better when we only saw each other once a year!<P><END>
I'm staying at the Inn by myself, but it's not as easy as you'd expect.<P><C>
Rick comes and gets drunk, then causes trouble. Can you believe it?!<P><END>
Come on over to my place some time. You're welcome there, you know.<P><END>
It seems like time passes more slowly here than where I live!<P><END>
Sorry, but I'm resting now. Come back later, OK?<P><END>
I love this beach! Next time I want to spend all year here!<P><END>
Hey there, <NAME_MEMO1>. Welcome.<P><END>
Other customers? There aren't many, I guess.<P><C>
Not that I care, much.<P><END>
Spend all the time here you like.<P><END>
