I heard that someone new had taken over the farm.<P><C>
You name is <NAME_MEMO1>, huh?<P><C>
Mine's Karen.<P><END>
A birthday present? For me? I love presents!<P><END>
Today's my birthday, too.  Did you know?<P><END>
A birthday present for me? Gee, thanks!<P><END>
Are you sure?<P><C>
I never thought I'd get a present from you, <NAME_MEMO1>!<P><END>
Are you sure you want to give me something so nice? I'm touched...<P><END>
Really? For me? I'm glad I married you, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><C>
Tee-hee...<P><END>
I can't believe you knew how much I love things like this!<P><END>
Gee, thanks! You're a sweet guy, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
I can really keep this?! I love things like this, you know!...<P><END>
Thanks, <NAME_MEMO2>. What a pleasant surprise!<P><END>
Aww, thanks! What a great gift!<P><END>
Thanks a lot.<P><END>
Thanks.<P><END>
Haven't I told you I hate things like this...?<P><END>
Sorry, but I really don't like these...<P><END>
No thanks!...<P><END>
Why don't you give that to someone who might actually like it?...<P><END>
That's very cute! Thanks for showing it to me.<P><END>
Awww, how cuuute!<P><END>
Get it away from me...quick!<P><END>
What are you thinking!?....<P><END>
For me?... What a surprise! Thanks...!<P><END>
Are you sure you're willing to give this to me...?<P><END>
This is for me...? What a surprise gift... Thanks!...<P><END>
For me? Seriously? Thanks, <NAME_MEMO2>...<P><END>
Thanks so much, <NAME_MEMO1>...<P><END>
Really? For me? You're swell, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
Gee, thanks! Can I wear it at the Festival coming up?<P><C>
It smells lovely!<P><END>
How wonderful! I hope Rick won't get mad when I tell him I got this!<P><END>
It looks so expensive! Can I really accept this?<P><C>
Yay! I can't wait to show it off!<P><END>
Mmm...This Cake looks delicious...<P><C>
Oh yeah...Today's the Spring Festival. I should go get one from Rick, too.<P><END>
I can't believe you made one for me! Thanks!<P><END>
Is this really for me? And I didn't make anything for you at the Winter Thanksgiving Festival!<P><C>
Thanks, I really appreciate it!...<P><END>
Wow, thanks!<P><C>
You remembered what I gave you at the Winter Thanksgiving Festival, didn't you? This looks delicious!<P><END>
Maybe we should go to your house for this conversation...?<P><END>
So you've finally decided to get married, huh? Good for you!<P><END>
I hope I haven't misled you, but I only like you as a friend...<P><END>
<NAME_MEMO1>! Did you know that tomorrow is the Starry Night <WB>
Festival?<P><C>
A party at our house starts at 6PM. Do you want to come?<P><END>
I'd love to!<END>
No, thanks.<END>
Great! We'll be waiting.<P><END>
Really? That's too bad...<P><END>
Tomorrow is the Starry Night Festival, so go back home by 12, OK?<P><END>
It had totally slipped my mind that I might be pregnant!<P><END>
It sure does explain the morning sickness...<P><END>
It sure doesn't feel like there's a baby in here!<P><C>
I still do feel nauseous, though...<P><END>
A few days ago, mom told me my face had changed.<P><C>
She told me I looked more like a mother.<P><END>
Huff...puff... Just walking tires me out, lately.<P><END>
I hope the baby comes out soon, and that it doesn't hurt too much!<P><END>
The big day is supposed to be tomorrow. So, Elli and the Doctor are coming over.<P><END>
<NAME_MEMO2>, don't forget to stay home tomorrow. And, come back early tonight!<P><END>
Whaaa!!!....<P><END>
The baby always keeps me up at night crying, so I don't get enought<WB>
sleep!<P><C>
I see you don't have the same problem, though!<P><END>
Do you think he gets this naughtiness from your side of the family<WB>
or mine?<P><END>
It warms my heart to see the baby healthy!<P><END>
Children seem to grow up so quickly!<P><END>
<NAME_MEMO6> is just now learning how to walk.<P><END>
Yawwn... Good morning... Raising kids sure takes<WB>
a lot out of you!<P><END>
I can't take my eyes off the baby for a second!<P><C>
<NAME_MEMO6> just loves getting into trouble!<P><END>
I can't believe how fast <NAME_MEMO6> is growing up!<P><C>
It seems like just yesterday he was an infant!<P><END>
I think I'm finally getting the hang of being a mom...<P><C>
I'm love <NAME_MEMO6> so much!...<P><END>
Sorry, but I'm not in the mood for talking right now...<P><END>
Can't you just leave me alone for now?...<P><END>
Good morning! Now what should I do first today...<P><END>
I'm just not a morning person...<P><END>
I get so tired of having to plan meals everyday...<P><END>
Don't get so worried! I'll make something.<P><END>
Good morning! Looks like a good day for working!<P><END>
Yawn... I'm still tired...<P><END>
I'm trying to figure out what to make...<P><END>
But, you might be a better cook than I am!<P><END>
Good morning! Boy did I sleep soundly!<P><END>
It's fun looking after animals!<P><END>
Lately I even enjoy planning our meals!<P><END>
And, of course I enjoy making meals!<P><END>
Morning, <NAME_MEMO2>. Looks like another sunny day!<P><END>
There's so much I want to do...I hardly know where to start!<P><END>
I'm thinking about what kind of food to make you today!<P><END>
There are so many choices to choose from...<P><END>
Welcome, <NAME_MEMO2>.<P><C>
I know, I know! I promise not to work too hard!<P><END>
Thanks for worrying about me, but you really don't have to!<P><END>
Ah, welcome, <NAME_MEMO2>!<P><END>
How is <NAME_MEMO6>? When you get home, tell him that I'll be home soon.<P><END>
I just don't want to talk right now.<P><END>
..........<P><END>
Welcome! Oh, it's you, <NAME_MEMO2>.<P><END>
I'm busy right now, slo leave me alone.<P><END>
Welcome! Oh, it's you, <NAME_MEMO2>. What's up?<P><END>
Will you do some shopping for me?<P><C>
I just need....everything! Hee-hee, just kidding!<P><END>
Welcome! What's up, <NAME_MEMO2>?<P><END>
Did you come to check on me? That's sweet of you.<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO2>. Feel free to hang out all you want.<P><END>
I gotta get working! I'll be back in the evening, OK?<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>. I like to help out at my parents' house on Sundays.<P><END>
How are you liking married life...?<P><END>
Why don't you get married, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><C>
A wife would bring some joy to your life, and make things on the farm easier!<P><END>
But, I get worried about the Chickens when it rains...<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
Do you need something?<P><END>
Keeping yourself busy, I see. Everything going well?<P><END>
How are you doing these days, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><END>
Your success at running the farm is impressive, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
Ah, <NAME_MEMO1>. What do you need?<P><END>
I can't wait for the wedding! I wonder how I'll look in my dress...?<P><END>
Hey.<P><END>
What can I do for you?<P><END>
Love!<P><END>
Just let me know if you need anything, OK?<P><END>
Sorry we don't have everything you might want.<P><END>
But, we do have everything you might need on a farm!<P><END>
My mom and dad get into fights too often...<P><C>
I wonder why my dad always loses...<P><END>
Of course, they always make up afterwards... I just don't <WB>
understand it...<P><END>
Ah, <NAME_MEMO1>. How are you doing?<P><END>
I'm impressed that someone the same age as I am is running a farm all <WB>
by himself!<P><END>
I love you!<P><END>
You surprised me! Try not to sneak up on me like that!<P><END>
I don't know why, but I find myself thinking a lot about you lately...<P><END>
Ha ha! Just kidding! Bet I had you fooled, huh?<P><END>
I was afraid it might rain today...<P><END>
The spring sure is pretty in this kind of weather...<P><END>
Hi. Good work today.<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>. Do you like the ocean?<P><END>
I love the ocean at night... The sound of the waves always calms me...<P><END>
I love it here.<P><END>
When I was a kid, I used to think I could meet the Harvest Goddess here.<P><END>
Are you drinking that?<P><END>
Wouldn't it be great if we could dissolve our troubles and just drink them away?<P><END>
Looks like it's started raining.<P><END>
Oh, what a coincidence.<P><END>
I like to rest here when it rains or snows. I get along well with the woodcutter.<P><END>
I love you, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
I like things the way they are now, learning things from Lillia and Rick, and making up for Popuri, too.<P><END>
Oh, hello, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
Can you believe it?<P><C>
Rick just seems to ignore me when Popuri's around!<P><END>
How are you doing, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><END>
I wish I had someone as dependable as you for a husband, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
Top of the morning to you, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
Helping out at the Poultry Farm has given me an idea how tough things must be for you all alone on that farm!<P><END>
Love, <NAME_MEMO1><P><END>
We eat eggs everyday! That's OK, though... I like eggs!<P><END>
Love, <NAME_MEMO1><P><END>
If you don't get home now, you'll regret it tomorrow, <NAME_MEMO1>!<P><END>
Take care now, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
