Oh, you're a new face around here, aren't you? Oh, are you <NAME_MEMO1>? Thomas mentioned you, come to think of it. Oh, sorry! My name is Manna. My husband Duke and I run the Aja Winery. Nice to meet you. There's not much around here, but at least the people are nice! Just let me know if you need anything, OK? I hope I haven't talked your ear off!<P><END>
This is for me? Thank you so much! You really are a great guy, you know that? My husband could take a lesson or two... <END>
That Duke! He's totally forgotten it's my birthday, so he's off drinking with his buddies again!<P><C>
<END>
He won't remember until tomorrow! <END>
Then he'll run to the Supermarket, and, even if it's Tuesday and they're closed<P><C>
<END>
...he'll yell at Jeff to sell him a present!<P><C>
<END>
!!!!!!!<P><C>
<END>
Then he'll give it to me as though nothing at all had happened!<P><END>
Know what I'll do then? I'll go exchange it for something I really want.<P><C>
Duke won't notice because he won't know what's inside it anyway!...<P><END>
Anyway, thanks very much! do you always give presents to the townspeople like if you're going to give them to some, you have to give to everybody, now! Not just the pretty girls, you hear?! Ha ha... Anyway, thanks again!<P><END>
Thanks! You're an uncommonly nice boy! What a refreshing thing after putting up with someone like Duke for so long...!<P><END>
Thanks. Oh yes, are you giving people what they like? Different people like different things, so be sure to watch their reactions. They won't necessarily tell you right off the bat, but if you observe them carefully, you'll be able to tell if they're happy or not.<P><END>
Sorry, but I really don't like these! I'll take it, of course, since I know you meant well. Still, I'd much prefer something I actually liked...<P><END>
Now what is this!? I like you, so I'll accept it, but others might get mad, you know! Most of the people in this town don't have very good senses of humor, so be more careful! <END>
You're not only nice, but pure as well. Stu is the same way. Sometimes he shows me icky things on purpose, though. He's still young, though, so I let him get away with it!<P><END>
Achh! Did you know I can't stand these!? I'll forgive you if you didn't know.<P><END>
Really? This is for me? I can really take it?! How much did you have to pay Saibara to make this? <END>
I didn't know Saibara also made things like this!<P><C>
Did you have to bring him the stone yourself? <END>
He demands lots of money for his work doesn't he? It's because he's such a proud man! Gray keeps rebelling against him, but for some reason he never leaves...<P><END>
It doesn't matter now, though, because he has a grandson!<P><C>
<END>
Now isn't that nice! What? You mean it's for me? I'm so glad! Thank you very much!<P><END>
Now isn't that nice! It smells lovely. I bet you're popular with the girls!<P><END>
Do you cook? I'll tell you a great recipe for Boiled Spinach? Don't forget, now. All you have to do is boil Spinach in a Pot and then put some Soy sauce on top. It's that simple! Are you sure you don't need to write it down? Well, if you say so!<P><END>
That's not for me, is it? Well, that's a relief! Well, will you tell me who the lucky girl is? Or, are you too nervous to let me know? Hee-hee...<P><END>
Listen to this, <NAME_MEMO1>. These days my daughter writes letters to me on her own once a week!<P><C>
She never used to write at all, but Sasha convinced her. Thank goodness for friends, is what I say!<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>, how are you dong? How are you enjoying the farming life? Sorry, I can't talk right now. I'm on my way to Rose Square!<P><END>
Recently I've stopped chatting with the other women at Rose Square. It's so much more fun talking with Duke and Cliff at the Bar!<P><END>
Ahh...I hope it clears up later on! Whenever I want to go somewhere it rains! I get so tired of talking only to my family... They never listen to me anyway!<P><END>
Cliff likes hearing Carter speak over at the Church. What he says never makes much sense to me, though!.<P><END>
Right now I'm going over to Anna's. Sasha is sick of me, and Lillia is in a permanent bad mood. Anna really is a saint!<P><END>
Can you believe the time?! The day seems to go so fast! I can't waste any more time talking to Duke!<P><END>
You're up early, <NAME_MEMO1>. I guess you can't sleep in if you run a farm by yourself! What? You say you sometimes do?! Well, I say once in a while you deserve a break! Don't be too hard on yourself - that's what I always say!<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>. Are you still here? You work too hard, just like Elli, Ellen's granddaughter. She not only works for the Doctor, but she also tries to help raise Stu! What a poor girl!... Stu is lonely a lot, too. Poor kid!...Don't you think so, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><END>
I know I haven't talked to you very much, but my daughter went to live in another town. And...my husband Duke spends every night drinking at the Bar! How did things get this way...?<P><END>
I get so lonely, I end up talking to lots of people, but in the end it just makes me miss my daughter even more!... You came to this town by yourself, didn't you? How brave!<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>! Have you talked to Kai much? He first came to town when he was a teenager. He asked Gotz - he's the woodcutter who lives in the mountains - to build him a cottage on Mineral Beach.<P><END>
Then, Kai painted his new house all white! What a strange thing to do! Carter was a big topic of conversation when he first came to town, too, but Kai seems to annoy all the other men. If I said I liked Kai, my Duke would blow his top! Men are so silly when they get too prideful!<P><END>
Hi, <NAME_MEMO1>. How is life on the farm? Speaking of farms, the girl of Yodel Farm left this town at the same time as my own daughter. Barley is already so old, and he's all alone! I feel so bad for him⓴c And, when she finally did come back, after 10 years, Joanna brought back a little girl with her! Barley must've been so shocked! Then, to top it off, Joanna left her little girl, May, and took off again! I feel so sorry for the poor little girl⓴c!<P><END>
Barley's daughter Joanna won't return even now. Barley says that he wouldn't give May up to Joanna even if she cam back and tried to take her away. It's none of my business, of course, but can you imagine what that would do to poor May!?⓴c<P><END>
Hi there, <NAME_MEMO1>. How is the farm going? <END>
You've never heard of Rod, have you? He's Lillian's husband, and the one who brought the shipper Zack to this town. When Rod met Zack on his travels, and heard that he had no family or job, he immediately brought him back to his own house. Things sure move a lot more smoothly around here with Zack on the job, that's for sure!<P><END>
Know what, though? Zack fell in love with Lillia! She's the wife of someone who saved him, so he can't act on it, but he can't forget his love, either! Oh, the humanity! Lillian isn't the kind of person who would ever notice it, and of course I would never tell her. "Don't trouble trouble", is what I always say!<P><END>
And how are you doing today, <NAME_MEMO1>? I just got done talking with Anna. She used to live near where my daughter lives now. I wonder what kind of life she lives⓴c<P><END>
Anna is great at making treats, so I always enjoy her visits on Saturdays.<P><END>
Listen to this! It's something I just overheard!⓴c ⓴cthen she⓴c ⓴cthen he⓴c Can you believe he said that!?<P><END>
⓴c⓴c⓴c⓴c⓴c⓴c⓴c<P><END>
I completely agree!⓴c<P><END>
No, no⓴cI think you got the story wrong! I heard⓴c<P><END>
Why do you think she⓴c<P><END>
Yes! That fits in with what I heard from⓴c<P><END>
Hello, <NAME_MEMO1>. Heard any juicy gossip lately?<P><END>
Can you believe it! Duke ran up another tab at the Supermarket! 5000G! I'm so embarrassed! He didn't even tell me!<P><END>
Jeff shouldn't even let Duke buy things on credit any more! After all, it's me who has to pay for it all! Doug also tells me that Duke calls Aja from the Inn nearly everyday! Just imagine the phone bill! What's a wife to do?!<P><END>
Hello, <NAME_MEMO1>. Ever since Cliff started coming, we all eat at the Inn on Saturdays before going to Church. It's almost like a real family!<P><END>
Cliff is a good influence on Duke, too. Today he was almost as happy as when Aja was with us! Cliff is such a nice boy, and he and Duke get along so well!<P><END>
Cliff is such a good boy, too. He's so quiet and respectful. He's been going to Church a lot, and Carter tells us what a tough life he's had. I like being almost like a mother to the boy⓴c If he wants to, he can even take over the winery from us when we retire⓴c Duke doesn't want to feel like he's giving up on Aja, but he has to look to the future too, you know?<P><END>
You have to be quiet at the Church!<P><END>
