Where did you come from? I've never seen you before.<P><C>
Oh! You're at that farm, are you?<P><C>
My name is May. Let's be friends.<P><END>
Wow! Thanks! A present from my mommy came in the mail today, too!<P><END>
I was happy... But I really wanted her to come visit...<P><END>
Thanks, thanks! I can't wait to show it to Grampa!<P><END>
This is the nicest present ever! Thank you!<P><END>
Thanks. I love presents!<P><END>
This is very pretty! Keep it a secret from Grampa...<P><END>
I won't be mad if you decide to give this to someone else.<P><END>
It's so cuute! Goooood boooooy.<P><END>
Eeek! You're such a meany!<P><END>
Can I really keep it? You're not going to take it back, are you?<P><C>
I'll wear it forever!<P><END>
This is the best present ever! I'll wear it when I get older, OK?<P><END>
Wow! Perfume! I know what it is because my mommy used to wear it all the time!<P><END>
It's so pretty! What is it?<P><END>
A few days ago, I talked with my mommy on the phone! It was nice to hear <WB>
her voice, but I hope she can come home soon...<P><END>
Hi!<P><END>
Grampa says he's too busy and too old, so he can't play with me...<P><END>
Grampa always gets quiet when I talk about Mommy...<P><END>
I feel like crying whenever Grampa looks angry or sad.<P><C>
Then he always cheers me up, though!<P><END>
I hate bad weather because it keeps me from playing outside!<P><END>
Once I caught a cold when I played outside in the rain, so now my grampa<WB>
always makes me stay in on rainy days. Pooh!<P><END>
I hope it's sunny tomorrow!<P><END>
It's my bed time!<P><END>
Sometimes I like to go to sleep with the goats. They feel all warm and furry, <WB>
and I have neat dreams.<P><END>
You should try it too! ...Good night!<P><END>
Today is Grampa's Hot Spring day.<P><END>
I hate the Hot Spring! It's too hot!<P><END>
Hi there!<P><END>
I heard there was a field of flowers above here.<P><C>
Grampa says it's dangerous, though, so I don't go.<P><END>
Hello there! I like Carter, don't you?<P><C>
He talks nice to me, and gives me treats!<P><END>
I like Stu... But sometimes I hate him, too. I don't know why.<P><END>
Won't you play with me?<P><END>
You have to work? That's too bad...<P><END>
All the adults say they're busy all the time.<P><C>
It's not fair! Maybe Carter will play...<P><END>
