You're not from around here, are you?<P><C>
My name? It's Stu. Hey, you have cows on your farm, right?<P><C>
Can I come pet one?<P><END>
Well, I really wanted Mechabot Ultror, but thanks anyway!<P><END>
Just remember next year, OK?<P><END>
Wow! Thanks!<P><END>
Thanks!<P><END>
I think maybe I'll give this to Grandma...!<P><END>
Can't you give this to somebody else?<P><END>
Gee, thanks!<P><END>
Gosh! You mean this is really for me?<P><END>
Thanks! When I get older, I'll give it to a girl I like.<P><END>
Thanks, but I won't use it, so I'll give it to my sister Elli.<P><END>
Ewww.... What's this...?<P><END>
Wow...It's pretty! We had something like it in our house...<P><C>
Elli said it was mom's.<P><END>
Hi there!<P><END>
You look like you're as bored as me!<P><END>
Hey...<P><END>
Have you ever ridden a cow? I want to do Rodeo.<P><C>
...You don't know Rodeo? Milk Cows are different from Rodeo Cows, I heard...<P><END>
Won't you play with me?<P><END>
Elli's always at work, and Grandma can't walk good, so I don't have <WB>
anyone to play with!<P><END>
Tomorrow is Church day!<P><C>
Do you go, too? Ever been to confessional?<P><END>
Carter says that we can be forgiven for everything if we truly feel sorry.<P><C>
I do sorta feel bad about putting bugs in Elli's bed.<P><END>
I'm so bored...! I wonder if May's at home?<P><END>
I wish there was someone who would take me to the Church when it was raining...<P><C>
Maybe Carter would come...<P><END>
Today isn't a Church day.<P><C>
My sis Elli is free on Wednesdays, and on Mondays May goes out with her<WB>
grandfather.<P><END>
I don't like playing mommy all day, you know!<P><END>
Hi!<P><END>
It's my bed time...<P><C>
If I stay up longer, the monsters will come get me!<P><END>
Hello!<P><END>
Carter makes really good food, you know.<P><END>
