<NAME_MEMO1>, is something the matter?<P><END>
If you say so...<P><END>
Ouch!...<P><END>
Jeff! What's wrong?!...<P><END>
It hurts! Call the Doctor...hurry...<P><END>
OK! Doctor! Doctor!<P><END>
Here is Jeff's medicine.<P><END>
Thank you.<P><END>
Hey, this isn't  Jeff's medicine!<P><END>
You're right! I'm terribly sorry.<P><C>
I'll bring the correct one right away.<P><END>
Am I gonna be okay...?<P><END>
I'm terribly sorry, Doctor.<P><END>
Well, everyone makes mistakes. Just try to be more careful.<P><END>
Take this everyday.<P><END>
Thanks, Doctor. Now I've got to get back to the store.<P><END>
I can't believe I made the same mistake as before!...<P><C>
I hope I can still become a good nurse...<P><END>
You'll make a great nurse.<END>
Hmm...<END>
Thanks for cheering me up. I have to get back to work now.<P><END>
I knew I wasn't cut out for it...<P><END>
