What's worng with her?<P><END>
I don't know⓴c<P><END>
Hi there, <NAME_MEMO1>.<P><END>
If you came to see Mary, I'd turn around and come back later.<P><END>
I don't know why, but she's in a fiercely bad mood right now.<P><END>
Whenever I try to talk to her, all she does is make a face and turn away.<P><END>
I think she's just at that difficult age...<P><END>
You're close to her age. Maybe she would open up to you.<P><END>
So...Would you do me a favor? Try talking to Mary and finding out what's wrong<WB>
with her, will you?<P><END>
You're the only person I can ask! Please...?<P><END>
Hmm...OK.<P><END>
In that case, she's on the second floor. I owe you one.<P><END>
Dad said that to you?<P><END>
I'm sorry to get you involved in this.<P><C>
I'm not in a bad mood, really.<P><END>
I'll explain to Dad. Let's go downstairs.<P><END>
You were misunderstanding me, that's all! <WB>
I was just trying to think of the plot for my next novel.<P><END>
That's good to hear! We thought you were mad at us for some reason.<P><END>
I'm sorry.<P><END>
That's OK. Did you decide anything about your new book?<P><END>
Not yet...<P><END>
Hmmm... Do you have any ideas, <NAME_MEMO1>?<P><END>
I can't think of anything.<END>
How about a farm story?<END>
How about Basil's job?<END>
It's natural you can't think of anything good on the spot.<P><C>
I've been thinking all day!<P><END>
That's a great idea! Why didn't I think of that myself!?<P><END>
I think that's a good idea. We've got a pro here, after all.<P><END>
That's a good idea.<P><END>
There are some questions I'd like to ask. Do you have time now?<P><END>
There are lots of things I have to learn. First...<P><END>
................ I think that's good enough for now. Thanks for<WB>
answering all my questions.<P><END>
Look how late it's gotten! I'm sorry to take so much time!<P><END>
Now I have enough material for my novel. Thank you, <NAME_MEMO1>!<P><END>
Something about my job! That's a great idea. What do you think, Mary?<P><END>
Hmm...I think I'll pass on that idea. Thanks anyway, though.<P><END>
That's too bad...<P><END>
I'll think a little bit more about it. <WB>
I know there's an idea just waiting for me!...<P><END>
